# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Little_Moses-003
# text = And Pharaoh's little daughter stepped down in the water
1	And	O	-	-
2	Pharaoh	B-PER	-	-
3	'	I-PER	-	-
4	s	I-PER	-	-
5	little	O	-	-
6	daughter	O	-	-
7	stepped	O	-	-
8	down	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	water	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Turkey_in_the_Straw-005
# text = Turkey in the hay, in the hay, hay, hay!
1	Turkey	B-LOC	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	hay	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	hay	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	hay	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	hay	O	-	-
13	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_Satan_Is_Real-025
# text = And then Satan came into my life
1	And	O	-	-
2	then	O	-	-
3	Satan	B-PER	-	-
4	came	O	-	-
5	into	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	life	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Fancy-033
# text = She said, "Here's your one chance, Fancy, don't let me down
1	She	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	Here	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	your	O	-	-
9	one	O	-	-
10	chance	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Fancy	B-PER	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	don	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	t	O	-	-
17	let	O	-	-
18	me	O	-	-
19	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Family_Tradition-006
# text = "Hank, why do you drink, Hank, why do you roll smoke?
1	"	O	-	-
2	Hank	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	why	O	-	-
5	do	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	drink	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Hank	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	why	O	-	-
12	do	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-
14	roll	O	-	-
15	smoke	O	-	-
16	?	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-John_Prine_Sweet_Revenge
# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Sweet_Revenge-001
# text = I got kicked off of Noah's Ark, I turn my cheek to unkind remarks
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	kicked	O	-	-
4	off	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	Noah	B-PER	-	-
7	'	I-PER	-	-
8	s	I-PER	-	-
9	Ark	0	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	turn	O	-	-
13	my	O	-	-
14	cheek	O	-	-
15	to	O	-	-
16	unkind	O	-	-
17	remarks	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Dangerous_Dan_McGrew-004
# text = And watching his luck was his light-o'-love, the lady that's known as Lou
1	And	O	-	-
2	watching	O	-	-
3	his	O	-	-
4	luck	O	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	his	O	-	-
7	light	O	-	-
8	-	O	-	-
9	o	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	love	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	lady	O	-	-
16	that	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-
18	s	O	-	-
19	known	O	-	-
20	as	O	-	-
21	Lou	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Patches-003
# text = I was so ragged that folks used to call me Patches
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	so	O	-	-
4	ragged	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	folks	O	-	-
7	used	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	call	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	Patches	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Big_In_Vegas-025
# text = La la la la la, big in Vegas...
1	La	O	-	-
2	la	O	-	-
3	la	O	-	-
4	la	O	-	-
5	la	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	big	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Vegas	B-LOC	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Automatic-021
# text = Boys would call the girls
1	Boys	O	-	-
2	would	O	-	-
3	call	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	girls	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_My_Little_Lady-013
# text = Oh, Sadie, my little lady, I love no one but you
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Sadie	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	little	O	-	-
7	lady	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	love	O	-	-
11	no	O	-	-
12	one	O	-	-
13	but	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Country_State_Of_Mind-010
# text = Mama and old Aunt Joan probably in the dinin' room tryin' to use the phone
1	Mama	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	old	O	-	-
4	Aunt	O	-	-
5	Joan	B-PER	-	-
6	probably	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	dinin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	room	O	-	-
12	tryin	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	to	O	-	-
15	use	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	phone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_New_San_Antonio_Rose-015
# text = For that moonlit pass by the Alamo
1	For	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	moonlit	O	-	-
4	pass	O	-	-
5	by	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Alamo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-035
# text = Sioux City, Cedar City, Dodge City, what a pity
1	Sioux	B-LOC	-	-
2	City	I-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Cedar	B-LOC	-	-
5	City	I-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Dodge	B-LOC	-	-
8	City	I-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	what	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	pity	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Sylvia_s_Mother-011
# text = Please, Mrs. Avery, I just want to tell
1	Please	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Mrs	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Avery	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	just	O	-	-
9	want	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	tell	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-026
# text = La da da la la la Bobby McGee
1	La	O	-	-
2	da	O	-	-
3	da	O	-	-
4	la	O	-	-
5	la	O	-	-
6	la	O	-	-
7	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
8	McGee	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Bonnie_Blue_Flag-055
# text = So cheer for the Bonnie Blue Flag
1	So	O	-	-
2	cheer	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Bonnie	B-ORG	-	-
6	Blue	I-ORG	-	-
7	Flag	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_King_Is_Gone_So_Are_You_-009
# text = Yabba Dabba Doo, the King is gone
1	Yabba	0	-	-
2	Dabba	0	-	-
3	Doo	0	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	King	O	-	-
7	is	O	-	-
8	gone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-030
# text = La da da la me and Bobby McGee (Ha, ho, hey, ho!)
1	La	O	-	-
2	da	O	-	-
3	da	O	-	-
4	la	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
8	McGee	I-PER	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Ha	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	ho	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	hey	O	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	ho	O	-	-
17	!	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Don_t_Rock_the_Jukebox-004
# text = For the Rolling Stones
1	For	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Rolling	B-ORG	-	-
4	Stones	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Glen_Campbell_Wichita_Lineman-006
# text = And the Wichita lineman
1	And	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Wichita	B-LOC	-	-
4	lineman	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-015
# text = Bobby shared the secrets of my soul
1	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
2	shared	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	secrets	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	soul	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Where_I_Come_From-031
# text = And starin' up at heaven, where I come from
1	And	O	-	-
2	starin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	at	O	-	-
6	heaven	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	where	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	come	O	-	-
11	from	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-018
# text = Tennessee, Hennessey, Chicopee Spirit Lake
1	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Hennessey	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Chicopee	B-LOC	-	-
6	Spirit	B-LOC	-	-
7	Lake	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_Old_Log_Cabin_for_Sale-003
# text = A stranger was standing in silence his eyes firmly fixed on the door
1	A	O	-	-
2	stranger	O	-	-
3	was	O	-	-
4	standing	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	silence	O	-	-
7	his	O	-	-
8	eyes	O	-	-
9	firmly	O	-	-
10	fixed	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	door	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Where_I_Come_From
# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Where_I_Come_From-001
# text = Well, I was rollin' wheels and shiftin' gears 'round that Jersey Turnpike
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	rollin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	wheels	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	shiftin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	gears	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	round	O	-	-
14	that	O	-	-
15	Jersey	B-LOC	-	-
16	Turnpike	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dixie_On_My_Mind-017
# text = And show 'em how they raise hell in Caroline
1	And	O	-	-
2	show	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	em	O	-	-
5	how	O	-	-
6	they	O	-	-
7	raise	O	-	-
8	hell	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Caroline	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Little_Moses-020
# text = Little Moses, the servant of God
1	Little	O	-	-
2	Moses	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	servant	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tammy_Wynette_My_Elusive_Dreams-015
# text = G: To a gold mine in Alaska
1	G	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	To	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	gold	O	-	-
6	mine	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Alaska	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Lonesome_Pine_Special-022
# text = Give me back my home in Texas
1	Give	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	back	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	home	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Texas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus-006
# text = I see Jesus over in the Promised Land
1	I	O	-	-
2	see	O	-	-
3	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
4	over	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Promised	B-LOC	-	-
8	Land	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Patsy_Cline_Dear_God-008
# text = Chorus:
1	Chorus	O	-	-
2	:	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Callin_Baton_Rouge-008
# text = I need a cup of coffee and a couple dollars change, callin' Baton Rouge
1	I	O	-	-
2	need	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	cup	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	coffee	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	couple	O	-	-
10	dollars	O	-	-
11	change	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	callin	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	Baton	B-LOC	-	-
16	Rouge	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lefty_Frizzell_Saginaw_Michigan-026
# text = He's ashamed to show his face in Saginaw, Michigan
1	He	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	ashamed	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	show	O	-	-
7	his	O	-	-
8	face	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Saginaw	B-LOC	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Michigan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Paul_s_Ministry-011
# text = He says brother Paul the Lord in the sky
1	He	O	-	-
2	says	O	-	-
3	brother	O	-	-
4	Paul	B-PER	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Lord	B-PER	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	sky	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Long_Time_Gone-036
# text = They got Junior but they don't have Hank
1	They	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	Junior	B-PER	-	-
4	but	O	-	-
5	they	O	-	-
6	don	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	have	O	-	-
10	Hank	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Drunkard_s_Son-016
# text = That Jesus had been there that day
1	That	O	-	-
2	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
3	had	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	there	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	day	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Detroit_City-007
# text = I wanna go home, I wanna go home, oh, how I wanna go home
1	I	O	-	-
2	wanna	O	-	-
3	go	O	-	-
4	home	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	wanna	O	-	-
8	go	O	-	-
9	home	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	oh	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	how	O	-	-
14	I	O	-	-
15	wanna	O	-	-
16	go	O	-	-
17	home	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_One_s_On_The_Way-002
# text = And Jackie's seen in a discotheque doing a brand new dance
1	And	O	-	-
2	Jackie	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	seen	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	discotheque	O	-	-
9	doing	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	brand	O	-	-
12	new	O	-	-
13	dance	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Frosty_the_Snowman
# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Frosty_the_Snowman-001
# text = Frosty the snowman was a jolly happy soul
1	Frosty	B-PER	-	-
2	the	0	-	-
3	snowman	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	jolly	O	-	-
7	happy	O	-	-
8	soul	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-024
# text = Larimore, Atmore, Haverstraw, Chatanika, Chaska, Nebraska, Alaska, Opelika
1	Larimore	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Atmore	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Haverstraw	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Chatanika	B-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Chaska	B-LOC	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Nebraska	B-LOC	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Alaska	B-LOC	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Opelika	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Ballad_Of_Hank_Williams-047
# text = Don, you know, you used to work for me one time
1	Don	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	used	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	work	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	one	O	-	-
13	time	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Mother_Was_A_Lady_If_Brother_Jack_Were_Here_-022
# text = And you wouldn't dare insult me, sir, if Jack were only here
1	And	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	wouldn	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	dare	O	-	-
7	insult	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	sir	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	if	O	-	-
13	Jack	B-PER	-	-
14	were	O	-	-
15	only	O	-	-
16	here	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Ballad_Of_Hank_Williams-005
# text = And we met this promoter in the town of New Orleans
1	And	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	met	O	-	-
4	this	O	-	-
5	promoter	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	town	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	New	B-LOC	-	-
11	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__A_Country_Boy_Can_Survive-021
# text = I had a good friend in New York City
1	I	O	-	-
2	had	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	good	O	-	-
5	friend	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	New	B-LOC	-	-
8	York	I-LOC	-	-
9	City	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Casey_s_Last_Ride-007
# text = But Casey minds the arrows and ignores the fatal echoes
1	But	O	-	-
2	Casey	B-PER	-	-
3	minds	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	arrows	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	ignores	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	fatal	O	-	-
10	echoes	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Never_Been_to_Spain-008
# text = Well, I've never been to England
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ve	O	-	-
6	never	O	-	-
7	been	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	England	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Gator-021
# text = That sheriff he'd soon mess around with the devil
1	That	O	-	-
2	sheriff	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	soon	O	-	-
7	mess	O	-	-
8	around	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	devil	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-048
# text = And stuff you in the trunk, Earl
1	And	O	-	-
2	stuff	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	trunk	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Earl	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_Old_Salty_Dog_Blues-009
# text = Pulled the trigger and they said go shot fell over in Mexico
1	Pulled	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	trigger	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	they	O	-	-
6	said	O	-	-
7	go	O	-	-
8	shot	O	-	-
9	fell	O	-	-
10	over	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	Mexico	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Engine_Engine_9-017
# text = Songwriter:  Roger Miller
1	Songwriter	O	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Roger	B-PER	-	-
4	Miller	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_The_Streets_of_Baltimore-008
# text = Is Baltimore at night
1	Is	O	-	-
2	Baltimore	B-LOC	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	night	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Don_t_You_Think_This_Outlaw_Bit_s_Done_Got_out_of_Hand-004
# text = New York sent a posse down like I ain't never seen
1	New	B-LOC	-	-
2	York	I-LOC	-	-
3	sent	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	posse	O	-	-
6	down	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	ain	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	never	O	-	-
13	seen	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_Knoxville_Girl-012
# text = Go down, go down, you Knoxville girl, you can never be my bride
1	Go	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	go	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	Knoxville	B-LOC	-	-
9	girl	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	can	O	-	-
13	never	O	-	-
14	be	O	-	-
15	my	O	-	-
16	bride	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina-012
# text = Corrine, Corrina is it true what they say?
1	Corrine	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Corrina	B-PER	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	true	O	-	-
7	what	O	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	say	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina-021
# text = So long Corrina, this is fare you well
1	So	O	-	-
2	long	O	-	-
3	Corrina	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	this	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	fare	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	well	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Keep_on_the_Firing_Line-006
# text = Keep on the firing line
1	Keep	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	firing	O	-	-
5	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dixie_On_My_Mind-016
# text = Oh, I'd love to haul 'em all down around Spartanburg
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	love	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	haul	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	em	O	-	-
11	all	O	-	-
12	down	O	-	-
13	around	O	-	-
14	Spartanburg	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Getaway_Driver-018
# text = Bonnie and Clyde reminder
1	Bonnie	B-ORG	-	-
2	and	I-ORG	-	-
3	Clyde	I-ORG	-	-
4	reminder	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_I_Ain_t_Living_Long_Like_This-018
# text = Makes Texas Ruby look like Sandra Dee
1	Makes	O	-	-
2	Texas	B-PER	-	-
3	Ruby	I-PER	-	-
4	look	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Sandra	B-PER	-	-
7	Dee	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Why_Me-006
# text = So help me, Jesus, I know what I am
1	So	O	-	-
2	help	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	know	O	-	-
9	what	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	am	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Tequila_Sheila-018
# text = Dor all the damn gold in Juarez
1	Dor	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	damn	O	-	-
5	gold	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Juarez	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Godspeed_Sweet_Dreams_-010
# text = Superman's in pajamas on the couch
1	Superman	B-PER	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	pajamas	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	couch	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Face_on_the_Barroom_Floor-025
# text = "Fill her up, Joe, I want to put some life into my frame
1	"	O	-	-
2	Fill	O	-	-
3	her	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Joe	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	want	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	put	O	-	-
12	some	O	-	-
13	life	O	-	-
14	into	O	-	-
15	my	O	-	-
16	frame	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_Winter_Wonderland_Sleigh_Ride-009
# text = And pretend that he is Parson Brown
1	And	O	-	-
2	pretend	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	he	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	Parson	B-PER	-	-
7	Brown	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Julianna_Calm_Down-005
# text = And Harper, hold on
1	And	O	-	-
2	Harper	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	hold	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Shania_Twain_Party_For_Two
# sent_id = lyrics-Shania_Twain_Party_For_Two-001
# text = Hey Billy
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	Billy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Callin_Baton_Rouge-017
# text = Sweet Baton Rouge
1	Sweet	O	-	-
2	Baton	B-LOC	-	-
3	Rouge	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Stay_A_Little_Longer-002
# text = She lives a way down on Shinbone Alley
1	She	O	-	-
2	lives	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	way	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	Shinbone	B-LOC	-	-
8	Alley	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-012
# text = Did she take your hat, Charming Billy?
1	Did	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	your	O	-	-
5	hat	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Charming	B-PER	-	-
8	Billy	I-PER	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Mom
# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Mom-001
# text = A little baby told God, "Hey, I'm kinda scared
1	A	O	-	-
2	little	O	-	-
3	baby	O	-	-
4	told	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	"	O	-	-
8	Hey	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	m	O	-	-
13	kinda	O	-	-
14	scared	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Virginia_s_Bloody_Soil-024
# text = Virginia's bloody soil"
1	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
2	'	I-LOC	-	-
3	s	I-LOC	-	-
4	bloody	O	-	-
5	soil	O	-	-
6	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Golden_Rocket-012
# text = This Golden Rocket's gonna roll my blues away
1	This	O	-	-
2	Golden	B-ORG	-	-
3	Rocket	I-ORG	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	gonna	O	-	-
7	roll	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	blues	O	-	-
10	away	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_My_Clinch_Mountain_Home-007
# text = Carry me back to old Virginia
1	Carry	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	back	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	old	O	-	-
6	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__The_Conversation-008
# text = Now Hank, if you just got to tell me
1	Now	O	-	-
2	Hank	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	if	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	just	O	-	-
7	got	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	tell	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-013
# text = Kaw-Liga was a lonely Indian, never went nowhere
1	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
2	-	I-PER	-	-
3	Liga	I-PER	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	lonely	O	-	-
7	Indian	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	never	O	-	-
10	went	O	-	-
11	nowhere	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Amarillo_By_Morning-005
# text = Amarillo by morning
1	Amarillo	B-LOC	-	-
2	by	O	-	-
3	morning	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Wabash_Cannonball-014
# text = And long be remembered in the courts of Tennessee
1	And	O	-	-
2	long	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	remembered	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	courts	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_The_Carroll_County_Accident-006
# text = Walter Browning lost his life and for a time
1	Walter	B-PER	-	-
2	Browning	I-PER	-	-
3	lost	O	-	-
4	his	O	-	-
5	life	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	time	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_That_s_What_I_Like_About_The_South-024
# text = Well let's sip that absinthe in New Orleans
1	Well	O	-	-
2	let	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	sip	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	absinthe	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	New	B-LOC	-	-
10	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-023
# text = Can she make a feather bed, Billy Boy, Billy Boy?
1	Can	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	make	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	feather	O	-	-
6	bed	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Billy	B-PER	-	-
9	Boy	I-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Billy	B-PER	-	-
12	Boy	I-PER	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Jackson-008
# text = Yeah, go to Jackson, go comb your hair
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	go	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	Jackson	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	go	O	-	-
8	comb	O	-	-
9	your	O	-	-
10	hair	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Shenandoah
# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Shenandoah-001
# text = Oh, Shenandoah
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Shenandoah	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Amarillo_By_Morning-003
# text = When that sun is high in that Texas sky
1	When	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	sun	O	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	high	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
9	sky	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Blue_Yodel_T_For_Texas_-009
# text = I'm gonna shoot poor Thelma just to see her jump and fall
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	gonna	O	-	-
5	shoot	O	-	-
6	poor	O	-	-
7	Thelma	B-PER	-	-
8	just	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	see	O	-	-
11	her	O	-	-
12	jump	O	-	-
13	and	O	-	-
14	fall	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gram_Parsons_The_New_Soft_Shoe-004
# text = And both kept Cord in line
1	And	O	-	-
2	both	O	-	-
3	kept	O	-	-
4	Cord	B-PER	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Pancho_and_Lefty-009
# text = Pancho was a bandit boy
1	Pancho	B-PER	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	bandit	O	-	-
5	boy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__The_Conversation-003
# text = Well just break out a bottle, Hoss
1	Well	O	-	-
2	just	O	-	-
3	break	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	bottle	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Hoss	0	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_My_Tennessee_Mountain_Home-005
# text = In my Tennessee mountain home
1	In	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-
4	mountain	O	-	-
5	home	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_City_of_New_Orleans-002
# text = Illinois Central, Monday morning rail
1	Illinois	B-ORG	-	-
2	Central	I-ORG	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Monday	O	-	-
5	morning	O	-	-
6	rail	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Goober_Peas-015
# text = The Georgia Militia, eating goober peas!
1	The	O	-	-
2	Georgia	B-ORG	-	-
3	Militia	I-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	eating	O	-	-
6	goober	O	-	-
7	peas	O	-	-
8	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-015
# text = Bangor, Baltimore, Salvador, Amarillo, Tocopilla, Barranquilla, and Padilla, I'm a killer
1	Bangor	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Baltimore	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Salvador	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Amarillo	B-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Tocopilla	B-LOC	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Barranquilla	B-LOC	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	and	O	-	-
14	Padilla	B-LOC	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	I	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-
18	m	O	-	-
19	a	O	-	-
20	killer	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Folsom_Prison_Blues-015
# text = Far from Folsom prison, that's where I want to stay
1	Far	O	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	Folsom	B-LOC	-	-
4	prison	I-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	where	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	want	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	stay	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-014
# text = Molly's a-beatin' old Tenbrooks, clear out of sight
1	Molly	B-PER	-	-
2	'	0	-	-
3	s	0	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	beatin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	old	O	-	-
9	Tenbrooks	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	clear	O	-	-
12	out	O	-	-
13	of	O	-	-
14	sight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Hank_Western-003
# text = I had me a country band down on the Georgia line
1	I	O	-	-
2	had	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	country	O	-	-
6	band	O	-	-
7	down	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-
11	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Big_In_Vegas-008
# text = I had to make it big, in Vegas
1	I	O	-	-
2	had	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	make	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	big	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Vegas	B-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__I_ve_Got_Rights
# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__I_ve_Got_Rights-001
# text = I went down to the Mary Carter paint store
1	I	O	-	-
2	went	O	-	-
3	down	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Mary	B-LOC	-	-
7	Carter	I-LOC	-	-
8	paint	I-LOC	-	-
9	store	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Back_To_God-019
# text = Back to God
1	Back	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Little_Green_Apples-012
# text = And there's no such thing as Dr. Seuss, or Disney Land
1	And	O	-	-
2	there	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	no	O	-	-
6	such	O	-	-
7	thing	O	-	-
8	as	O	-	-
9	Dr	B-PER	-	-
10	.	I-PER	-	-
11	Seuss	I-PER	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	or	O	-	-
14	Disney	B-LOC	-	-
15	Land	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_It_s_All_Going_to_Pot-036
# text = Merle, it's all goin' to pot
1	Merle	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	goin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	pot	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_The_Lily_of_the_Valley-013
# text = Through Jesus I shall safely reach that goal
1	Through	O	-	-
2	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	shall	O	-	-
5	safely	O	-	-
6	reach	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	goal	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gram_Parsons_Kiss_the_Children-017
# text = Is like the road sign pointing straight to satan's cage
1	Is	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	road	O	-	-
5	sign	O	-	-
6	pointing	O	-	-
7	straight	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	satan	B-PER	-	-
10	'	I-PER	-	-
11	s	I-PER	-	-
12	cage	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_West_Bound_and_Down-009
# text = Ol' Smokey's got them ears on, he's hot on your trail
1	Ol	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	Smokey	B-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	them	O	-	-
8	ears	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	he	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	hot	O	-	-
15	on	O	-	-
16	your	O	-	-
17	trail	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_The_Church_in_the_Wildwood-016
# text = CHORUS (x2)
1	CHORUS	O	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	x2	O	-	-
4	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Hello_Darlin_-016
# text = Come back, Darlin', I'll be waitin' for you
1	Come	O	-	-
2	back	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Darlin	0	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	ll	O	-	-
10	be	O	-	-
11	waitin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	for	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-009
# text = Poor ol' Kaw-Liga, you ain't never got a kiss
1	Poor	O	-	-
2	ol	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
5	-	I-PER	-	-
6	Liga	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	ain	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	never	O	-	-
13	got	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	kiss	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Whiskey_Trip-013
# text = Whiskey, you're a friend of mine
1	Whiskey	0	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	re	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	friend	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	mine	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_In_The_Jailhouse_Now-021
# text = Met a girl named Susie
1	Met	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	girl	O	-	-
4	named	O	-	-
5	Susie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_Father_s_Table_Grace-004
# text = But when he's talking to the Lord, even a little child can understand
1	But	O	-	-
2	when	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	talking	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Lord	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	even	O	-	-
12	a	O	-	-
13	little	O	-	-
14	child	O	-	-
15	can	O	-	-
16	understand	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Can_t_You_See-006
# text = What that woman's been doin' to me
1	What	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	woman	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	been	O	-	-
7	doin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_The_Carroll_County_Accident-024
# text = The truth about the Carroll County accident
1	The	O	-	-
2	truth	O	-	-
3	about	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Carroll	B-LOC	-	-
6	County	I-LOC	-	-
7	accident	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__All_My_Rowdy_Friends_Have_Settled_Down_-011
# text = And old George Jones, I'm glad to see, is finally getting straight
1	And	O	-	-
2	old	O	-	-
3	George	B-PER	-	-
4	Jones	I-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	glad	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	see	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	is	O	-	-
14	finally	O	-	-
15	getting	O	-	-
16	straight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__A_Country_Boy_Can_Survive-018
# text = We came from the West Virginia coal mines
1	We	O	-	-
2	came	O	-	-
3	from	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	West	B-LOC	-	-
6	Virginia	I-LOC	-	-
7	coal	I-LOC	-	-
8	mines	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gram_Parsons_The_New_Soft_Shoe-003
# text = Mister Walker held the dough
1	Mister	O	-	-
2	Walker	B-PER	-	-
3	held	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	dough	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Pretty_Good-024
# text = I heard Allah and Buddha
1	I	O	-	-
2	heard	O	-	-
3	Allah	B-PER	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Buddha	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_Satan_Is_Real-035
# text = Satan is real too
1	Satan	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	real	O	-	-
4	too	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kenny_Rogers_Coward_Of_The_County-032
# text = He said, "This one's for Becky" as he watched the last one fall
1	He	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	This	O	-	-
6	one	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	for	O	-	-
10	Becky	B-PER	-	-
11	"	O	-	-
12	as	O	-	-
13	he	O	-	-
14	watched	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	last	O	-	-
17	one	O	-	-
18	fall	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Drive_For_Daddy_Gene_-024
# text = Down a dirt strip where we'd dump trash off of Thigpen Road
1	Down	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	dirt	O	-	-
4	strip	O	-	-
5	where	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	d	O	-	-
9	dump	O	-	-
10	trash	O	-	-
11	off	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	Thigpen	B-LOC	-	-
14	Road	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eddy_Arnold_Green_Green_Grass_of_Home-003
# text = Down the road I look and there runs Mary hair of gold and lips like cherries
1	Down	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	road	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	look	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	there	O	-	-
8	runs	O	-	-
9	Mary	B-PER	-	-
10	hair	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	gold	O	-	-
13	and	O	-	-
14	lips	O	-	-
15	like	O	-	-
16	cherries	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_City_of_New_Orleans-005
# text = All along the southbound odyssey, the train pulls out of Kankakee
1	All	O	-	-
2	along	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	southbound	O	-	-
5	odyssey	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	train	O	-	-
9	pulls	O	-	-
10	out	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	Kankakee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Ben_Dewberry_s_Final_Run-006
# text = Ben Dewberry said before he died
1	Ben	B-PER	-	-
2	Dewberry	I-PER	-	-
3	said	O	-	-
4	before	O	-	-
5	he	O	-	-
6	died	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_When_You_re_Hot_You_re_Hot
# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_When_You_re_Hot_You_re_Hot-001
# text = Well, now me and Homer Jones and Big John Talley
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	now	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	Homer	B-PER	-	-
7	Jones	I-PER	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	Big	B-PER	-	-
10	John	I-PER	-	-
11	Talley	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Seven_Spanish_Angels-028
# text = Come on Willie, help me with this thing
1	Come	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	Willie	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	help	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	this	O	-	-
9	thing	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_Daniel_Prayed-004
# text = Oh, Daniel prayed every morning, noon, and night
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Daniel	B-PER	-	-
4	prayed	O	-	-
5	every	O	-	-
6	morning	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	noon	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	night	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Ballad_Of_Hank_Williams-038
# text = So he fired your ass and he fired Jerry Rivers
1	So	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	fired	O	-	-
4	your	O	-	-
5	ass	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	he	O	-	-
8	fired	O	-	-
9	Jerry	B-PER	-	-
10	Rivers	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_The_Carroll_County_Accident-004
# text = What we all call the Carroll County accident
1	What	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	all	O	-	-
4	call	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Carroll	B-LOC	-	-
7	County	I-LOC	-	-
8	accident	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dixie_On_My_Mind-024
# text = Oh, and I'm stuck up here and got Dixie on my mind
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	stuck	O	-	-
8	up	O	-	-
9	here	O	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	got	O	-	-
12	Dixie	B-LOC	-	-
13	on	O	-	-
14	my	O	-	-
15	mind	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_Lorene-007
# text = Lorene, you seem to be near me
1	Lorene	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	seem	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	near	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_Drunkard_s_Doom-026
# text = To ring with Christ an endless day
1	To	O	-	-
2	ring	O	-	-
3	with	O	-	-
4	Christ	B-PER	-	-
5	an	O	-	-
6	endless	O	-	-
7	day	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Patsy_Cline_Dear_God-009
# text = Dear God
1	Dear	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_The_Yellow_Rose_Of_Texas-008
# text = But the Yellow Rose of Texas is the only girl for me
1	But	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Yellow	O	-	-
4	Rose	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
7	is	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	only	O	-	-
10	girl	O	-	-
11	for	O	-	-
12	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Bonnie_Blue_Flag-031
# text = Davis, our loved president
1	Davis	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	our	O	-	-
4	loved	O	-	-
5	president	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Away_Out_On_The_Mountain-002
# text = Kiss Susie Jane goodbye at the fountain
1	Kiss	O	-	-
2	Susie	B-PER	-	-
3	Jane	I-PER	-	-
4	goodbye	O	-	-
5	at	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	fountain	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Uncle_Pen-014
# text = When Uncle Pen was called away
1	When	O	-	-
2	Uncle	B-PER	-	-
3	Pen	I-PER	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	called	O	-	-
6	away	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga
# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-001
# text = Kaw-Liga was a wooden Indian standin' over by the door
1	Kaw	B-LOC	-	-
2	-	I-LOC	-	-
3	Liga	I-LOC	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	wooden	O	-	-
7	Indian	O	-	-
8	standin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	over	O	-	-
11	by	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	door	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina-009
# text = Corrine, Corrina be a pal of mine
1	Corrine	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Corrina	B-PER	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	pal	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	mine	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Fancy-072
# text = Oh, here's your one chance, Fancy, don't let me down
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	here	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	one	O	-	-
8	chance	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Fancy	B-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	don	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	t	O	-	-
15	let	O	-	-
16	me	O	-	-
17	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Miller_s_Cave-008
# text = The meanest man in Waycross Georgia
1	The	O	-	-
2	meanest	O	-	-
3	man	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	Waycross	B-LOC	-	-
6	Georgia	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Marie_Laveau-017
# text = He was looking around for Marie Laveau
1	He	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	looking	O	-	-
4	around	O	-	-
5	for	O	-	-
6	Marie	B-PER	-	-
7	Laveau	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__All_My_Rowdy_Friends_Are_Coming_Over_Tonight-012
# text = It's a long, long way from here to Hollywood
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	long	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	long	O	-	-
8	way	O	-	-
9	from	O	-	-
10	here	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Paul_s_Ministry-003
# text = Go to Damascus the way that is straight
1	Go	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	Damascus	B-LOC	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	way	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	is	O	-	-
8	straight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__All_My_Rowdy_Friends_Have_Settled_Down_-020
# text = And Johnny Cash don't act like he did back in '68
1	And	O	-	-
2	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
3	Cash	I-PER	-	-
4	don	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	act	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	he	O	-	-
10	did	O	-	-
11	back	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	68	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Thirty_Nine_and_Holding-018
# text = He should have turned loose long ago
1	He	O	-	-
2	should	O	-	-
3	have	O	-	-
4	turned	O	-	-
5	loose	O	-	-
6	long	O	-	-
7	ago	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_Walking_The_Floor_Over_You-009
# text = Aw, pick it out, Smitty!
1	Aw	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	pick	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Smitty	B-PER	-	-
8	!	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_Paul_and_Silas
# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_Paul_and_Silas-001
# text = Paul and Silas bound in jail (All night long)
1	Paul	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Silas	B-PER	-	-
4	bound	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	jail	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	All	O	-	-
9	night	O	-	-
10	long	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Nashville_Is_A_Groovy_Little_Town-023
# text = What else you got? Yes, nashville is a groovy little town
1	What	O	-	-
2	else	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	Yes	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	nashville	B-LOC	-	-
9	is	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	groovy	O	-	-
12	little	O	-	-
13	town	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_All_My_Ex_s_Live_In_Texas-011
# text = And Dimples, who now lives in Temple's
1	And	O	-	-
2	Dimples	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	who	O	-	-
5	now	O	-	-
6	lives	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Temple	B-LOC	-	-
9	'	I-LOC	-	-
10	s	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_Won_t_Back_Down-009
# text = Hey, I will stand my ground, and I won't back down
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	will	O	-	-
5	stand	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	ground	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	won	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	t	O	-	-
14	back	O	-	-
15	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Army_of_the_Free-019
# text = Add Morell to the list of names and we must all agree
1	Add	O	-	-
2	Morell	B-PER	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	list	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	names	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	must	O	-	-
11	all	O	-	-
12	agree	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Long_Time_Gone-006
# text = M' Sisters a nurse at the old folks home
1	M	0	-	-
2	'	0	-	-
3	Sisters	0	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	nurse	O	-	-
6	at	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	old	O	-	-
9	folks	O	-	-
10	home	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Frosty_the_Snowman-019
# text = Frosty the snowman knew
1	Frosty	B-PER	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	snowman	O	-	-
4	knew	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_I_Dreamed_I_Searched_Heaven_for_You-014
# text = That flows through the city of God
1	That	O	-	-
2	flows	O	-	-
3	through	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	city	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	God	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_Jolene-024
# text = Jolene, Jolene
1	Jolene	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Jolene	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kenny_Rogers_Coward_Of_The_County-014
# text = There's someone for everyone, and Tommy's love was Becky
1	There	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	someone	O	-	-
5	for	O	-	-
6	everyone	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	Tommy	B-PER	-	-
10	'	I-PER	-	-
11	s	I-PER	-	-
12	love	O	-	-
13	was	O	-	-
14	Becky	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Drive_For_Daddy_Gene_-003
# text = Secondhand from a dealer in Atlanta
1	Secondhand	O	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	dealer	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Atlanta	B-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_I_m_a_Ramblin_Man
# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_I_m_a_Ramblin_Man-001
# text = I've been down to Mississippi
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	Mississippi	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-036
# text = And is she very tall, Charming Billy?
1	And	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	she	O	-	-
4	very	O	-	-
5	tall	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Charming	B-PER	-	-
8	Billy	I-PER	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__A_Country_Boy_Can_Survive-033
# text = We're from north California and south Alabam'
1	We	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	north	O	-	-
6	California	B-LOC	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	south	O	-	-
9	Alabam	B-LOC	-	-
10	'	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Kaw_Liga-006
# text = Poor ol' Kaw-Liga, never got a kiss
1	Poor	O	-	-
2	ol	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
5	-	I-PER	-	-
6	Liga	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	never	O	-	-
9	got	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	kiss	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Homecoming-037
# text = We worked in San Antone last night
1	We	O	-	-
2	worked	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	San	B-LOC	-	-
5	Antone	I-LOC	-	-
6	last	O	-	-
7	night	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Guitar_Man-013
# text = So I bummed me a ride down to Macon, Georgia
1	So	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	bummed	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	ride	O	-	-
7	down	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Macon	B-LOC	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_The_Jogger-021
# text = But it's just nine miles to Forkers Leap
1	But	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	just	O	-	-
6	nine	O	-	-
7	miles	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Forkers	B-LOC	-	-
10	Leap	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_It_All_Comes_Out_in_the_Wash-008
# text = In a truck at the 7-Eleven, don't sweat it
1	In	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	truck	O	-	-
4	at	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	7	B-ORG	-	-
7	-	I-ORG	-	-
8	Eleven	I-ORG	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	don	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	sweat	O	-	-
14	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Kansas_City_Star-016
# text = No thanks Omaha, thanks a lot
1	No	O	-	-
2	thanks	O	-	-
3	Omaha	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	thanks	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	lot	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_One_of_Everything_You_Got-003
# text = He wrote old Santa Claus a letter today
1	He	O	-	-
2	wrote	O	-	-
3	old	O	-	-
4	Santa	B-PER	-	-
5	Claus	I-PER	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	letter	O	-	-
8	today	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-023
# text = I bet feelin' good was easy, Lord, when Bobby sang the blues
1	I	O	-	-
2	bet	O	-	-
3	feelin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	good	O	-	-
6	was	O	-	-
7	easy	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Lord	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	when	O	-	-
12	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
13	sang	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	blues	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Luckenbach_Texas_Back_to_the_Basics_of_Love_-026
# text = Out in Luckenbach, Texas there ain't nobody feelin' no pain
1	Out	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	Luckenbach	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
6	there	O	-	-
7	ain	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	t	O	-	-
10	nobody	O	-	-
11	feelin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	no	O	-	-
14	pain	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Are_the_Good_Times_Really_Over_I_Wish_a_Buck_Was_Still_Silver_-017
# text = And it was back before Nixon
1	And	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	was	O	-	-
4	back	O	-	-
5	before	O	-	-
6	Nixon	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Spanish_Pipedream-032
# text = They all found Jesus on their own
1	They	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	found	O	-	-
4	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	their	O	-	-
7	own	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Can_t_Get_Enough_Of_Texas-005
# text = And when that Texas moon gives out and I hear a sweet guitar
1	And	O	-	-
2	when	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
5	moon	O	-	-
6	gives	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	hear	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	sweet	O	-	-
13	guitar	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_One_Piece_at_a_Time-064
# text = Uh, what model is it?
1	Uh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	what	O	-	-
4	model	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_You_re_The_Reason_Our_Kids_Are_Ugly-016
# text = Well, Loretta, look at yourself
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Loretta	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	look	O	-	-
6	at	O	-	-
7	yourself	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_In_The_Jailhouse_Now
# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_In_The_Jailhouse_Now-001
# text = I had a friend named Ramblin' Bob
1	I	O	-	-
2	had	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	friend	O	-	-
5	named	O	-	-
6	Ramblin	B-PER	-	-
7	'	I-PER	-	-
8	Bob	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Never_Been_to_Spain-016
# text = But I've been to Oklahoma
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	ve	O	-	-
5	been	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	Oklahoma	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Lonesome_Pine_Special-010
# text = Take me back to Texas
1	Take	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	back	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	Texas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tammy_Wynette_My_Elusive_Dreams-002
# text = T: I followed you to Utah
1	T	O	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	followed	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	Utah	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-017
# text = Took her oh so far away and ol' Kaw-Liga stayed
1	Took	O	-	-
2	her	O	-	-
3	oh	O	-	-
4	so	O	-	-
5	far	O	-	-
6	away	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	ol	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
11	-	I-PER	-	-
12	Liga	I-PER	-	-
13	stayed	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_What_Would_You_Do_If_Jesus_Came_to_Your_House_-002
# text = If Jesus came to your house to spend a day or two
1	If	O	-	-
2	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
3	came	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	house	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	spend	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	day	O	-	-
11	or	O	-	-
12	two	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Uptown_Poker_Club-030
# text = So Bill rose up and he looked around the room and with a sigh
1	So	O	-	-
2	Bill	B-PER	-	-
3	rose	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	looked	O	-	-
8	around	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	room	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	with	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	sigh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Face_on_the_Barroom_Floor-007
# text = "Here, Toby, seek him, if your stomach's equal to the work!"
1	"	O	-	-
2	Here	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Toby	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	seek	O	-	-
7	him	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	if	O	-	-
10	your	O	-	-
11	stomach	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	equal	O	-	-
15	to	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	work	O	-	-
18	!	O	-	-
19	"	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Folsom_Prison_Blues_Live_at_Folsom_State_Prison_Folsom_CA_January_1968_
# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Folsom_Prison_Blues_Live_at_Folsom_State_Prison_Folsom_CA_January_1968_-001
# text = "Hello, I'm Johnny Cash."
1	"	O	-	-
2	Hello	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
8	Cash	I-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Cherokee_Maiden-009
# text = Someday I'll make a trip back to that Cherokee strip
1	Someday	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	ll	O	-	-
5	make	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	trip	O	-	-
8	back	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	that	O	-	-
11	Cherokee	B-LOC	-	-
12	strip	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_The_Ballad_of_Jed_Clampett-005
# text = (Oil, that is. Black gold, Texas tea)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Oil	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	Black	O	-	-
8	gold	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
11	tea	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_King_Is_Gone_So_Are_You_-007
# text = I pulled the head off Elvis
1	I	O	-	-
2	pulled	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	head	O	-	-
5	off	O	-	-
6	Elvis	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kenny_Rogers_Coward_Of_The_County-034
# text = I promised you, Dad, not to do the things you've done
1	I	O	-	-
2	promised	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Dad	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	not	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	do	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	things	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	ve	O	-	-
15	done	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Pancho_And_Lefty-032
# text = The desert's quiet, Cleveland's cold
1	The	O	-	-
2	desert	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	quiet	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Cleveland	B-LOC	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	cold	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Illegal_Smile-017
# text = Well, I went to court and the judge's name was Hoffman
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	went	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	court	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	judge	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	s	O	-	-
12	name	O	-	-
13	was	O	-	-
14	Hoffman	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Summertime_Blues-013
# text = Well I called my congressman and he said quote
1	Well	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	called	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	congressman	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	he	O	-	-
8	said	O	-	-
9	quote	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_It_s_All_Going_to_Pot-022
# text = And we’re all gonna miss it a lot
1	And	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	’	O	-	-
4	re	O	-	-
5	all	O	-	-
6	gonna	O	-	-
7	miss	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	lot	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Casey_s_Last_Ride-013
# text = Casey leaves the underground and stops inside the Golden Crown
1	Casey	B-PER	-	-
2	leaves	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	underground	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	stops	O	-	-
7	inside	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Golden	B-LOC	-	-
10	Crown	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_Daniel_Prayed-009
# text = The jaws were locked and it made him shout, and God soon got them
1	The	O	-	-
2	jaws	O	-	-
3	were	O	-	-
4	locked	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	made	O	-	-
8	him	O	-	-
9	shout	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	God	B-PER	-	-
13	soon	O	-	-
14	got	O	-	-
15	them	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Picture_on_the_Wall-019
# text = Let me hold that dear old picture on the wall
1	Let	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	hold	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	dear	O	-	-
6	old	O	-	-
7	picture	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	wall	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Strawberry_Farms-009
# text = Bobby had a brother, he got killed in the war
1	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
2	had	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	brother	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	got	O	-	-
8	killed	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	war	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Long_Time_Gone-030
# text = Now, me and Deliah singing every Sunday
1	Now	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Deliah	B-PER	-	-
6	singing	O	-	-
7	every	O	-	-
8	Sunday	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Are_You_Sure_Hank_Done_It_This_Way-009
# text = But I don't think Hank done it this way, no
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	think	O	-	-
7	Hank	B-PER	-	-
8	done	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	this	O	-	-
11	way	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	no	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_The_Martha_White_Theme-011
# text = Martha White self-rising meal
1	Martha	B-PER	-	-
2	White	I-PER	-	-
3	self	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	rising	O	-	-
6	meal	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_Angels_Rejoiced_Last_Night-007
# text = I've never seen my daddy inside the house of God
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	never	O	-	-
5	seen	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	daddy	O	-	-
8	inside	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	house	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Fancy-004
# text = On the outskirts of New Orleans
1	On	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	outskirts	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	New	B-LOC	-	-
6	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Chattahoochee-003
# text = We laid rubber on the Georgia asphalt
1	We	O	-	-
2	laid	O	-	-
3	rubber	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-
7	asphalt	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Country_State_Of_Mind-021
# text = Yodel-ay-ee-oh, del-ay-ee-oh, del-ay
1	Yodel	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	ay	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	ee	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	oh	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	del	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	ay	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	ee	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	oh	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	del	O	-	-
18	-	O	-	-
19	ay	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__All_My_Rowdy_Friends_Have_Settled_Down_-021
# text = And Kris, he is a movie star and he's moved off to L.A..
1	And	O	-	-
2	Kris	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	he	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	movie	O	-	-
8	star	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	he	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	moved	O	-	-
14	off	O	-	-
15	to	O	-	-
16	L	B-LOC	-	-
17	.	I-LOC	-	-
18	A	I-LOC	-	-
19	.	I-LOC	-	-
20	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Nobody_s_Child-015
# text = I'd walk the streets of heaven where all the blind can see
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	d	O	-	-
4	walk	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	streets	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	heaven	B-LOC	-	-
9	where	O	-	-
10	all	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	blind	O	-	-
13	can	O	-	-
14	see	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_The_Yellow_Rose_Of_Texas
# sent_id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_The_Yellow_Rose_Of_Texas-001
# text = There's a yellow rose in Texas that I'm gonna see
1	There	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	yellow	O	-	-
6	rose	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	m	O	-	-
13	gonna	O	-	-
14	see	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Country_State_Of_Mind-017
# text = And ain't it great to be livin' in the U.S.A
1	And	O	-	-
2	ain	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	great	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	be	O	-	-
9	livin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	U	B-LOC	-	-
14	.	I-LOC	-	-
15	S	I-LOC	-	-
16	.	I-LOC	-	-
17	A	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Hello_Darlin_-011
# text = Thank you, Darlin', may God bless you and each step you take
1	Thank	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Darlin	0	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	may	O	-	-
8	God	O	-	-
9	bless	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	each	O	-	-
13	step	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	take	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Frosty_the_Snowman-011
# text = O, Frosty the snowman
1	O	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Frosty	B-PER	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	snowman	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-George_Jones_White_Lightning
# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_White_Lightning-001
# text = Well, in North Carolina, way back in the hills
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	North	B-LOC	-	-
5	Carolina	I-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	way	O	-	-
8	back	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	hills	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_Charlie_s_Angel-005
# text = And I'm holding Charlie's Angel tonight
1	And	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	holding	O	-	-
6	Charlie	B-PER	-	-
7	'	I-PER	-	-
8	s	I-PER	-	-
9	Angel	I-PER	-	-
10	tonight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Out_Of_Hand-008
# text = For it to get so out of hand
1	For	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	get	O	-	-
5	so	O	-	-
6	out	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	hand	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Union_Dixie-006
# text = We'll all go down to Dixie, away, away!
1	We	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	go	O	-	-
6	down	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Dixie	B-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	away	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	away	O	-	-
13	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_God_s_Gonna_Cut_You_Down-017
# text = But as sure as God made black and white
1	But	O	-	-
2	as	O	-	-
3	sure	O	-	-
4	as	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	made	O	-	-
7	black	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	white	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charlie_Rich_On_My_Knees_1977_-015
# text = (Janie Fricke)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Janie	B-PER	-	-
3	Fricke	I-PER	-	-
4	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-018
# text = Can she cook and can she spin, Charming Billy?
1	Can	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	cook	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	can	O	-	-
6	she	O	-	-
7	spin	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Charming	B-PER	-	-
10	Billy	I-PER	-	-
11	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Mother_Was_A_Lady_If_Brother_Jack_Were_Here_-012
# text = And you wouldn't dare insult me, sir, if Jack were only here."
1	And	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	wouldn	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	dare	O	-	-
7	insult	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	sir	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	if	O	-	-
13	Jack	B-PER	-	-
14	were	O	-	-
15	only	O	-	-
16	here	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Little_Green_Apples-010
# text = God didn't make the little green apples
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	didn	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	make	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	little	O	-	-
8	green	O	-	-
9	apples	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Will_Your_Lawyer_Talk_to_God-005
# text = Will your lawyer talk to God and plead your case up on high
1	Will	O	-	-
2	your	O	-	-
3	lawyer	O	-	-
4	talk	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	God	B-PER	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	plead	O	-	-
9	your	O	-	-
10	case	O	-	-
11	up	O	-	-
12	on	O	-	-
13	high	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Luckenbach_Texas_Back_to_the_Basics_of_Love_-006
# text = Let's go to Luckenbach, Texas
1	Let	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	go	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Luckenbach	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Texas	B-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Nashville_Is_A_Groovy_Little_Town
# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Nashville_Is_A_Groovy_Little_Town-001
# text = My plane set down in nashville at a quarter after 2
1	My	O	-	-
2	plane	O	-	-
3	set	O	-	-
4	down	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	nashville	B-LOC	-	-
7	at	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	quarter	O	-	-
10	after	O	-	-
11	2	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_Father_s_Table_Grace-024
# text = So we all be together in Heaven, in Jesus' name, Amen
1	So	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	all	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	together	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Heaven	B-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
11	'	I-PER	-	-
12	name	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Amen	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_I_Need_The_Prayers-004
# text = And live for Jesus every day
1	And	O	-	-
2	live	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
5	every	O	-	-
6	day	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_Paul_and_Silas-005
# text = Paul and Silas prayed to God (All night long)
1	Paul	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Silas	B-PER	-	-
4	prayed	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	God	B-PER	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	All	O	-	-
9	night	O	-	-
10	long	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Tomorrow_Night_In_Baltimore-019
# text = God' if I have to crawl, I'm gonna be there tomorrow night in Baltimore
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	'	0	-	-
3	if	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	have	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	crawl	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	gonna	O	-	-
13	be	O	-	-
14	there	O	-	-
15	tomorrow	O	-	-
16	night	O	-	-
17	in	O	-	-
18	Baltimore	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Shania_Twain_No_One_Needs_To_Know-014
# text = A little Benji we call Leroy
1	A	O	-	-
2	little	O	-	-
3	Benji	B-PER	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	call	O	-	-
6	Leroy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Lord_Lead_Me_On-013
# text = I asked the Lord, (I asked the Lord)
1	I	O	-	-
2	asked	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Lord	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	asked	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Lord	B-PER	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Ain_t_No_Grave-033
# text = 'Cuz the bride of Christ is looking like the Bride of Frankenstein
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cuz	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	bride	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	Christ	B-PER	-	-
7	is	O	-	-
8	looking	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	Bride	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	Frankenstein	B-PER	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Hello_Darlin_
# sent_id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Hello_Darlin_-001
# text = Hello Darlin', nice to see you, it's been a long time
1	Hello	O	-	-
2	Darlin	0	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	nice	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	see	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	been	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	long	O	-	-
16	time	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_King_Is_Gone_So_Are_You_-016
# text = And Fred said, "Old Fashioned girls are fun."
1	And	O	-	-
2	Fred	B-PER	-	-
3	said	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	"	O	-	-
6	Old	O	-	-
7	Fashioned	O	-	-
8	girls	O	-	-
9	are	O	-	-
10	fun	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-
12	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Drinkin_and_Dreamin_-012
# text = I'll never see Texas, L.A., or Old Mexico
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	never	O	-	-
5	see	O	-	-
6	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	L	B-LOC	-	-
9	.	I-LOC	-	-
10	A	I-LOC	-	-
11	.	I-LOC	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	or	O	-	-
14	Old	B-LOC	-	-
15	Mexico	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Automatic-007
# text = If we drove all the way to Dallas just to buy an Easter dress
1	If	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	drove	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	way	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Dallas	B-LOC	-	-
9	just	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	buy	O	-	-
12	an	O	-	-
13	Easter	O	-	-
14	dress	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_Ruby_Don_t_Take_Your_Love_to_Town-008
# text = Oh but Ruby I still need some company
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	but	O	-	-
3	Ruby	B-PER	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	still	O	-	-
6	need	O	-	-
7	some	O	-	-
8	company	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_City_of_New_Orleans-017
# text = And the sons of Pullman porters and the sons of engineers
1	And	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	sons	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	Pullman	B-ORG	-	-
6	porters	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	sons	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	engineers	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__O_D_d_In_Denver-010
# text = Doc said, "Son, you can't do anymore of that cocaine"
1	Doc	B-PER	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	Son	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	can	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	do	O	-	-
12	anymore	O	-	-
13	of	O	-	-
14	that	O	-	-
15	cocaine	O	-	-
16	"	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Legend
# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Legend-001
# text = You heard about the legend of Jesse James
1	You	O	-	-
2	heard	O	-	-
3	about	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	legend	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	Jesse	B-PER	-	-
8	James	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Amos_Moses-013
# text = Alligator bait in the Louisiana Bayou
1	Alligator	O	-	-
2	bait	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Louisiana	B-LOC	-	-
6	Bayou	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Margie_s_At_The_Lincoln_Park_Inn-012
# text = And all of the Margie's at all of the Lincoln Park Inns
1	And	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Margie	B-PER	-	-
6	'	I-PER	-	-
7	s	I-PER	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	all	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Lincoln	B-LOC	-	-
13	Park	I-LOC	-	-
14	Inns	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina-002
# text = Help me Corrina, where you been so long?
1	Help	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	Corrina	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	where	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	been	O	-	-
8	so	O	-	-
9	long	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Mama_s_Broken_Heart-015
# text = Like a Kennedy when Camelot went down in flames
1	Like	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	Kennedy	B-PER	-	-
4	when	O	-	-
5	Camelot	B-LOC	-	-
6	went	O	-	-
7	down	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	flames	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Last_Ride-045
# text = I knew that fever had you, Jack
1	I	O	-	-
2	knew	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	fever	O	-	-
5	had	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Jack	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lefty_Frizzell_Saginaw_Michigan-012
# text = I'll go back home and claim my love in Saginaw, Michigan
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	go	O	-	-
5	back	O	-	-
6	home	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	claim	O	-	-
9	my	O	-	-
10	love	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	Saginaw	B-LOC	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Michigan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Nobody_s_Child-018
# text = Cause I know that it's true that God takes little blind children with him in the sky
1	Cause	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	know	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	true	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	God	B-PER	-	-
11	takes	O	-	-
12	little	O	-	-
13	blind	O	-	-
14	children	O	-	-
15	with	O	-	-
16	him	O	-	-
17	in	O	-	-
18	the	O	-	-
19	sky	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Miller_s_Cave-015
# text = The most wanted man in the state of Georgia
1	The	O	-	-
2	most	O	-	-
3	wanted	O	-	-
4	man	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	state	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_I_m_A_White_Boy-004
# text = Cause daddy’s name wadn’t Willy Woodrow
1	Cause	O	-	-
2	daddy	O	-	-
3	’	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	name	O	-	-
6	wadn	O	-	-
7	’	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	Willy	B-PER	-	-
10	Woodrow	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Ain_t_No_Grave-060
# text = The man who took on the devil and danced with death, never lost
1	The	O	-	-
2	man	O	-	-
3	who	O	-	-
4	took	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	devil	B-PER	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	danced	O	-	-
10	with	O	-	-
11	death	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	never	O	-	-
14	lost	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Walkin_In_The_Sunshine-010
# text = Songwriter:  Roger Miller
1	Songwriter	O	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Roger	B-PER	-	-
4	Miller	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Fancy-071
# text = "Here's your one chance, Fancy, don't let me down
1	"	O	-	-
2	Here	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	one	O	-	-
7	chance	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Fancy	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	don	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	t	O	-	-
14	let	O	-	-
15	me	O	-	-
16	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Engine_Engine_9-006
# text = I know she got on in Baltimore
1	I	O	-	-
2	know	O	-	-
3	she	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Baltimore	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__All_My_Rowdy_Friends_Are_Coming_Over_Tonight-012
# text = It's a long, long way from here to Hollywood
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	long	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	long	O	-	-
8	way	O	-	-
9	from	O	-	-
10	here	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_The_Long_Way_Around-010
# text = I've been a long time gone now
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	long	O	-	-
7	time	O	-	-
8	gone	O	-	-
9	now	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Gaslighter-009
# text = Hollywood welcomed you with open doors
1	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
2	welcomed	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	open	O	-	-
6	doors	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Blue_Danube_Waltz-012
# text = Oh the Danube isn't blue, it's green
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Danube	B-LOC	-	-
4	isn	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	blue	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	s	O	-	-
12	green	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_Angels_Rejoiced_Last_Night-008
# text = For Satan held his hand, down the path of sin he trod
1	For	O	-	-
2	Satan	B-PER	-	-
3	held	O	-	-
4	his	O	-	-
5	hand	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	down	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	path	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	sin	O	-	-
12	he	O	-	-
13	trod	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Big_In_Vegas-014
# text = When I turn 'em on in Vegas
1	When	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	turn	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	em	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Vegas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_The_Conversation-029
# text = How he sure did love Miss Audrey and raisin' hell
1	How	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	sure	O	-	-
4	did	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-
6	Miss	B-PER	-	-
7	Audrey	I-PER	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	raisin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	hell	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina
# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina-001
# text = Corrine Corrina, where you been so long?
1	Corrine	B-PER	-	-
2	Corrina	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	where	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	been	O	-	-
7	so	O	-	-
8	long	O	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Dropkick_Me_Jesus
# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Dropkick_Me_Jesus-001
# text = Dropkick me, Jesus, through the goal posts of life
1	Dropkick	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	through	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	goal	O	-	-
9	posts	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	life	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Pancho_And_Lefty-030
# text = The poets tell how Pancho fell
1	The	O	-	-
2	poets	O	-	-
3	tell	O	-	-
4	how	O	-	-
5	Pancho	B-PER	-	-
6	fell	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Shenandoah-006
# text = ’Cross the wide Missouri
1	’	O	-	-
2	Cross	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	wide	O	-	-
5	Missouri	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_My_Little_Georgia_Rose-008
# text = She's my little Georgia rose
1	She	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	little	O	-	-
6	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-
7	rose	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_My_Favorite_Memory-011
# text = Like the winter we spent on Lake Shasta
1	Like	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	winter	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	spent	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	Lake	B-LOC	-	-
8	Shasta	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_I_Need_The_Prayers-007
# text = And intercede with God for me
1	And	O	-	-
2	intercede	O	-	-
3	with	O	-	-
4	God	B-PER	-	-
5	for	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Mom-007
# text = And God said, "Oh, child, of course I do
1	And	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	said	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	"	O	-	-
6	Oh	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	child	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	course	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	do	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Time_Out_For_Jesus-011
# text = But don't forget about Jesus
1	But	O	-	-
2	don	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	forget	O	-	-
6	about	O	-	-
7	Jesus	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_The_Yellow_Rose_Of_Texas-009
# text = Where the Rio Grande is flowing and the skies are bright
1	Where	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Rio	B-LOC	-	-
4	Grande	I-LOC	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	flowing	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	skies	O	-	-
10	are	O	-	-
11	bright	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_The_Winner-003
# text = But everybody they said watch out hey that's the Tiger Man McCool
1	But	O	-	-
2	everybody	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	said	O	-	-
5	watch	O	-	-
6	out	O	-	-
7	hey	O	-	-
8	that	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Tiger	B-PER	-	-
13	Man	I-PER	-	-
14	McCool	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Guitar_Man-003
# text = By sundown I'd left Kingston
1	By	O	-	-
2	sundown	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	left	O	-	-
7	Kingston	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Squid_Jiggin_Ground-012
# text = There's old Billy Cave and there's young Raymond Brown;
1	There	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	old	O	-	-
5	Billy	B-PER	-	-
6	Cave	I-PER	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	there	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	young	O	-	-
12	Raymond	B-PER	-	-
13	Brown	I-PER	-	-
14	;	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Bonnie_Blue_Flag-029
# text = Texas and fair Louisiana
1	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	fair	O	-	-
4	Louisiana	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Born_To_Boogie-016
# text = And we moved it on over to MGM
1	And	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	moved	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	over	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	MGM	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_My_Favorite_Memory-013
# text = And I remember that London vacation
1	And	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	remember	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	London	B-LOC	-	-
6	vacation	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Highway_Vagabond-017
# text = Roaming town to town like Willie did when he was a kid, on the road again
1	Roaming	O	-	-
2	town	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	town	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Willie	B-PER	-	-
7	did	O	-	-
8	when	O	-	-
9	he	O	-	-
10	was	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	kid	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	on	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	road	O	-	-
17	again	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Squid_Jiggin_Ground-013
# text = There's Rip, Red and Gory out here in the dory
1	There	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	Rip	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Red	B-PER	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	Gory	B-PER	-	-
9	out	O	-	-
10	here	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	dory	0	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kenny_Rogers_Ruby_Don_t_Take_Your_Love_To_Town-004
# text = Oh, Ruby
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Ruby	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Amarillo_By_Morning-014
# text = Amarillo is where I'll be
1	Amarillo	B-LOC	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	where	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	ll	O	-	-
7	be	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dinosaur-007
# text = And we don't all get into Donna Summer
1	And	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	get	O	-	-
8	into	O	-	-
9	Donna	B-PER	-	-
10	Summer	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Give_It_Away-006
# text = That night in Frisco Bay
1	That	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	Frisco	B-LOC	-	-
5	Bay	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Never_Been_to_Spain-019
# text = In Oklahoma or Arizona
1	In	O	-	-
2	Oklahoma	B-LOC	-	-
3	or	O	-	-
4	Arizona	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-038
# text = Are her eyes very bright, Billy Boy, Billy Boy?
1	Are	O	-	-
2	her	O	-	-
3	eyes	O	-	-
4	very	O	-	-
5	bright	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Billy	B-PER	-	-
8	Boy	I-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Billy	B-PER	-	-
11	Boy	I-PER	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga
# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-001
# text = Kaw-Liga was a wooden Indian standin' over by the door
1	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
2	-	I-PER	-	-
3	Liga	I-PER	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	wooden	O	-	-
7	Indian	O	-	-
8	standin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	over	O	-	-
11	by	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	door	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-017
# text = Can she cook and can she spin, Billy Boy, Billy Boy?
1	Can	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	cook	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	can	O	-	-
6	she	O	-	-
7	spin	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Billy	B-PER	-	-
10	Boy	I-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Billy	B-PER	-	-
13	Boy	I-PER	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_New_San_Antonio_Rose-005
# text = It was there I found beside the Alamo
1	It	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	there	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	found	O	-	-
6	beside	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	Alamo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Pancho_and_Lefty-030
# text = The poets tell how Pancho fell
1	The	O	-	-
2	poets	O	-	-
3	tell	O	-	-
4	how	O	-	-
5	Pancho	B-PER	-	-
6	fell	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Made_In_Japan-015
# text = That's when I left my heart with the girl made in Japan
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	when	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	left	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	heart	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	girl	O	-	-
12	made	O	-	-
13	in	O	-	-
14	Japan	B-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Golden_Rocket
# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Golden_Rocket-001
# text = From old Montana down to Alabam'
1	From	O	-	-
2	old	O	-	-
3	Montana	B-LOC	-	-
4	down	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Alabam	B-LOC	-	-
7	'	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Okie_From_Muskogee-008
# text = Like the hippies out in San Francisco do
1	Like	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	hippies	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	San	B-LOC	-	-
7	Francisco	I-LOC	-	-
8	do	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare__Margie_s_At_The_Lincoln_Park_Inn-004
# text = My wife’s in the kitchen and Margie is at the Lincoln Park Inn
1	My	O	-	-
2	wife	O	-	-
3	’	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	kitchen	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	Margie	B-PER	-	-
10	is	O	-	-
11	at	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	Lincoln	B-LOC	-	-
14	Park	I-LOC	-	-
15	Inn	0	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_Coal_Miner_s_Daughter-016
# text = In the summertime, we didn't have shoes to wear
1	In	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	summertime	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	we	O	-	-
6	didn	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	have	O	-	-
10	shoes	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	wear	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_King_Is_Gone_So_Are_You_-002
# text = That looks like Elvis
1	That	O	-	-
2	looks	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	Elvis	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_Great_Atomic_Power-016
# text = God will surely save his children from that awful awful fate
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	will	O	-	-
3	surely	O	-	-
4	save	O	-	-
5	his	O	-	-
6	children	O	-	-
7	from	O	-	-
8	that	O	-	-
9	awful	O	-	-
10	awful	O	-	-
11	fate	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Casey_s_Last_Ride-024
# text = "Lord," she said, "Casey, it's a shame to be alone"
1	"	O	-	-
2	Lord	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	she	O	-	-
6	said	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	"	O	-	-
9	Casey	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	shame	O	-	-
16	to	O	-	-
17	be	O	-	-
18	alone	O	-	-
19	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-050
# text = Good, let's go for a ride Earl
1	Good	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	let	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	go	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	ride	O	-	-
10	Earl	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_Why_d_You_Come_in_Here_Lookin_Like_That-005
# text = He's drivin' me crazy, who says love is blind?
1	He	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	drivin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	crazy	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	who	O	-	-
10	says	O	-	-
11	love	O	-	-
12	is	O	-	-
13	blind	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Miller_s_Cave-004
# text = I had a girl in Waycross Georgia but she had unfaithful ways
1	I	O	-	-
2	had	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	girl	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Waycross	B-LOC	-	-
7	Georgia	I-LOC	-	-
8	but	O	-	-
9	she	O	-	-
10	had	O	-	-
11	unfaithful	O	-	-
12	ways	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_River_Of_Jordan
# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_River_Of_Jordan-001
# text = To the River Of Jordan our Savior went one day
1	To	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	River	B-LOC	-	-
4	Of	I-LOC	-	-
5	Jordan	I-LOC	-	-
6	our	O	-	-
7	Savior	B-PER	-	-
8	went	O	-	-
9	one	O	-	-
10	day	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Virginia_s_Bloody_Soil-004
# text = It took to down secession on Virginia's bloody soil
1	It	O	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	down	O	-	-
5	secession	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
8	'	O	I-LOC	-
9	s	O	I-LOC	-
10	bloody	O	-	-
11	soil	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dinosaur-016
# text = Then a little old Jim Beam and we'd get right
1	Then	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	little	O	-	-
4	old	O	-	-
5	Jim	B-ORG	-	-
6	Beam	I-ORG	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	we	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	d	O	-	-
11	get	O	-	-
12	right	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_River_Of_Jordan-002
# text = And we read that John The Baptist met Him there
1	And	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	read	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	John	B-PER	-	-
6	The	I-PER	-	-
7	Baptist	I-PER	-	-
8	met	O	-	-
9	Him	O	-	-
10	there	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_Send_Me_Down_to_Tucson-015
# text = The one in Tucson she don’t hide it and when she gets excited
1	The	O	-	-
2	one	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	Tucson	B-LOC	-	-
5	she	O	-	-
6	don	O	-	-
7	’	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	hide	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	when	O	-	-
13	she	O	-	-
14	gets	O	-	-
15	excited	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Big_Daddy-009
# text = Big Daddy's Alabamy bound
1	Big	B-PER	-	-
2	Daddy	I-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	Alabamy	B-LOC	-	-
6	bound	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_Black_Jack_s_Bar-004
# text = And I took in the money in Black Jack's Bar
1	And	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	took	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	money	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Black	B-LOC	-	-
9	Jack	I-LOC	-	-
10	'	I-LOC	-	-
11	s	I-LOC	-	-
12	Bar	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_Country_Christmas-008
# text = Aunt Annie Belle will be here uncle Bill and darn our kids
1	Aunt	O	-	-
2	Annie	B-PER	-	-
3	Belle	I-PER	-	-
4	will	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	here	O	-	-
7	uncle	O	-	-
8	Bill	B-PER	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	darn	O	-	-
11	our	O	-	-
12	kids	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_One_Piece_at_a_Time-058
# text = Uh, yeah, Red Ryder?
1	Uh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Red	B-ORG	-	-
6	Ryder	I-ORG	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Ugly_Woman-014
# text = Hoss I'm gonna go out and find me an ugly woman to love
1	Hoss	0	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	gonna	O	-	-
6	go	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	find	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	an	O	-	-
12	ugly	O	-	-
13	woman	O	-	-
14	to	O	-	-
15	love	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Sylvia_s_Mother-003
# text = "Sylvia's trying to start a new life of her own."
1	"	O	-	-
2	Sylvia	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	trying	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	start	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	new	O	-	-
10	life	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	her	O	-	-
13	own	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-
15	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gram_Parsons_Sin_City-006
# text = But Satan is waiting his turn
1	But	O	-	-
2	Satan	B-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	waiting	O	-	-
5	his	O	-	-
6	turn	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Amos_Moses-029
# text = Well you can sure get lost in the Louisiana Bayou!
1	Well	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	can	O	-	-
4	sure	O	-	-
5	get	O	-	-
6	lost	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Louisiana	B-LOC	-	-
10	Bayou	I-LOC	-	-
11	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Hey_Joe-012
# text = Hey Joe my poor heart is yearning burning just to hold you tightly nighty
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	Joe	B-PER	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	poor	O	-	-
5	heart	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	yearning	O	-	-
8	burning	O	-	-
9	just	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	hold	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	tightly	O	-	-
14	nighty	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__All_My_Rowdy_Friends_Have_Settled_Down_-012
# text = And Waylon's staying home and loving Jessi more these days
1	And	O	-	-
2	Waylon	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	staying	O	-	-
6	home	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	loving	O	-	-
9	Jessi	B-PER	-	-
10	more	O	-	-
11	these	O	-	-
12	days	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Virginia_s_Bloody_Soil-012
# text = Come from the plains o'er hill and dale, ye hardy sons of toil
1	Come	O	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	plains	O	-	-
5	o	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	er	O	-	-
8	hill	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	dale	0	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	ye	O	-	-
13	hardy	O	-	-
14	sons	O	-	-
15	of	O	-	-
16	toil	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_Jolene
# sent_id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_Jolene-001
# text = Jolene, Jolene, Jolene, Jolene
1	Jolene	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Jolene	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Jolene	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Jolene	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Williamson_County-002
# text = Of a Williamson County hotel
1	Of	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	Williamson	B-LOC	-	-
4	County	I-LOC	-	-
5	hotel	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dinosaur-007
# text = And we don't all get into Donna Summer
1	And	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	get	O	-	-
8	into	O	-	-
9	Donna	B-PER	-	-
10	Summer	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Heartbreak_U_S_A_-009
# text = Back home in heartbreak USA
1	Back	O	-	-
2	home	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	heartbreak	O	-	-
5	USA	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_Be_a_Little_Quieter-003
# text = But each night you've come to visit me in mem'ries
1	But	O	-	-
2	each	O	-	-
3	night	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	ve	O	-	-
7	come	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	visit	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	mem	0	-	-
13	'	0	-	-
14	ries	0	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Keeper_of_the_Flame-020
# text = But I swear to God
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	swear	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-006
# text = Blowin' sad while Bobby sang the blues
1	Blowin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	sad	O	-	-
4	while	O	-	-
5	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
6	sang	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	blues	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-020
# text = Men's all a-hollerin'; old Tenbrooks a-flyin'
1	Men	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	hollerin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	;	O	-	-
10	old	O	-	-
11	Tenbrooks	B-PER	-	-
12	a	O	-	-
13	-	O	-	-
14	flyin	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_White_Liar-016
# text = With a red head named Bernice
1	With	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	red	O	-	-
4	head	O	-	-
5	named	O	-	-
6	Bernice	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-025
# text = Schefferville, Jacksonville, Waterville, Costa Rica
1	Schefferville	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Jacksonville	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Waterville	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Costa	B-LOC	-	-
8	Rica	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Hank_Western-021
# text = Was sung in the big Georgia jail
1	Was	O	-	-
2	sung	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	big	O	-	-
6	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-
7	jail	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eddy_Arnold_Happy_Birthday_To_You-004
# text = In Olive Hill Kentucky
1	In	O	-	-
2	Olive	B-LOC	-	-
3	Hill	I-LOC	-	-
4	Kentucky	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_It_s_Five_O_Clock_Somewhere-026
# text = Funny you should ask Alan, I'd say:
1	Funny	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	should	O	-	-
4	ask	O	-	-
5	Alan	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	d	O	-	-
10	say	O	-	-
11	:	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__The_Conversation-019
# text = Well if he was here right now, Bocephus
1	Well	O	-	-
2	if	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	here	O	-	-
6	right	O	-	-
7	now	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Bocephus	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Sam_Stone-015
# text = And Sammy took to stealing when he got that empty feeling
1	And	O	-	-
2	Sammy	B-PER	-	-
3	took	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	stealing	O	-	-
6	when	O	-	-
7	he	O	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	empty	O	-	-
11	feeling	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Whoa_Babe-016
# text = (Yes, brother L. Sam)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Yes	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	brother	O	-	-
5	L	B-PER	-	-
6	.	I-PER	-	-
7	Sam	I-PER	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Wreck_of_the_Old_97
# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Wreck_of_the_Old_97-001
# text = They give him his orders at Monroe, Virginia
1	They	O	-	-
2	give	O	-	-
3	him	O	-	-
4	his	O	-	-
5	orders	O	-	-
6	at	O	-	-
7	Monroe	B-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Face_on_the_Barroom_Floor-064
# text = And you shall see the lovely Madeline upon the barroom floor."
1	And	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	shall	O	-	-
4	see	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	lovely	O	-	-
7	Madeline	B-PER	-	-
8	upon	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	barroom	O	-	-
11	floor	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	"	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Gaslighter
# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Gaslighter-001
# text = Gaslighter, denier
1	Gaslighter	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	denier	0	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_City_Boy_Country_Born-007
# text = Where I'd wake unto the wonder of the West Virginia morn
1	Where	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	d	O	-	-
5	wake	O	-	-
6	unto	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	wonder	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	West	B-LOC	-	-
12	Virginia	I-LOC	-	-
13	morn	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_New_Texas_Playboy_Rag-011
# text = And memories start to roam of my Texas home
1	And	O	-	-
2	memories	O	-	-
3	start	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	roam	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
9	home	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Backslider_s_Wine-016
# text = I dare not drink Backslider's wine no more
1	I	O	-	-
2	dare	O	-	-
3	not	O	-	-
4	drink	O	-	-
5	Backslider	0	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	wine	O	-	-
9	no	O	-	-
10	more	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Silent_Night-010
# text = Son of God, love's pure light
1	Son	O	-	-
2	of	O	-	-
3	God	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	pure	O	-	-
9	light	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_All_My_Ex_s_Live_In_Texas-021
# text = Therefore I reside in Tennessee
1	Therefore	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	reside	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_In_The_Pines-002
# text = Went down that Georgia line
1	Went	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-
5	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Chasin_That_Neon_Rainbow-011
# text = Heading down to Houston for a show on Saturday night
1	Heading	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	Houston	B-LOC	-	-
5	for	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	show	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	Saturday	O	-	-
10	night	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_River_Of_Jordan-011
# text = But Elisha said to Naaman "go dip yourself in Jordan"
1	But	O	-	-
2	Elisha	B-PER	-	-
3	said	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	Naaman	B-PER	-	-
6	"	O	-	-
7	go	O	-	-
8	dip	O	-	-
9	yourself	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	Jordan	B-LOC	-	-
12	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_As_Soon_As_I_Hang_Up_The_Phone-004
# text = Loretta, there's something I just got to tell ya...
1	Loretta	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	there	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	something	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	just	O	-	-
9	got	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	tell	O	-	-
12	ya	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus
# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus-001
# text = Once a man named Steven preached about the Lord
1	Once	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	man	O	-	-
4	named	O	-	-
5	Steven	B-PER	-	-
6	preached	O	-	-
7	about	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Lord	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_The_Martha_White_Theme-009
# text = Get Martha White self-rising meal
1	Get	O	-	-
2	Martha	B-PER	-	-
3	White	I-PER	-	-
4	self	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	rising	O	-	-
7	meal	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gram_Parsons_Hearts_on_Fire-013
# text = Go out forget her lies
1	Go	O	-	-
2	out	O	-	-
3	forget	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	lies	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Paradise-006
# text = Down by the Green River where Paradise lay
1	Down	O	-	-
2	by	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Green	B-LOC	-	-
5	River	I-LOC	-	-
6	where	O	-	-
7	Paradise	B-LOC	-	-
8	lay	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_I_m_Ready_To_Go_Home-016
# text = Where the children of God will never part
1	Where	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	children	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	will	O	-	-
7	never	O	-	-
8	part	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-008
# text = And all she found was Earl
1	And	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	she	O	-	-
4	found	O	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	Earl	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Nashville_Is_A_Groovy_Little_Town-017
# text = I've got myself a little shack out on ol' hickory lake
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	myself	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	little	O	-	-
8	shack	O	-	-
9	out	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-
11	ol	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	hickory	B-LOC	-	-
14	lake	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_It_s_All_Going_to_Pot-018
# text = If ya ask ol' Will
1	If	O	-	-
2	ya	O	-	-
3	ask	O	-	-
4	ol	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	Will	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_The_Martha_White_Theme-004
# text = Get Martha White self-rising flour
1	Get	O	-	-
2	Martha	B-PER	-	-
3	White	I-PER	-	-
4	self	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	rising	O	-	-
7	flour	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Amos_Moses-010
# text = When Amos Moses was a boy
1	When	O	-	-
2	Amos	B-PER	-	-
3	Moses	I-PER	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	boy	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-George_Strait_All_My_Ex_s_Live_In_Texas
# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_All_My_Ex_s_Live_In_Texas-001
# text = All my exes live in Texas
1	All	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	exes	O	-	-
4	live	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Texas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Kansas_City_Star-002
# text = It was postmarked Omaha
1	It	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	postmarked	O	-	-
4	Omaha	B-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Mid_the_Green_Fields_of_Virginia
# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Mid_the_Green_Fields_of_Virginia-001
# text = Mid the green fields of Virginia in the vale of Shenandoah
1	Mid	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	green	O	-	-
4	fields	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	vale	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	Shenandoah	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Tequila_Sheila-005
# text = For all the damn gold in Juarez
1	For	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	damn	O	-	-
5	gold	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Juarez	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Face_on_the_Barroom_Floor-002
# text = Which well-nigh filled Joe's barroom on the corner of the square
1	Which	O	-	-
2	well	O	-	-
3	-	O	-	-
4	nigh	O	-	-
5	filled	O	-	-
6	Joe	B-PER	-	-
7	'	I-PER	-	-
8	s	I-PER	-	-
9	barroom	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	corner	O	-	-
13	of	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	square	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Pretty_Good-018
# text = She got raped by Dobbin's dog
1	She	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	raped	O	-	-
4	by	O	-	-
5	Dobbin	B-PER	-	-
6	'	I-PER	-	-
7	s	I-PER	-	-
8	dog	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_When_I_Get_to_Heaven-018
# text = What are you gonna do with time after you've bought the farm?
1	What	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	gonna	O	-	-
5	do	O	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	time	O	-	-
8	after	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	ve	O	-	-
12	bought	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	farm	O	-	-
15	?	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Heartbreak_U_S_A_
# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Heartbreak_U_S_A_-001
# text = (Back home in heartbreak USA)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Back	O	-	-
3	home	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	heartbreak	O	-	-
6	USA	B-LOC	-	-
7	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_The_Carroll_County_Accident-007
# text = It seemed that Mary Ellen Jones would surely die
1	It	O	-	-
2	seemed	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	Mary	B-PER	-	-
5	Ellen	I-PER	-	-
6	Jones	I-PER	-	-
7	would	O	-	-
8	surely	O	-	-
9	die	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_New_Texas_Playboy_Rag-015
# text = With that Texas playboy rag
1	With	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
4	playboy	O	-	-
5	rag	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Fall_of_Charleston-024
# text = We’ll squash poor Jeff’s confederacy, and then get hunkydory!
1	We	O	-	-
2	’	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	squash	O	-	-
5	poor	O	-	-
6	Jeff	B-PER	-	-
7	’	I-PER	-	-
8	s	I-PER	-	-
9	confederacy	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	then	O	-	-
13	get	O	-	-
14	hunkydory	O	-	-
15	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Jesus_Don_t_Give_Up_On_Me-003
# text = I've let you down, Jesus, that's not hard to see
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	let	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	down	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	that	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	not	O	-	-
14	hard	O	-	-
15	to	O	-	-
16	see	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_Old_Gang_s_Gone-008
# text = Johnny Green's in Jacksonville he's a doctor now you know
1	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
2	Green	I-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Jacksonville	B-LOC	-	-
7	he	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	doctor	O	-	-
12	now	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-
14	know	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-034
# text = Baraboo, Waterloo, Kalamazoo, Kansas City
1	Baraboo	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Waterloo	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Kalamazoo	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Kansas	B-LOC	-	-
8	City	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Honky_Tonk_Heroes-011
# text = I was down at Green Gables, a-hawkin' them tables
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	down	O	-	-
4	at	O	-	-
5	Green	B-LOC	-	-
6	Gables	I-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	hawkin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	them	O	-	-
13	tables	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Back_Up_And_Push-003
# text = Well, it's old Satan, right there a waiting
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	old	O	-	-
7	Satan	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	right	O	-	-
10	there	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	waiting	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gram_Parsons_Pride_of_Man-005
# text = Babylon is laid to waste Egypt's buried in her shame
1	Babylon	B-LOC	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	laid	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	waste	O	-	-
6	Egypt	B-LOC	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	buried	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	her	O	-	-
12	shame	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_Who_s_Gonna_Fill_Their_Shoes-016
# text = And the Wabash Cannonball
1	And	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Wabash	B-ORG	-	-
4	Cannonball	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Tequila_Sheila-032
# text = So pour me another Tequila Sheila
1	So	O	-	-
2	pour	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	another	O	-	-
5	Tequila	O	-	-
6	Sheila	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_One_Piece_at_a_Time-002
# text = And went to Detroit, working on assembly line
1	And	O	-	-
2	went	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	Detroit	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	working	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	assembly	O	-	-
9	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_Get_in_Line_Brother-013
# text = Then I'm sure you'll know the love of God is real
1	Then	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	sure	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	ll	O	-	-
9	know	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	love	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	God	B-PER	-	-
14	is	O	-	-
15	real	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_That_s_Where_My_Money_Goes-002
# text = I've got a gal in Monroeville she won't dance but her sister will
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	gal	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Monroeville	B-LOC	-	-
9	she	O	-	-
10	won	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	dance	O	-	-
14	but	O	-	-
15	her	O	-	-
16	sister	O	-	-
17	will	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_I_m_Ready_to_Go-007
# text = But Jesus came in and saved us all from sin
1	But	O	-	-
2	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
3	came	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	saved	O	-	-
7	us	O	-	-
8	all	O	-	-
9	from	O	-	-
10	sin	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Uptown_Poker_Club-050
# text = Henry if you'll break out another deck of them Bicycles me and the boys will get on with the business
1	Henry	B-PER	-	-
2	if	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ll	O	-	-
6	break	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	another	O	-	-
9	deck	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	them	O	-	-
12	Bicycles	B-ORG	-	-
13	me	O	-	-
14	and	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	boys	O	-	-
17	will	O	-	-
18	get	O	-	-
19	on	O	-	-
20	with	O	-	-
21	the	O	-	-
22	business	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_My_Little_Lady-005
# text = Oh, Haydee, my little lady, I love no one but you
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Haydee	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	little	O	-	-
7	lady	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	love	O	-	-
11	no	O	-	-
12	one	O	-	-
13	but	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Lonesome_On_ry_and_Mean
# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Lonesome_On_ry_and_Mean-001
# text = On a Greyhound bus
1	On	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	Greyhound	B-ORG	-	-
4	bus	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Have_You_Ever_Seen_the_Rain-011
# text = I know it can't stop, I wonder
1	I	O	-	-
2	know	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	can	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	stop	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	wonder	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-014
# text = Did she set for you a chair, Billy Boy, Billy Boy?
1	Did	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	set	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	chair	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Billy	B-PER	-	-
10	Boy	I-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Billy	B-PER	-	-
13	Boy	I-PER	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Little_Rock-009
# text = Oh, little rock
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	little	B-LOC	-	-
4	rock	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Wreck_of_the_Old_97-007
# text = And when we cross that White Oak Mountain
1	And	O	-	-
2	when	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	cross	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	White	B-LOC	-	-
7	Oak	I-LOC	-	-
8	Mountain	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_King_Of_The_Road-010
# text = Destination: Bangor, Maine
1	Destination	O	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Bangor	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Maine	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina-016
# text = Corrine, Corrina where did you stay last night?
1	Corrine	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Corrina	B-PER	-	-
4	where	O	-	-
5	did	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	stay	O	-	-
8	last	O	-	-
9	night	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Bonnie_Blue_Flag-034
# text = And here's to old Virginia-
1	And	O	-	-
2	here	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	old	O	-	-
7	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
8	-	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Me_and_Bobby_McGee-012
# text = Feelin' good was easy, Lord, when Bobby sang the blues
1	Feelin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	good	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	easy	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Lord	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	when	O	-	-
10	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
11	sang	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	blues	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_Lorene-015
# text = Lorene, I feel I have lost you
1	Lorene	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	feel	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	have	O	-	-
7	lost	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Two_Piña_Coladas-027
# text = Let's all set sail with Captain Morgan
1	Let	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	set	O	-	-
6	sail	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	Captain	B-ORG	-	-
9	Morgan	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_The_Story_of_the_Lawson_Family-004
# text = At his home in North Carolina
1	At	O	-	-
2	his	O	-	-
3	home	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	North	B-LOC	-	-
6	Carolina	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Hello_in_There-005
# text = John and Linda live in Omaha
1	John	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Linda	B-PER	-	-
4	live	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Omaha	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-015
# text = But Earl walked right through that restraining order
1	But	O	-	-
2	Earl	B-PER	-	-
3	walked	O	-	-
4	right	O	-	-
5	through	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	restraining	O	-	-
8	order	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lefty_Frizzell_Saginaw_Michigan-009
# text = Now I'm up here in Alaska, looking around for gold
1	Now	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	up	O	-	-
6	here	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Alaska	B-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	looking	O	-	-
11	around	O	-	-
12	for	O	-	-
13	gold	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_One_I_Loved_Back_Then_The_Corvette_Song_
# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_One_I_Loved_Back_Then_The_Corvette_Song_-001
# text = I stopped off at the Quicksack
1	I	O	-	-
2	stopped	O	-	-
3	off	O	-	-
4	at	O	-	-
5	the	0	-	-
6	Quicksack	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Footprints_in_the_Snow-007
# text = I bless that happy day that Nellie lost her way
1	I	O	-	-
2	bless	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	happy	O	-	-
5	day	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	Nellie	B-PER	-	-
8	lost	O	-	-
9	her	O	-	-
10	way	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Streets_Of_Bakersfield-012
# text = Ever walked the streets of Bakersfield?
1	Ever	O	-	-
2	walked	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	streets	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	Bakersfield	B-LOC	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Ocean_Front_Property-005
# text = I got some ocean front property in Arizona
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	some	O	-	-
4	ocean	O	-	-
5	front	O	-	-
6	property	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Arizona	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_Angels_Rejoiced_Last_Night-010
# text = When God called on Mother one night
1	When	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	called	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	Mother	O	-	-
6	one	O	-	-
7	night	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Mid_the_Green_Fields_of_Virginia-009
# text = Mid the green fields of Virginia stands an old mill by the stream
1	Mid	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	green	O	-	-
4	fields	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
7	stands	O	-	-
8	an	O	-	-
9	old	O	-	-
10	mill	O	-	-
11	by	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	stream	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__The_Conversation-031
# text = To the stories only Hank could tell
1	To	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	stories	O	-	-
4	only	O	-	-
5	Hank	B-PER	-	-
6	could	O	-	-
7	tell	O	-	-
