# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_South-017
# text = She was rich in looks from a poor Memphis family
1	She	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	rich	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	looks	O	-	-
6	from	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	poor	O	-	-
9	Memphis	B-LOC	-	-
10	family	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-014
# text = Molly's a-beatin' old Tenbrooks, clear out of sight
1	Molly	B-PER	-	-
2	'	0	-	-
3	s	0	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	beatin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	old	O	-	-
9	Tenbrooks	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	clear	O	-	-
12	out	O	-	-
13	of	O	-	-
14	sight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Trudy-014
# text = I met a peroxide blonde in a bar on D-ville I was flyin' high and feelin' mean
1	I	O	-	-
2	met	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	peroxide	O	-	-
5	blonde	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	bar	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	D	B-LOC	-	-
11	-	I-LOC	-	-
12	ville	I-LOC	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	was	O	-	-
15	flyin	O	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	high	O	-	-
18	and	O	-	-
19	feelin	O	-	-
20	'	O	-	-
21	mean	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_Angels_Rejoiced_Last_Night-007
# text = I've never seen my daddy inside the house of God
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	never	O	-	-
5	seen	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	daddy	O	-	-
8	inside	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	house	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_The_Carroll_County_Accident-006
# text = Walter Browning lost his life and for a time
1	Walter	B-PER	-	-
2	Browning	I-PER	-	-
3	lost	O	-	-
4	his	O	-	-
5	life	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	time	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__The_Conversation-035
# text = And how Miss Audrey loved that man
1	And	O	-	-
2	how	O	-	-
3	Miss	O	-	-
4	Audrey	B-PER	-	-
5	loved	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	man	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Folsom_Prison_Blues-007
# text = But I shot a man in Reno just to watch him die
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	shot	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	man	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Reno	B-LOC	-	-
8	just	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	watch	O	-	-
11	him	O	-	-
12	die	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_Country_Christmas-008
# text = Aunt Annie Belle will be here uncle Bill and darn our kids
1	Aunt	O	-	-
2	Annie	B-PER	-	-
3	Belle	I-PER	-	-
4	will	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	here	O	-	-
7	uncle	O	-	-
8	Bill	B-PER	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	darn	O	-	-
11	our	O	-	-
12	kids	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Julianna_Calm_Down-026
# text = And Eva, hold on
1	And	O	-	-
2	Eva	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	hold	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__A_Country_Boy_Can_Survive-033
# text = We're from north California and south Alabam'
1	We	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	north	O	-	-
6	California	B-LOC	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	south	O	-	-
9	Alabam	B-LOC	-	-
10	'	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Chattahoochee-009
# text = Yeah way down yonder on the Chattahoochee
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	way	O	-	-
3	down	O	-	-
4	yonder	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Chattahoochee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Four_Strong_Winds-005
# text = I may go out to Alberta weather's good there in the fall
1	I	O	-	-
2	may	O	-	-
3	go	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Alberta	B-LOC	-	-
7	weather	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	good	O	-	-
11	there	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	fall	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tammy_Wynette_My_Elusive_Dreams-020
# text = G: And a little memory to cling to
1	G	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	And	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	little	O	-	-
6	memory	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	cling	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Fancy-016
# text = She said, "Here's your one chance, Fancy, don't let me down"
1	She	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	Here	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	your	O	-	-
9	one	O	-	-
10	chance	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Fancy	B-PER	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	don	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	t	O	-	-
17	let	O	-	-
18	me	O	-	-
19	down	O	-	-
20	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Hellacious_Acres-016
# text = Oh, even the Devil needs money
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	even	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Devil	B-PER	-	-
6	needs	O	-	-
7	money	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Luckenbach_Texas_Back_to_the_Basics_of_Love_-025
# text = And Jerry Jeff's train songs and Blue Eyes Cryin' in the Rain
1	And	O	-	-
2	Jerry	B-PER	-	-
3	Jeff	I-PER	-	-
4	'	I-PER	-	-
5	s	I-PER	-	-
6	train	O	-	-
7	songs	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	Blue	0	-	-
10	Eyes	0	-	-
11	Cryin	0	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	in	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	Rain	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lefty_Frizzell_Saginaw_Michigan-002
# text = I grew up in a house on Saginaw bay
1	I	O	-	-
2	grew	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	house	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	Saginaw	B-LOC	-	-
9	bay	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Tomorrow_Night_In_Baltimore-018
# text = Then she told him to load the baggage because they open tomorrow night in Baltimore
1	Then	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	told	O	-	-
4	him	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	load	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	baggage	O	-	-
9	because	O	-	-
10	they	O	-	-
11	open	O	-	-
12	tomorrow	O	-	-
13	night	O	-	-
14	in	O	-	-
15	Baltimore	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Pancho_And_Lefty-034
# text = Pancho needs your prayers, it's true
1	Pancho	B-PER	-	-
2	needs	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	prayers	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	true	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_When_I_Get_to_Heaven-019
# text = And then I'm gonna go find my mom and dad and good old brother Doug
1	And	O	-	-
2	then	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	gonna	O	-	-
7	go	O	-	-
8	find	O	-	-
9	my	O	-	-
10	mom	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	dad	O	-	-
13	and	O	-	-
14	good	O	-	-
15	old	O	-	-
16	brother	O	-	-
17	Doug	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_Committed_To_Parkview-006
# text = And for one thing or another, committed to Parkview
1	And	O	-	-
2	for	O	-	-
3	one	O	-	-
4	thing	O	-	-
5	or	O	-	-
6	another	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	committed	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	Parkview	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Williamson_County-002
# text = Of a Williamson County hotel
1	Of	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	Williamson	B-LOC	-	-
4	County	I-LOC	-	-
5	hotel	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-030
# text = I've been to Pittsburgh, Parkersburg, Gravelbourg, Colorado
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Pittsburgh	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Parkersburg	B-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Gravelbourg	B-LOC	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Colorado	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_I_m_A_Survivor-004
# text = And God's amazing grace
1	And	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	'	I-PER	-	-
4	s	I-PER	-	-
5	amazing	O	-	-
6	grace	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Uptown_Poker_Club-019
# text = And Leroy quit takin' em offa the bottom ooh that's rough
1	And	O	-	-
2	Leroy	B-PER	-	-
3	quit	O	-	-
4	takin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	em	O	-	-
7	offa	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	bottom	O	-	-
10	ooh	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	rough	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-013
# text = Kaw-Liga was a lonely Indian, never went nowhere
1	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
2	-	I-PER	-	-
3	Liga	I-PER	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	lonely	O	-	-
7	Indian	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	never	O	-	-
10	went	O	-	-
11	nowhere	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Glen_Campbell_Galveston
# sent_id = lyrics-Glen_Campbell_Galveston-001
# text = Galveston, oh Galveston
1	Galveston	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	oh	O	-	-
4	Galveston	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_Send_Me_Down_to_Tucson-015
# text = The one in Tucson she don’t hide it and when she gets excited
1	The	O	-	-
2	one	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	Tucson	B-LOC	-	-
5	she	O	-	-
6	don	O	-	-
7	’	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	hide	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	when	O	-	-
13	she	O	-	-
14	gets	O	-	-
15	excited	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Take_Me_Back_To_Tulsa-005
# text = Take me back to Tulsa
1	Take	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	back	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	Tulsa	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_King_Is_Gone_So_Are_You_-002
# text = That looks like Elvis
1	That	O	-	-
2	looks	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	Elvis	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Union_Dixie-007
# text = Each Dixie boy must understand that he must mind his Uncle Sam
1	Each	O	-	-
2	Dixie	B-LOC	-	-
3	boy	O	-	-
4	must	O	-	-
5	understand	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	he	O	-	-
8	must	O	-	-
9	mind	O	-	-
10	his	O	-	-
11	Uncle	B-PER	-	-
12	Sam	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_Charlie_s_Angel-008
# text = Charlie thinks his game is cool but he's the picture of a fool
1	Charlie	B-PER	-	-
2	thinks	O	-	-
3	his	O	-	-
4	game	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	cool	O	-	-
7	but	O	-	-
8	he	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	picture	O	-	-
13	of	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	fool	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus-010
# text = Steven knew he'd soon be through with all toil and strife
1	Steven	B-PER	-	-
2	knew	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	soon	O	-	-
7	be	O	-	-
8	through	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	all	O	-	-
11	toil	O	-	-
12	and	O	-	-
13	strife	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Tequila_Sheila-026
# text = But I can't make love to a squealer, Sheila
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	can	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	make	O	-	-
7	love	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	squealer	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Sheila	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Spanish_Pipedream-032
# text = They all found Jesus on their own
1	They	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	found	O	-	-
4	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	their	O	-	-
7	own	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Never_Been_to_Spain-019
# text = In Oklahoma or Arizona
1	In	O	-	-
2	Oklahoma	B-LOC	-	-
3	or	O	-	-
4	Arizona	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_Who_s_Gonna_Fill_Their_Shoes-010
# text = The Okie from Muskogee
1	The	O	-	-
2	Okie	O	-	-
3	from	O	-	-
4	Muskogee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Golden_Rocket-020
# text = That Golden Rocket is doin' me right
1	That	O	-	-
2	Golden	B-ORG	-	-
3	Rocket	I-ORG	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	doin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	right	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Brakeman_s_Blues_Yodeling_The_Blues_Away_-008
# text = Get my breakfast here, get my dinner in New Orleans
1	Get	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	breakfast	O	-	-
4	here	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	get	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	dinner	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	New	B-LOC	-	-
11	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Patsy_Cline_Dear_God-024
# text = Dear God...
1	Dear	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Automatic-007
# text = If we drove all the way to Dallas just to buy an Easter dress
1	If	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	drove	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	way	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Dallas	B-LOC	-	-
9	just	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	buy	O	-	-
12	an	O	-	-
13	Easter	O	-	-
14	dress	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Rodeo-003
# text = And she'd give half of Texas
1	And	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	d	O	-	-
5	give	O	-	-
6	half	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	Texas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Marie_Laveau-023
# text = So Marie done some magic, and she shook a little sand
1	So	O	-	-
2	Marie	B-PER	-	-
3	done	O	-	-
4	some	O	-	-
5	magic	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	she	O	-	-
9	shook	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	little	O	-	-
12	sand	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Jody_and_the_Kid-016
# text = How they use to call us Jody and the kid
1	How	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	use	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	call	O	-	-
6	us	O	-	-
7	Jody	B-PER	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	kid	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Folsom_Prison_Blues_Live_at_Folsom_State_Prison_Folsom_CA_January_1968_
# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Folsom_Prison_Blues_Live_at_Folsom_State_Prison_Folsom_CA_January_1968_-001
# text = "Hello, I'm Johnny Cash."
1	"	O	-	-
2	Hello	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
8	Cash	I-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Attitude_Adjustment-024
# text = I said, "Darlin', that was you're first mistake"
1	I	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	Darlin	0	-	-
6	'	0	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	that	O	-	-
9	was	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	re	O	-	-
13	first	O	-	-
14	mistake	O	-	-
15	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare__Margie_s_At_The_Lincoln_Park_Inn-012
# text = And all of the Margie’s and all of the Lincoln Park Inns
1	And	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Margie	B-LOC	-	-
6	’	I-LOC	-	-
7	s	I-LOC	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	all	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Lincoln	B-LOC	-	-
13	Park	I-LOC	-	-
14	Inns	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kenny_Rogers_Coward_Of_The_County-023
# text = The Gatlin boys just laughed at him
1	The	O	-	-
2	Gatlin	B-LOC	-	-
3	boys	O	-	-
4	just	O	-	-
5	laughed	O	-	-
6	at	O	-	-
7	him	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Dixie-009
# text = To arms! To arms! And conquer peace for Dixie!
1	To	O	-	-
2	arms	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-
4	To	O	-	-
5	arms	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	And	O	-	-
8	conquer	O	-	-
9	peace	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	Dixie	B-LOC	-	-
12	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Jackson-004
# text = Yeah, I'm goin' to Jackson
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	goin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Jackson	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_City_Boy_Country_Born-004
# text = But New York ain't a place for kids to grow
1	But	O	-	-
2	New	B-LOC	-	-
3	York	I-LOC	-	-
4	ain	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	place	O	-	-
9	for	O	-	-
10	kids	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	grow	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_I_Ain_t_Living_Long_Like_This-018
# text = Makes Texas Ruby look like Sandra Dee
1	Makes	O	-	-
2	Texas	B-PER	-	-
3	Ruby	I-PER	-	-
4	look	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Sandra	B-PER	-	-
7	Dee	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_The_Carroll_County_Accident-013
# text = Mary Ellen testified he flagged her down
1	Mary	B-PER	-	-
2	Ellen	I-PER	-	-
3	testified	O	-	-
4	he	O	-	-
5	flagged	O	-	-
6	her	O	-	-
7	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Don_t_Rock_the_Jukebox-004
# text = For the Rolling Stones
1	For	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Rolling	B-ORG	-	-
4	Stones	I-ORG	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_The_Church_in_the_Wildwood
# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_The_Church_in_the_Wildwood-001
# text = There's a church in the valley by the wildwood,
1	There	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	church	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	valley	O	-	-
9	by	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	wildwood	0	-	-
12	,	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Shania_Twain_Giddy_Up_-002
# text = Somewhere in small-town Ohio
1	Somewhere	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	small	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	town	O	-	-
6	Ohio	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_One_s_On_The_Way-022
# text = And Better Homes and Gardens shows the modern way to live
1	And	O	-	-
2	Better	B-ORG	-	-
3	Homes	I-ORG	-	-
4	and	I-ORG	-	-
5	Gardens	I-ORG	-	-
6	shows	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	modern	O	-	-
9	way	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	live	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-020
# text = Poor ol' Kaw-Liga, you just ain't never had no kissin'
1	Poor	O	-	-
2	ol	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
5	-	I-PER	-	-
6	Liga	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	just	O	-	-
10	ain	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	never	O	-	-
14	had	O	-	-
15	no	O	-	-
16	kissin	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_Filipino_Baby-013
# text = In a little rustic cottage in the port of Philippines dwells a lonely little maiden all alone
1	In	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	little	O	-	-
4	rustic	O	-	-
5	cottage	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	port	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	Philippines	B-LOC	-	-
11	dwells	O	-	-
12	a	O	-	-
13	lonely	O	-	-
14	little	O	-	-
15	maiden	O	-	-
16	all	O	-	-
17	alone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Two_Piña_Coladas-011
# text = Let's set sail with Captain Morgan
1	Let	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	set	O	-	-
5	sail	O	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	Captain	B-ORG	-	-
8	Morgan	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eddy_Arnold_Green_Green_Grass_of_Home-003
# text = Down the road I look and there runs Mary hair of gold and lips like cherries
1	Down	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	road	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	look	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	there	O	-	-
8	runs	O	-	-
9	Mary	B-PER	-	-
10	hair	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	gold	O	-	-
13	and	O	-	-
14	lips	O	-	-
15	like	O	-	-
16	cherries	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_One_Piece_at_a_Time-002
# text = And went to Detroit, working on assembly line
1	And	O	-	-
2	went	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	Detroit	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	working	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	assembly	O	-	-
9	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Nashville_Is_A_Groovy_Little_Town-023
# text = What else you got? Yes, nashville is a groovy little town
1	What	O	-	-
2	else	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	Yes	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	nashville	B-LOC	-	-
9	is	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	groovy	O	-	-
12	little	O	-	-
13	town	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-010
# text = That Wanda started gettin' abused
1	That	O	-	-
2	Wanda	B-PER	-	-
3	started	O	-	-
4	gettin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	abused	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_Daniel_Prayed-007
# text = And he prayed to God every morning, noon, and night
1	And	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	prayed	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	every	O	-	-
7	morning	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	noon	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	night	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Casey_s_Last_Ride-007
# text = But Casey minds the arrows and ignores the fatal echoes
1	But	O	-	-
2	Casey	B-PER	-	-
3	minds	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	arrows	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	ignores	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	fatal	O	-	-
10	echoes	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Virginia_s_Bloody_Soil-036
# text = Till a bullet pierced our captain's brain, on Virginia's bloody soil
1	Till	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	bullet	O	-	-
4	pierced	O	-	-
5	our	O	-	-
6	captain	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	brain	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
13	'	O	I-LOC	-
14	s	O	I-LOC	-
15	bloody	O	-	-
16	soil	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_Blue_Ridge_Cabin_Home-006
# text = From those Blue Ridge hills I did roam
1	From	O	-	-
2	those	O	-	-
3	Blue	B-LOC	-	-
4	Ridge	I-LOC	-	-
5	hills	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	did	O	-	-
8	roam	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charlie_Rich_Good_Time_Charlie_s_Got_The_Blues-002
# text = Said they're movin' to L.A
1	Said	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	re	O	-	-
5	movin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	L	B-LOC	-	-
9	.	I-LOC	-	-
10	A	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Lonesome_On_ry_and_Mean-011
# text = Of the Basin Street Queens
1	Of	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Basin	B-LOC	-	-
4	Street	I-LOC	-	-
5	Queens	I-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Frosty_the_Snowman
# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Frosty_the_Snowman-001
# text = Frosty the snowman was a jolly happy soul
1	Frosty	B-PER	-	-
2	the	0	-	-
3	snowman	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	jolly	O	-	-
7	happy	O	-	-
8	soul	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Lord_Lead_Me_On-013
# text = I asked the Lord, (I asked the Lord)
1	I	O	-	-
2	asked	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Lord	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	asked	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Lord	B-PER	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-003
# text = If you're going to Winnemucca Mack, with me, you can ride
1	If	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	re	O	-	-
5	going	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	Winnemucca	B-LOC	-	-
8	Mack	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	with	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-
14	can	O	-	-
15	ride	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_Black_Jack_s_Bar-002
# text = I played for the people in Black Jack's Bar
1	I	O	-	-
2	played	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	people	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Black	B-ORG	-	-
8	Jack	I-ORG	-	-
9	'	I-ORG	-	-
10	s	I-ORG	-	-
11	Bar	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Blue_Yodel_T_For_Texas_-013
# text = 'Cause this Georgia water tastes like turpentine
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	this	O	-	-
4	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-
5	water	O	-	-
6	tastes	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	turpentine	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Fall_of_Charleston-009
# text = This South Carolina chivalry, they once did loudly boast
1	This	O	-	-
2	South	B-LOC	-	-
3	Carolina	I-LOC	-	-
4	chivalry	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	they	O	-	-
7	once	O	-	-
8	did	O	-	-
9	loudly	O	-	-
10	boast	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-013
# text = Kaw-Liga was a lonely Indian, never went nowhere
1	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
2	-	I-PER	-	-
3	Liga	I-PER	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	lonely	O	-	-
7	Indian	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	never	O	-	-
10	went	O	-	-
11	nowhere	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Me_and_Bobby_McGee-016
# text = Bobby shared the secrets of my soul
1	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
2	shared	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	secrets	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	soul	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_I_m_Working_on_a_Road_To_Glory_Land_-004
# text = So now I started building a road to Gloryland
1	So	O	-	-
2	now	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	started	O	-	-
5	building	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	road	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Gloryland	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__The_Conversation-031
# text = To the stories only Hank could tell
1	To	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	stories	O	-	-
4	only	O	-	-
5	Hank	B-PER	-	-
6	could	O	-	-
7	tell	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charlie_Rich_San_Francisco_Is_A_Lonely_Town-013
# text = San Francisco is a lonely town...
1	San	B-LOC	-	-
2	Francisco	I-LOC	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	lonely	O	-	-
6	town	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-013
# text = Kyper, Kyper, you're not a-ridin' right
1	Kyper	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Kyper	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	re	O	-	-
8	not	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	ridin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	right	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_Cuddle_Up_Cozy_Down_Christmas-034
# text = Merry Christmas Dolly
1	Merry	O	-	-
2	Christmas	O	-	-
3	Dolly	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Amarillo_By_Morning-007
# text = They took my saddle in Houston, broke my leg in Santa Fe
1	They	O	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	saddle	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Houston	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	broke	O	-	-
9	my	O	-	-
10	leg	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	Santa	B-LOC	-	-
13	Fe	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Patches-056
# text = I can still hear Papa, what he said
1	I	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	still	O	-	-
4	hear	O	-	-
5	Papa	0	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	what	O	-	-
8	he	O	-	-
9	said	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Folsom_Prison_Blues-007
# text = But I shot a man in Reno just to watch him die
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	shot	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	man	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Reno	B-LOC	-	-
8	just	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	watch	O	-	-
11	him	O	-	-
12	die	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__All_My_Rowdy_Friends_Have_Settled_Down_-011
# text = And old George Jones, I'm glad to see, is finally getting straight
1	And	O	-	-
2	old	O	-	-
3	George	B-PER	-	-
4	Jones	I-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	glad	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	see	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	is	O	-	-
14	finally	O	-	-
15	getting	O	-	-
16	straight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-013
# text = I've been to Reno, Chicago, Fargo, Minnesota, Buffalo, Toronto, Winslow, Sarasota
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Reno	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Chicago	B-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Fargo	B-LOC	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Minnesota	B-LOC	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Buffalo	B-LOC	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	Toronto	B-LOC	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	Winslow	B-LOC	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	Sarasota	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Trudy-002
# text = Tell her I'm hung up in Dallas they won't let me out of this jail
1	Tell	O	-	-
2	her	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	hung	O	-	-
7	up	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Dallas	B-LOC	-	-
10	they	O	-	-
11	won	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	t	O	-	-
14	let	O	-	-
15	me	O	-	-
16	out	O	-	-
17	of	O	-	-
18	this	O	-	-
19	jail	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_Blues_Man-012
# text = I went to Basin Street Joe
1	I	O	-	-
2	went	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	Basin	B-PER	-	-
5	Street	I-PER	-	-
6	Joe	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Take_Me_Back_To_Tulsa-011
# text = Walk and talk, Susie
1	Walk	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	talk	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Susie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_Jolene-015
# text = But you don't know what he means to me, Jolene
1	But	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	know	O	-	-
7	what	O	-	-
8	he	O	-	-
9	means	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Jolene	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Jackson-022
# text = I'm goin' to Jackson, and that's a fact
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	goin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	Jackson	B-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	that	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	fact	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Good_Time-025
# text = B & D, Kix and Dunn
1	B	B-ORG	-	-
2	&	I-ORG	-	-
3	D	I-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Kix	B-PER	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	Dunn	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_99_Years_Is_Almost_for_Life-015
# text = I'm serving in Nashville for another man's hate
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	serving	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Nashville	B-LOC	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	another	O	-	-
9	man	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	s	O	-	-
12	hate	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gram_Parsons_Big_Mouth_Blues-006
# text = And Lord knows that New York City's got
1	And	O	-	-
2	Lord	B-PER	-	-
3	knows	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	New	B-LOC	-	-
6	York	I-LOC	-	-
7	City	I-LOC	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	got	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Amarillo_By_Morning-006
# text = Amarillo, I'll be there
1	Amarillo	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ll	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	there	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Cherokee_Maiden-011
# text = And straight as an arrow flies, we'll ride to Paradise
1	And	O	-	-
2	straight	O	-	-
3	as	O	-	-
4	an	O	-	-
5	arrow	O	-	-
6	flies	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	we	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ll	O	-	-
11	ride	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	Paradise	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Uptown_Poker_Club-039
# text = Now Clyde you keep them bony hands up here on top of the table when you're dealin' please
1	Now	O	-	-
2	Clyde	B-PER	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	keep	O	-	-
5	them	O	-	-
6	bony	O	-	-
7	hands	O	-	-
8	up	O	-	-
9	here	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-
11	top	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	table	O	-	-
15	when	O	-	-
16	you	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-
18	re	O	-	-
19	dealin	O	-	-
20	'	O	-	-
21	please	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_Fancy-072
# text = Oh, here's your one chance, Fancy, don't let me down
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	here	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	one	O	-	-
8	chance	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Fancy	B-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	don	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	t	O	-	-
15	let	O	-	-
16	me	O	-	-
17	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Jesus_Don_t_Give_Up_On_Me-011
# text = Ah, Jesus, oh Jesus, don't give up on me
1	Ah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	oh	O	-	-
6	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	don	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	give	O	-	-
12	up	O	-	-
13	on	O	-	-
14	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Mule_Train-013
# text = A guitar for a cowboy way out in Arizona
1	A	O	-	-
2	guitar	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	cowboy	O	-	-
6	way	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Arizona	B-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Patsy_Cline_Bill_Bailey_Won_t_You_Please_Come_Home
# sent_id = lyrics-Patsy_Cline_Bill_Bailey_Won_t_You_Please_Come_Home-001
# text = Won't you come home, Bill Bailey, won't you come home?
1	Won	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	come	O	-	-
6	home	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Bill	B-PER	-	-
9	Bailey	I-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	won	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	t	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	come	O	-	-
16	home	O	-	-
17	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Wabash_Cannonball-016
# text = He'll be carried back to victory on the Wabash Cannonball
1	He	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	carried	O	-	-
6	back	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	victory	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	Wabash	B-ORG	-	-
12	Cannonball	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-002
# text = Tenbrooks gonna beat you, bright shinin' sun
1	Tenbrooks	B-PER	-	-
2	gonna	O	-	-
3	beat	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	bright	O	-	-
7	shinin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	sun	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_The_Legend_of_the_Johnson_Boys-006
# text = The Johnson boys were boys of honor they knew how the fortune made
1	The	O	-	-
2	Johnson	B-PER	-	-
3	boys	I-PER	-	-
4	were	O	-	-
5	boys	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	honor	O	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	knew	O	-	-
10	how	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	fortune	O	-	-
13	made	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-029
# text = La da da la me and Bobby McGee
1	La	O	-	-
2	da	O	-	-
3	da	O	-	-
4	la	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
8	McGee	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Julianna_Calm_Down-035
# text = And Yaya, calm down
1	And	O	-	-
2	Yaya	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	calm	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_Polka_on_a_Banjo-002
# text = Flatt and Scruggs
1	Flatt	B-ORG	-	-
2	and	I-ORG	-	-
3	Scruggs	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tammy_Wynette_D_I_V_O_R_C_E-007
# text = Me and little J-O-E will be goin' away
1	Me	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	little	O	-	-
4	J	B-PER	-	-
5	-	I-PER	-	-
6	O	I-PER	-	-
7	-	I-PER	-	-
8	E	I-PER	-	-
9	will	O	-	-
10	be	O	-	-
11	goin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	away	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-024
# text = They tasted alright to me, Earl
1	They	O	-	-
2	tasted	O	-	-
3	alright	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Earl	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_I_m_a_Ramblin_Man-024
# text = Well, up in Chicago
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	Chicago	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-013
# text = Buffalo, Toronto, Winslow, Sarasota
1	Buffalo	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Toronto	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Winslow	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Sarasota	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus-003
# text = Satan did not like it soon he had his crowd
1	Satan	B-PER	-	-
2	did	O	-	-
3	not	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	soon	O	-	-
7	he	O	-	-
8	had	O	-	-
9	his	O	-	-
10	crowd	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__The_American_Way-003
# text = If you blew in from Boston
1	If	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	blew	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	Boston	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Night_I_Stole_Old_Sammy_Morgan_s_Gin-018
# text = 'Twas the night I stole old Sammy Morgan's gin
1	'	O	-	-
2	Twas	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	night	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	stole	O	-	-
7	old	O	-	-
8	Sammy	B-PER	-	-
9	Morgan	I-PER	-	-
10	'	I-PER	-	-
11	s	I-PER	-	-
12	gin	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Foggy_Mountain_Top-010
# text = Lee-oh-lay-ee, lay-ee, oh-lay-ee
1	Lee	0	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	oh	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	lay	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	ee	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	lay	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	ee	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	oh	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	lay	O	-	-
16	-	O	-	-
17	ee	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Okie_From_Muskogee-008
# text = Like the hippies out in San Francisco do
1	Like	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	hippies	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	San	B-LOC	-	-
7	Francisco	I-LOC	-	-
8	do	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Drinkin_and_Dreamin_-012
# text = I'll never see Texas, L.A., or Old Mexico
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	never	O	-	-
5	see	O	-	-
6	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	L	B-LOC	-	-
9	.	I-LOC	-	-
10	A	I-LOC	-	-
11	.	I-LOC	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	or	O	-	-
14	Old	B-LOC	-	-
15	Mexico	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Getaway_Driver-018
# text = Bonnie and Clyde reminder
1	Bonnie	B-ORG	-	-
2	and	I-ORG	-	-
3	Clyde	I-ORG	-	-
4	reminder	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus-006
# text = I see Jesus over in the Promised Land
1	I	O	-	-
2	see	O	-	-
3	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
4	over	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Promised	B-LOC	-	-
8	Land	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_Coal_Miner_s_Daughter-002
# text = In a cabin on a hill in Butcher Holler
1	In	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	cabin	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	hill	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Butcher	B-LOC	-	-
9	Holler	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Pretty_Good-018
# text = She got raped by Dobbin's dog
1	She	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	raped	O	-	-
4	by	O	-	-
5	Dobbin	B-PER	-	-
6	'	I-PER	-	-
7	s	I-PER	-	-
8	dog	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Hellacious_Acres-014
# text = And tricky Dickie barkin', flashin' you his pardon
1	And	O	-	-
2	tricky	B-PER	-	-
3	Dickie	I-PER	-	-
4	barkin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	flashin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	his	O	-	-
11	pardon	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Homecoming-042
# text = We got a dance to work in Cartersville tonight
1	We	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	dance	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	work	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Cartersville	B-LOC	-	-
9	tonight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_A_Boy_Named_Sue-009
# text = Was before he left, he went and named me "Sue"
1	Was	O	-	-
2	before	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	left	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	went	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	named	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	"	O	-	-
12	Sue	B-PER	-	-
13	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_A_Boy_Named_Sue-015
# text = I tell ya, life ain't easy for a boy named "Sue"
1	I	O	-	-
2	tell	O	-	-
3	ya	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	life	O	-	-
6	ain	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	easy	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	boy	O	-	-
13	named	O	-	-
14	"	O	-	-
15	Sue	B-PER	-	-
16	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Uptown_Poker_Club-050
# text = Henry if you'll break out another deck of them Bicycles me and the boys will get on with the business
1	Henry	B-PER	-	-
2	if	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ll	O	-	-
6	break	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	another	O	-	-
9	deck	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	them	O	-	-
12	Bicycles	B-ORG	-	-
13	me	O	-	-
14	and	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	boys	O	-	-
17	will	O	-	-
18	get	O	-	-
19	on	O	-	-
20	with	O	-	-
21	the	O	-	-
22	business	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Blue_Eyes_Crying_In_the_Rain-013
# text = I can see her star in heaven
1	I	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	see	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	star	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	heaven	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-012
# text = Did she take your hat, Charming Billy?
1	Did	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	your	O	-	-
5	hat	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Charming	B-PER	-	-
8	Billy	I-PER	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Kentucky_In_The_Morning-010
# text = Oh I can't recall how I came to go by Kentucky shores on the Ohio
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	can	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	recall	O	-	-
7	how	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	came	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	go	O	-	-
12	by	O	-	-
13	Kentucky	B-LOC	-	-
14	shores	O	-	-
15	on	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	Ohio	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Spanish_Pipedream-012
# text = Try and find Jesus on your own
1	Try	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	find	O	-	-
4	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	own	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Ben_Dewberry_s_Final_Run-006
# text = Ben Dewberry said before he died
1	Ben	B-PER	-	-
2	Dewberry	I-PER	-	-
3	said	O	-	-
4	before	O	-	-
5	he	O	-	-
6	died	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_One_s_On_The_Way-024
# text = Here in Topeka, the flies are a-buzzing
1	Here	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	Topeka	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	flies	O	-	-
7	are	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	buzzing	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Julianna_Calm_Down
# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Julianna_Calm_Down-001
# text = Julianna, calm down
1	Julianna	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	calm	O	-	-
4	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_Keeper_of_the_Flame-020
# text = But I swear to God
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	swear	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Good_Time-047
# text = Head for that Waffle House way across town
1	Head	O	-	-
2	for	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	Waffle	B-ORG	-	-
5	House	I-ORG	-	-
6	way	O	-	-
7	across	O	-	-
8	town	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_Who_s_Gonna_Fill_Their_Shoes-023
# text = Old Jerry Lee and Charlie
1	Old	O	-	-
2	Jerry	B-PER	-	-
3	Lee	I-PER	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Charlie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Every_Little_Honky_Tonk_Bar-003
# text = Stool holds the fool that pours the whiskey on his broken heart
1	Stool	B-PER	-	-
2	holds	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	fool	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	pours	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	whiskey	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	his	O	-	-
11	broken	O	-	-
12	heart	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_The_Fields_Have_Turned_Brown-006
# text = "Remember that love for God can be found"
1	"	O	-	-
2	Remember	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	love	O	-	-
5	for	O	-	-
6	God	B-PER	-	-
7	can	O	-	-
8	be	O	-	-
9	found	O	-	-
10	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dixie_On_My_Mind-002
# text = The way they did in sweet home Alabam'
1	The	O	-	-
2	way	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	did	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	sweet	O	-	-
7	home	O	-	-
8	Alabam	B-LOC	-	-
9	'	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Hello_Darlin_-011
# text = Thank you, Darlin', may God bless you and each step you take
1	Thank	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Darlin	0	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	may	O	-	-
8	God	O	-	-
9	bless	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	each	O	-	-
13	step	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	take	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Bandit-005
# text = Bandit, you're reckless, and you live much too hard
1	Bandit	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	re	O	-	-
6	reckless	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	live	O	-	-
11	much	O	-	-
12	too	O	-	-
13	hard	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Shenandoah-007
# text = Missouri, she's a mighty river
1	Missouri	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	she	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	mighty	O	-	-
8	river	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-028
# text = La da da la me and Bobby McGee (Hey, ho!)
1	La	O	-	-
2	da	O	-	-
3	da	O	-	-
4	la	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
8	McGee	I-PER	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Hey	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	ho	O	-	-
13	!	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Don_t_You_Think_This_Outlaw_Bit_s_Done_Got_out_of_Hand-004
# text = New York sent a posse down like I ain't never seen
1	New	B-LOC	-	-
2	York	I-LOC	-	-
3	sent	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	posse	O	-	-
6	down	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	ain	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	never	O	-	-
13	seen	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__The_Conversation-029
# text = How he sure did love Miss Audrey and raisin' hell
1	How	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	sure	O	-	-
4	did	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-
6	Miss	B-PER	-	-
7	Audrey	I-PER	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	raisin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	hell	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Sylvia_s_Mother-002
# text = "Sylvia's busy, too busy to come to the phone"
1	"	O	-	-
2	Sylvia	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	busy	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	too	O	-	-
8	busy	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	come	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	phone	O	-	-
14	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tammy_Wynette_My_Elusive_Dreams-012
# text = G: Then I heard of work in Nashville
1	G	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Then	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	heard	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	work	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Nashville	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-021
# text = Holdin' Bobby's body next to mine
1	Holdin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
4	'	I-PER	-	-
5	s	I-PER	-	-
6	body	O	-	-
7	next	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	mine	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Small_Town_Southern_Man-037
# text = 'Cause God has a place in Heaven
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	God	B-PER	-	-
4	has	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	place	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Heaven	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Patsy_Cline_Come_on_In_And_Make_Yourself_at_Home_-019
# text = And I knew right then from God I'd never roam
1	And	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	knew	O	-	-
4	right	O	-	-
5	then	O	-	-
6	from	O	-	-
7	God	B-PER	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	d	O	-	-
11	never	O	-	-
12	roam	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Me_and_Bobby_McGee-019
# text = Then somewhere near Salinas, Lord, I let her slip away
1	Then	O	-	-
2	somewhere	O	-	-
3	near	O	-	-
4	Salinas	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Lord	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	let	O	-	-
10	her	O	-	-
11	slip	O	-	-
12	away	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_Brown_s_Ferry_Blues-020
# text = I got a girl in the Cumberland Gap
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	girl	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Cumberland	B-LOC	-	-
8	Gap	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Tomorrow_Night_In_Baltimore-019
# text = God' if I have to crawl, I'm gonna be there tomorrow night in Baltimore
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	'	0	-	-
3	if	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	have	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	crawl	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	gonna	O	-	-
13	be	O	-	-
14	there	O	-	-
15	tomorrow	O	-	-
16	night	O	-	-
17	in	O	-	-
18	Baltimore	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_My_Little_Home_Down_In_New_Orleans-021
# text = And that's my little old home down in New Orleans
1	And	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	little	O	-	-
7	old	O	-	-
8	home	O	-	-
9	down	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	New	B-LOC	-	-
12	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Patsy_Cline_Faded_Love-006
# text = As Heaven would miss the stars above
1	As	O	-	-
2	Heaven	B-LOC	-	-
3	would	O	-	-
4	miss	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	stars	O	-	-
7	above	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-025
# text = Schefferville, Jacksonville, Waterville, Costa Rica
1	Schefferville	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Jacksonville	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Waterville	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Costa	B-LOC	-	-
8	Rica	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_I_m_a_Man_of_Constant_Sorrow-024
# text = I'll meet you on God's golden shore
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	meet	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	God	B-PER	-	-
8	'	I-PER	-	-
9	s	I-PER	-	-
10	golden	O	-	-
11	shore	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_I_Can_Still_Make_Cheyenne-025
# text = And in that Cheyenne wind he could still hear her say
1	And	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	Cheyenne	B-LOC	-	-
5	wind	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	could	O	-	-
8	still	O	-	-
9	hear	O	-	-
10	her	O	-	-
11	say	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dinosaur-019
# text = It looks like they've turned the Longhorn into a spaceship
1	It	O	-	-
2	looks	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	they	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	ve	O	-	-
7	turned	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Longhorn	B-ORG	-	-
10	into	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	spaceship	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Porter_Wagoner_Committed_To_Parkview-012
# text = Who have withdrawn from the rat race and committed to Parkview
1	Who	O	-	-
2	have	O	-	-
3	withdrawn	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	rat	O	-	-
7	race	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	committed	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	Parkview	B-ORG	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks
# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-001
# text = Run, oh Molly run; run, oh Molly run
1	Run	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	oh	O	-	-
4	Molly	B-PER	-	-
5	run	O	-	-
6	;	O	-	-
7	run	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	oh	O	-	-
10	Molly	B-PER	-	-
11	run	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_Who_s_Gonna_Fill_Their_Shoes-016
# text = And the Wabash Cannonball
1	And	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Wabash	B-ORG	-	-
4	Cannonball	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_How_Far_to_Little_Rock-003
# text = Ah, could you tell me how far it is to Little Rock?
1	Ah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	could	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	tell	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	how	O	-	-
8	far	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	is	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	Little	B-LOC	-	-
13	Rock	I-LOC	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-027
# text = Can she make a pudding well, Charming Billy?
1	Can	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	make	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	pudding	O	-	-
6	well	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Charming	B-PER	-	-
9	Billy	I-PER	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dinosaur-016
# text = Then a little old Jim Beam and we'd get right
1	Then	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	little	O	-	-
4	old	O	-	-
5	Jim	B-ORG	-	-
6	Beam	I-ORG	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	we	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	d	O	-	-
11	get	O	-	-
12	right	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina-012
# text = Corrine, Corrina is it true what they say?
1	Corrine	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Corrina	B-PER	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	true	O	-	-
7	what	O	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	say	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Memphis_Yodel-012
# text = Lord, I love you, Memphis
1	Lord	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	love	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Memphis	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Gator-032
# text = Watch out, boys, old Smokey's in the Okefenokee
1	Watch	O	-	-
2	out	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	boys	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	old	O	-	-
7	Smokey	B-PER	-	-
8	'	0	-	-
9	s	0	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Okefenokee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kenny_Rogers_Coward_Of_The_County-016
# text = One day while he was working, the Gatlin boys came calling
1	One	O	-	-
2	day	O	-	-
3	while	O	-	-
4	he	O	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	working	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	the	B-ORG	-	-
9	Gatlin	I-ORG	-	-
10	boys	I-ORG	-	-
11	came	O	-	-
12	calling	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Golden_Rocket-024
# text = And this Golden Rocket is rollin' my blues away
1	And	O	-	-
2	this	O	-	-
3	Golden	B-ORG	-	-
4	Rocket	I-ORG	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	rollin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	blues	O	-	-
10	away	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-024
# text = I've been to Louisville, Nashville, Knoxville, Ombabika
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Louisville	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Nashville	B-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Knoxville	B-LOC	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Ombabika	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Pancho_and_Lefty-025
# text = The day they laid poor Pancho low
1	The	O	-	-
2	day	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	laid	O	-	-
5	poor	O	-	-
6	Pancho	B-PER	-	-
7	low	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_That_Summer-006
# text = Wheat fields as far as I could see
1	Wheat	0	-	-
2	fields	0	-	-
3	as	O	-	-
4	far	O	-	-
5	as	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	could	O	-	-
8	see	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Rachel
# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Rachel-001
# text = Rachel pays good money for the clothes she wears
1	Rachel	B-PER	-	-
2	pays	O	-	-
3	good	O	-	-
4	money	O	-	-
5	for	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	clothes	O	-	-
8	she	O	-	-
9	wears	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Flatt_Scruggs_The_Ballad_of_Jed_Clampett-011
# text = Now its time to say good-bye to Jed and all his kin
1	Now	O	-	-
2	its	O	-	-
3	time	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	say	O	-	-
6	good	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	bye	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	Jed	B-PER	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	all	O	-	-
13	his	O	-	-
14	kin	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Reba_McEntire_The_Night_The_Lights_Went_Out_In_Georgia-004
# text = Andy Wo-Lo said hello, he said, "Hi, what's new?" and Wo said
1	Andy	B-PER	-	-
2	Wo	I-PER	-	-
3	-	I-PER	-	-
4	Lo	I-PER	-	-
5	said	O	-	-
6	hello	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	he	O	-	-
9	said	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	"	O	-	-
12	Hi	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	what	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	s	O	-	-
17	new	O	-	-
18	?	O	-	-
19	"	O	-	-
20	and	O	-	-
21	Wo	B-PER	-	-
22	said	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Kansas_City_Star-016
# text = No thanks Omaha, thanks a lot
1	No	O	-	-
2	thanks	O	-	-
3	Omaha	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	thanks	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	lot	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Jackson-014
# text = 'Cause I'm goin' to Jackson
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	goin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Jackson	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Smoke_On_The_Water-009
# text = Hirohito, ′long with Hitler, will be ridin' on a rail
1	Hirohito	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	′	O	-	-
4	long	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	Hitler	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	will	O	-	-
9	be	O	-	-
10	ridin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	on	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	rail	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Ain_t_No_Grave-049
# text = Adonai can save from the darkest nights of the soul
1	Adonai	B-PER	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	save	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	darkest	O	-	-
7	nights	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	soul	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Tequila_Sheila-005
# text = For all the damn gold in Juarez
1	For	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	damn	O	-	-
5	gold	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Juarez	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_One_Piece_at_a_Time-058
# text = Uh, yeah, Red Ryder?
1	Uh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Red	B-ORG	-	-
6	Ryder	I-ORG	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Seven_Spanish_Angels-007
# text = If they take me back to Texas
1	If	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	back	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	Texas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_Coalminer_s_Daughter-025
# text = I never thought of ever leaving Butcher Holler
1	I	O	-	-
2	never	O	-	-
3	thought	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	ever	O	-	-
6	leaving	O	-	-
7	Butcher	B-LOC	-	-
8	Holler	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miranda_Lambert_White_Liar-016
# text = With a red head named Bernice
1	With	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	red	O	-	-
4	head	O	-	-
5	named	O	-	-
6	Bernice	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Uncle_Pen-011
# text = The greatest of all was "Jenny Lynn"
1	The	O	-	-
2	greatest	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	"	O	-	-
7	Jenny	B-PER	-	-
8	Lynn	I-PER	-	-
9	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_Jackson-023
# text = Yeah, we're goin' to Jackson
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	re	O	-	-
6	goin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Jackson	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Check_Yes_Or_No-007
# text = And Emmylou got caught passing me a note
1	And	O	-	-
2	Emmylou	B-PER	-	-
3	got	O	-	-
4	caught	O	-	-
5	passing	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	note	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Pearly_Shells-019
# text = **Emailed by Donald Grasser 06/10/03
1	*	O	-	-
2	*	O	-	-
3	Emailed	O	-	-
4	by	O	-	-
5	Donald	B-PER	-	-
6	Grasser	I-PER	-	-
7	06	O	-	-
8	/	O	-	-
9	10	O	-	-
10	/	O	-	-
11	03	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-003
# text = "If you're goin' to Winnemucca, Mack, with me you can ride"
1	"	O	-	-
2	If	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	re	O	-	-
6	goin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Winnemucca	B-LOC	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Mack	B-PER	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	with	O	-	-
14	me	O	-	-
15	you	O	-	-
16	can	O	-	-
17	ride	O	-	-
18	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_How_Far_to_Little_Rock-020
# text = (Buddy, she's got a head)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Buddy	0	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	she	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	s	O	-	-
7	got	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	head	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Dixie-007
# text = Advance the flag of Dixie! Hurrah! Hurrah!
1	Advance	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	flag	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	Dixie	B-LOC	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	Hurrah	O	-	-
8	!	O	-	-
9	Hurrah	O	-	-
10	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Luckenbach_Texas_Back_to_the_Basics_of_Love_-009
# text = Got us feuding like the Hatfields and McCoys
1	Got	O	-	-
2	us	O	-	-
3	feuding	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Hatfields	B-PER	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	McCoys	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tammy_Wynette_My_Elusive_Dreams-004
# text = T: I went with you to Alabam'
1	T	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	went	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Alabam	B-LOC	-	-
9	'	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_One_s_On_The_Way-021
# text = The girls in New York City, they all march for women's lib
1	The	O	-	-
2	girls	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	New	B-LOC	-	-
5	York	I-LOC	-	-
6	City	I-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	all	O	-	-
10	march	O	-	-
11	for	O	-	-
12	women	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	s	O	-	-
15	lib	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Drunkard_s_Son-016
# text = That Jesus had been there that day
1	That	O	-	-
2	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
3	had	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	there	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	day	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_A_Very_Merry_Christmas-011
# text = Ol' Santa Claus might be watching you
1	Ol	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	Santa	B-PER	-	-
4	Claus	I-PER	-	-
5	might	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	watching	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_Who_s_Gonna_Fill_Their_Shoes-020
# text = Blue Suede Shoes and Elvis
1	Blue	0	-	-
2	Suede	0	-	-
3	Shoes	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Elvis	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Whiskey_Bent_And_Hell_Bound-021
# text = Yeah, old Hank's songs always make me feel low down
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	old	O	-	-
4	Hank	B-PER	-	-
5	'	I-PER	-	-
6	s	I-PER	-	-
7	songs	O	-	-
8	always	O	-	-
9	make	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	feel	O	-	-
12	low	O	-	-
13	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_All_I_Want_for_Christmas_Is_My_Daddy-009
# text = Tell old Santa Claus forget about those presents
1	Tell	O	-	-
2	old	O	-	-
3	Santa	B-PER	-	-
4	Claus	I-PER	-	-
5	forget	O	-	-
6	about	O	-	-
7	those	O	-	-
8	presents	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Stanley_Brothers_The_Fields_Have_Turned_Brown-003
# text = Remember that God will always watch over you
1	Remember	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	God	B-PER	-	-
4	will	O	-	-
5	always	O	-	-
6	watch	O	-	-
7	over	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Made_In_Japan-009
# text = In the dark of night we would lay on Tokyo Bay
1	In	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	dark	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	night	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	would	O	-	-
8	lay	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	Tokyo	B-LOC	-	-
11	Bay	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-028
# text = Idaho, Jellico, Argentina, Diamantina
1	Idaho	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Jellico	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Argentina	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Diamantina	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-006
# text = Oh, where does she live, Charming Billy?
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	where	O	-	-
4	does	O	-	-
5	she	O	-	-
6	live	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Charming	B-PER	-	-
9	Billy	I-PER	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Big_In_Vegas-016
# text = Honky tonk and smokey bar, in Vegas
1	Honky	O	-	-
2	tonk	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	smokey	O	-	-
5	bar	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Vegas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Guitar_Man-003
# text = By sundown I'd left Kingston
1	By	O	-	-
2	sundown	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	left	O	-	-
7	Kingston	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Union_Dixie-006
# text = We'll all go down to Dixie, away, away!
1	We	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	go	O	-	-
6	down	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Dixie	B-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	away	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	away	O	-	-
13	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Alan_Jackson_Where_I_Come_From-019
# text = Well, I was headin' home on 65, somewhere around Kentucky
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	headin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	home	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	65	B-LOC	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	somewhere	O	-	-
12	around	O	-	-
13	Kentucky	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Trudy-017
# text = I was rakin' in chips like Grant took Richmond till big John Lee come strollin' in
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	rakin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	chips	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	Grant	B-PER	-	-
9	took	O	-	-
10	Richmond	B-LOC	-	-
11	till	O	-	-
12	big	O	-	-
13	John	B-PER	-	-
14	Lee	I-PER	-	-
15	come	O	-	-
16	strollin	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-
18	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Away_Out_On_The_Mountain-002
# text = Kiss Susie Jane goodbye at the fountain
1	Kiss	O	-	-
2	Susie	B-PER	-	-
3	Jane	I-PER	-	-
4	goodbye	O	-	-
5	at	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	fountain	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tammy_Wynette_Two_Story_House-009
# text = (Tammy)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Tammy	B-PER	-	-
3	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-040
# text = They sell Tennessee ham
1	They	O	-	-
2	sell	O	-	-
3	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-
4	ham	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Carter_Boys-023
# text = The only thing we feared was the Lord
1	The	O	-	-
2	only	O	-	-
3	thing	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	feared	O	-	-
6	was	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	Lord	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Me_and_Bobby_McGee-014
# text = Good enough for me and my Bobby McGee.
1	Good	O	-	-
2	enough	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
8	McGee	I-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Glen_Campbell_Galveston-005
# text = When I left Galveston
1	When	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	left	O	-	-
4	Galveston	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_I_m_Ready_To_Go_Home-016
# text = Where the children of God will never part
1	Where	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	children	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	will	O	-	-
7	never	O	-	-
8	part	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Kaw_Liga-007
# text = Poor ol' Kaw-Liga, he don't know what he missed
1	Poor	O	-	-
2	ol	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
5	-	I-PER	-	-
6	Liga	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	he	O	-	-
9	don	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	know	O	-	-
13	what	O	-	-
14	he	O	-	-
15	missed	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_Take_Me-011
# text = Darlin', if you would just show a sign of love
1	Darlin	0	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	if	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	would	O	-	-
7	just	O	-	-
8	show	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	sign	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	love	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Red_Hot_Gal_Of_Mine-006
# text = Rosie cheeks eyes of brown the hottest little baby in this town
1	Rosie	0	-	-
2	cheeks	O	-	-
3	eyes	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	brown	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	hottest	O	-	-
8	little	O	-	-
9	baby	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	this	O	-	-
12	town	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dinosaur-007
# text = And we don't all get into Donna Summer
1	And	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	get	O	-	-
8	into	O	-	-
9	Donna	B-PER	-	-
10	Summer	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus-004
# text = And as he was tried they heard Steven cry aloud
1	And	O	-	-
2	as	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	tried	O	-	-
6	they	O	-	-
7	heard	O	-	-
8	Steven	B-PER	-	-
9	cry	O	-	-
10	aloud	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Hello_Darlin_-016
# text = Come back, Darlin', I'll be waitin' for you
1	Come	O	-	-
2	back	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Darlin	0	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	ll	O	-	-
10	be	O	-	-
11	waitin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	for	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_Charlie_s_Angel-005
# text = And I'm holding Charlie's Angel tonight
1	And	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	holding	O	-	-
6	Charlie	B-PER	-	-
7	'	I-PER	-	-
8	s	I-PER	-	-
9	Angel	I-PER	-	-
10	tonight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Miss_Molly-005
# text = Oh, Oh, Oh, me, oh, my Miss Molly I'm in love with you
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Oh	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Oh	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	oh	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	my	O	-	-
12	Miss	O	-	-
13	Molly	B-PER	-	-
14	I	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	m	O	-	-
17	in	O	-	-
18	love	O	-	-
19	with	O	-	-
20	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_In_The_Pines-002
# text = Went down that Georgia line
1	Went	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	Georgia	B-LOC	-	-
5	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Back_Up_And_Push-003
# text = Well, it's old Satan, right there a waiting
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	old	O	-	-
7	Satan	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	right	O	-	-
10	there	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	waiting	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Virginia_s_Bloody_Soil-004
# text = It took to down secession on Virginia's bloody soil
1	It	O	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	down	O	-	-
5	secession	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
8	'	O	I-LOC	-
9	s	O	I-LOC	-
10	bloody	O	-	-
11	soil	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_We_Buried_Her_Beneath_the_Willows-007
# text = God needed her to sing in heaven
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	needed	O	-	-
3	her	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	sing	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	heaven	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Streets_Of_Bakersfield-012
# text = Ever walked the streets of Bakersfield?
1	Ever	O	-	-
2	walked	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	streets	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	Bakersfield	B-LOC	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_River_Of_Jordan-013
# text = So he went right down to the River Of Jordan
1	So	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	went	O	-	-
4	right	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	River	0	-	-
9	Of	0	-	-
10	Jordan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Jody_and_the_Kid-008
# text = Looky yonder there goes Jody and the kid
1	Looky	O	-	-
2	yonder	O	-	-
3	there	O	-	-
4	goes	O	-	-
5	Jody	B-PER	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	kid	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-010
# text = Out in California where Molly done as she pleased
1	Out	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	California	B-LOC	-	-
4	where	O	-	-
5	Molly	B-PER	-	-
6	done	O	-	-
7	as	O	-	-
8	she	O	-	-
9	pleased	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tammy_Wynette_My_Elusive_Dreams-021
# text = T: And still I won't let you go on alone
1	T	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	And	O	-	-
4	still	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	won	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	let	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	go	O	-	-
12	on	O	-	-
13	alone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_Blue_Kentucky_Girl-012
# text = That's good enough for this blue Kentucky Girl
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	good	O	-	-
5	enough	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	this	O	-	-
8	blue	O	-	-
9	Kentucky	0	-	-
10	Girl	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Detroit_City-008
# text = Homefolks think I'm big in Detroit City
1	Homefolks	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	big	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Detroit	B-LOC	-	-
9	City	0	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Paradise-019
# text = Let my soul roll on up to the Rochester Dam
1	Let	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	soul	O	-	-
4	roll	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Rochester	B-LOC	-	-
10	Dam	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-017
# text = Give old Tenbrooks the bridle, let old Tenbrooks run
1	Give	O	-	-
2	old	O	-	-
3	Tenbrooks	B-PER	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	bridle	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	let	O	-	-
8	old	O	-	-
9	Tenbrooks	B-PER	-	-
10	run	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_King_Is_Gone_So_Are_You_
# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_King_Is_Gone_So_Are_You_-001
# text = Last night I broke the seal on a Jim Beam decanter
1	Last	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	broke	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	seal	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	Jim	B-ORG	-	-
10	Beam	I-ORG	-	-
11	decanter	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_When_You_re_Hot_You_re_Hot-029
# text = "Ninety days, Jerry, when you hot, you hot"
1	"	O	-	-
2	Ninety	O	-	-
3	days	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Jerry	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	when	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	hot	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	hot	O	-	-
13	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Buck_Owens_Home_on_Christmas_Day-010
# text = Well, Johnny's coming home from the army
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	coming	O	-	-
7	home	O	-	-
8	from	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	army	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Dinosaur-019
# text = It looks like they've turned the Longhorn into a spaceship
1	It	O	-	-
2	looks	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	they	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	ve	O	-	-
7	turned	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Longhorn	B-ORG	-	-
10	into	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	spaceship	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Fall_of_Charleston-025
# text = How are you, neutral Johnny Bull?
1	How	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	neutral	O	-	-
6	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
7	Bull	I-PER	-	-
8	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-014
# text = Wichita, Tulsa, Ottawa, Oklahoma, Tampa, Panama, Mattawa, La Paloma
1	Wichita	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Tulsa	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Ottawa	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Oklahoma	B-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Tampa	B-LOC	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Panama	B-LOC	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Mattawa	B-LOC	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	La	B-LOC	-	-
16	Paloma	I-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-John_Prine_Clay_Pigeons
# sent_id = lyrics-John_Prine_Clay_Pigeons-001
# text = I'm goin' down to the Greyhound Station, gonna buy a ticket to ride
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	goin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	down	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Greyhound	B-LOC	-	-
10	Station	I-LOC	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	gonna	O	-	-
13	buy	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	ticket	O	-	-
16	to	O	-	-
17	ride	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Abilene
# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Abilene-001
# text = Abilene, Abilene
1	Abilene	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Abilene	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Kentucky_Waltz-008
# text = In that beautiful Kentucky waltz
1	In	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	beautiful	O	-	-
4	Kentucky	B-LOC	-	-
5	waltz	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_The_Fall_of_Charleston-013
# text = Babylon is fallen
1	Babylon	B-LOC	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	fallen	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Julianna_Calm_Down-036
# text = And Berta, calm down
1	And	O	-	-
2	Berta	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	calm	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-007
# text = With them windshield wipers slappin' time and Bobby clappin' hands we fin-
1	With	O	-	-
2	them	O	-	-
3	windshield	O	-	-
4	wipers	O	-	-
5	slappin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	time	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
10	clappin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	hands	O	-	-
13	we	O	-	-
14	fin	O	-	-
15	-	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mel_Tillis_That_s_Where_My_Money_Goes-002
# text = I've got a gal in Monroeville she won't dance but her sister will
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	gal	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Monroeville	B-LOC	-	-
9	she	O	-	-
10	won	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	dance	O	-	-
14	but	O	-	-
15	her	O	-	-
16	sister	O	-	-
17	will	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Steal_Away-003
# text = I was walkin’ in Savannah passed the church decayed and dimmed
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	walkin	O	-	-
4	’	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Savannah	B-LOC	-	-
7	passed	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	church	O	-	-
10	decayed	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	dimmed	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gary_Stewart_Hank_Western-018
# text = And then one night in a bar down in Lincoln
1	And	O	-	-
2	then	O	-	-
3	one	O	-	-
4	night	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	bar	O	-	-
8	down	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Lincoln	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Amos_Moses-024
# text = Well the Sheriff got wind that Amos
1	Well	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Sheriff	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	wind	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	Amos	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Pancho_and_Lefty-026
# text = Lefty split for Ohio
1	Lefty	B-PER	-	-
2	split	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	Ohio	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Guitar_Man-005
# text = I hitchhiked all the way down to Memphis
1	I	O	-	-
2	hitchhiked	O	-	-
3	all	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	way	O	-	-
6	down	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Memphis	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Blue_Danube_Waltz-013
# text = Oh, the Danube is green as the grass in the spring
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Danube	B-LOC	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	green	O	-	-
7	as	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	grass	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	spring	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_River_Of_Jordan-010
# text = And he sent for the man of God to pray
1	And	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	sent	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	man	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	God	B-PER	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	pray	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Hey_Joe
# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Hey_Joe-001
# text = Hey Joe someone stole your pearly girlie walked off with your jolly dolly
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	Joe	B-PER	-	-
3	someone	O	-	-
4	stole	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	pearly	O	-	-
7	girlie	O	-	-
8	walked	O	-	-
9	off	O	-	-
10	with	O	-	-
11	your	O	-	-
12	jolly	O	-	-
13	dolly	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Roly_Poly
# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Roly_Poly-001
# text = Roly Poly, eatin' corn and taters
1	Roly	B-PER	-	-
2	Poly	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	eatin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	corn	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	taters	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bob_Wills_Corrine_Corrina-020
# text = Goodbye Corrina, this is fare you well
1	Goodbye	O	-	-
2	Corrina	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	this	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	fare	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	well	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Luckenbach_Texas_Back_to_the_Basics_of_Love_-022
# text = With Willie and Waylon and the boys
1	With	O	-	-
2	Willie	B-PER	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	Waylon	B-PER	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	boys	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Blue_Yodel_T_For_Texas_
# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Blue_Yodel_T_For_Texas_-001
# text = T for Texas, T for Tennessee
1	T	O	-	-
2	for	O	-	-
3	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	T	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Sylvia_s_Mother-011
# text = Please, Mrs. Avery, I just want to tell
1	Please	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Mrs	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Avery	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	just	O	-	-
9	want	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	tell	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_A_Daisy_a_Day-006
# text = Honey has something gone wrong
1	Honey	0	-	-
2	has	O	-	-
3	something	O	-	-
4	gone	O	-	-
5	wrong	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Loretta_Lynn_Coal_Miner_s_Daughter-025
# text = I never thought of ever leaving Butcher Holler
1	I	O	-	-
2	never	O	-	-
3	thought	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	ever	O	-	-
6	leaving	O	-	-
7	Butcher	B-LOC	-	-
8	Holler	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_The_Streets_of_Baltimore-023
# text = Yes, my baby walks the streets of Baltimore
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	baby	O	-	-
5	walks	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	streets	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	Baltimore	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_The_Lily_of_the_Valley-013
# text = Through Jesus I shall safely reach that goal
1	Through	O	-	-
2	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	shall	O	-	-
5	safely	O	-	-
6	reach	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	goal	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_Me_And_Bobby_McGhee-006
# text = Blowin' sad while Bobby sang the blues
1	Blowin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	sad	O	-	-
4	while	O	-	-
5	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
6	sang	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	blues	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Last_Ride-045
# text = I knew that fever had you, Jack
1	I	O	-	-
2	knew	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	fever	O	-	-
5	had	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Jack	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_Two_Glasses_Joe-005
# text = He's stole her love I know but he can't stop me Joe from having just a dream or two
1	He	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	stole	O	-	-
5	her	O	-	-
6	love	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	know	O	-	-
9	but	O	-	-
10	he	O	-	-
11	can	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	t	O	-	-
14	stop	O	-	-
15	me	O	-	-
16	Joe	B-PER	-	-
17	from	O	-	-
18	having	O	-	-
19	just	O	-	-
20	a	O	-	-
21	dream	O	-	-
22	or	O	-	-
23	two	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Detroit_City-003
# text = Last night I went to sleep in Detroit City
1	Last	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	went	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	sleep	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Detroit	B-LOC	-	-
9	City	0	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Don_t_Call_Him_a_Cowboy
# sent_id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Don_t_Call_Him_a_Cowboy-001
# text = So you came from New York city
1	So	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	came	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	New	B-LOC	-	-
6	York	I-LOC	-	-
7	city	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-005
# text = After graduation Mary Anne went out
1	After	O	-	-
2	graduation	O	-	-
3	Mary	B-PER	-	-
4	Anne	I-PER	-	-
5	went	O	-	-
6	out	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Is_Anybody_Goin_to_San_Antone-017
# text = Yonder comes a truck with the US mail
1	Yonder	O	-	-
2	comes	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	truck	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	US	0	-	-
8	mail	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kitty_Wells_Paul_s_Ministry-007
# text = I counted on Judas but he proved untrue
1	I	O	-	-
2	counted	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	Judas	B-PER	-	-
5	but	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	proved	O	-	-
8	untrue	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-007
# text = Wanda looked all around this town
1	Wanda	B-PER	-	-
2	looked	O	-	-
3	all	O	-	-
4	around	O	-	-
5	this	O	-	-
6	town	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gram_Parsons_Kiss_the_Children-017
# text = Is like the road sign pointing straight to satan's cage
1	Is	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	road	O	-	-
5	sign	O	-	-
6	pointing	O	-	-
7	straight	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	satan	B-PER	-	-
10	'	I-PER	-	-
11	s	I-PER	-	-
12	cage	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus-016
# text = I believed he smiled and said "Steven welcome home"
1	I	O	-	-
2	believed	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	smiled	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	said	O	-	-
7	"	O	-	-
8	Steven	B-PER	-	-
9	welcome	O	-	-
10	home	O	-	-
11	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Luckenbach_Texas_Back_to_the_Basics_of_Love_-024
# text = Between Hank Williams' pain songs
1	Between	O	-	-
2	Hank	B-PER	-	-
3	Williams	I-PER	-	-
4	'	I-PER	-	-
5	pain	O	-	-
6	songs	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lefty_Frizzell_That_s_The_Way_Love_Goes-010
# text = That's the music God made
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	music	O	-	-
6	God	B-PER	-	-
7	made	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Golden_Rocket
# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_The_Golden_Rocket-001
# text = From old Montana down to Alabam'
1	From	O	-	-
2	old	O	-	-
3	Montana	B-LOC	-	-
4	down	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Alabam	B-LOC	-	-
7	'	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Travelin_Soldier-021
# text = In California then Vietnam
1	In	O	-	-
2	California	B-LOC	-	-
3	then	O	-	-
4	Vietnam	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Uptown_Poker_Club-043
# text = And Leroy quit takin' em off the bottom of the deck son I tell ya that's rough
1	And	O	-	-
2	Leroy	B-PER	-	-
3	quit	O	-	-
4	takin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	em	O	-	-
7	off	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	bottom	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	deck	O	-	-
13	son	O	-	-
14	I	O	-	-
15	tell	O	-	-
16	ya	O	-	-
17	that	O	-	-
18	'	O	-	-
19	s	O	-	-
20	rough	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_The_Jogger-017
# text = I'm LA bound and I don't slow down for dead raccoons or joggers
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	LA	B-LOC	-	-
5	bound	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	don	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	slow	O	-	-
12	down	O	-	-
13	for	O	-	-
14	dead	O	-	-
15	raccoons	O	-	-
16	or	O	-	-
17	joggers	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kris_Kristofferson_Casey_s_Last_Ride-013
# text = Casey leaves the underground and stops inside the Golden Crown
1	Casey	B-PER	-	-
2	leaves	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	underground	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	stops	O	-	-
7	inside	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Golden	B-LOC	-	-
10	Crown	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Drinking_Wine_Spo_Dee_O_Dee-013
# text = Well, I was standing on Bourbon Street in Willie's den
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	standing	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	Bourbon	B-LOC	-	-
8	Street	I-LOC	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Willie	B-PER	-	-
11	'	I-PER	-	-
12	s	I-PER	-	-
13	den	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Nashville_Is_A_Groovy_Little_Town-012
# text = And I'd get up and sing for all those folks at jody's bar
1	And	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	d	O	-	-
5	get	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	sing	O	-	-
9	for	O	-	-
10	all	O	-	-
11	those	O	-	-
12	folks	O	-	-
13	at	O	-	-
14	jody	B-PER	-	-
15	'	I-PER	-	-
16	s	I-PER	-	-
17	bar	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_Kentucky-005
# text = Kentucky, I miss the voices singing in the silvery moonlight
1	Kentucky	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	miss	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	voices	O	-	-
7	singing	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	silvery	O	-	-
11	moonlight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash__Ghost_Riders_in_the_Sky-018
# text = Tryin' to catch the Devil's herd, across these endless skies"
1	Tryin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	catch	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Devil	B-PER	-	-
7	'	I-PER	-	-
8	s	I-PER	-	-
9	herd	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	across	O	-	-
12	these	O	-	-
13	endless	O	-	-
14	skies	O	-	-
15	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Gator-021
# text = That sheriff he'd soon mess around with the devil
1	That	O	-	-
2	sheriff	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	soon	O	-	-
7	mess	O	-	-
8	around	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	devil	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lefty_Frizzell_I_Love_You_A_Thousand_Ways-016
# text = Darlin', please wait, please wait until I'm free
1	Darlin	0	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	please	O	-	-
5	wait	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	please	O	-	-
8	wait	O	-	-
9	until	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	m	O	-	-
13	free	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lefty_Frizzell_Saginaw_Michigan-016
# text = I hit the biggest strike in Klondike history"
1	I	O	-	-
2	hit	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	biggest	O	-	-
5	strike	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Klondike	0	-	-
8	history	O	-	-
9	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_Who_s_Gonna_Fill_Their_Shoes-011
# text = Or Hello Darlin'
1	Or	O	-	-
2	Hello	O	-	-
3	Darlin	0	-	-
4	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Kaw_Liga-010
# text = Poor ol' Kaw-Liga, you don't know what you what miss
1	Poor	O	-	-
2	ol	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
5	-	I-PER	-	-
6	Liga	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	don	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	know	O	-	-
13	what	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	what	O	-	-
16	miss	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_Little_Moses-003
# text = And Pharaoh's little daughter stepped down in the water
1	And	O	-	-
2	Pharaoh	B-PER	-	-
3	'	I-PER	-	-
4	s	I-PER	-	-
5	little	O	-	-
6	daughter	O	-	-
7	stepped	O	-	-
8	down	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	water	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_One_I_Loved_Back_Then_The_Corvette_Song_
# sent_id = lyrics-George_Jones_The_One_I_Loved_Back_Then_The_Corvette_Song_-001
# text = I stopped off at the Quicksack
1	I	O	-	-
2	stopped	O	-	-
3	off	O	-	-
4	at	O	-	-
5	the	0	-	-
6	Quicksack	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_Almost_Persuaded-007
# text = Jesus invites you, angels are lingering near
1	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
2	invites	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	angels	O	-	-
6	are	O	-	-
7	lingering	O	-	-
8	near	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_The_Conversation-021
# text = Don't you know he would, Watasha
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	know	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	would	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Watasha	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_I_ve_Been_Everywhere-032
# text = Larimore, Admore, Haverstraw, Chatanika
1	Larimore	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Admore	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Haverstraw	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Chatanika	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Is_Anybody_Goin_to_San_Antone-009
# text = Is anybody goin to San Antone
1	Is	O	-	-
2	anybody	O	-	-
3	goin	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	San	B-LOC	-	-
6	Antone	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_All_My_Ex_s_Live_In_Texas-002
# text = And Texas is the place I'd dearly love to be
1	And	O	-	-
2	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	place	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	d	O	-	-
9	dearly	O	-	-
10	love	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	be	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Roger_Miller_South-011
# text = She was born in '52, she finished in a Mississippi school
1	She	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	born	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	52	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	she	O	-	-
9	finished	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	Mississippi	B-LOC	-	-
13	school	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Kaw_Liga-009
# text = Kaw-Liga's got a poor ol' wooden head
1	Kaw	B-PER	-	-
2	-	I-PER	-	-
3	Liga	I-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	poor	O	-	-
9	ol	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	wooden	O	-	-
12	head	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Ballad_Of_Hank_Williams-047
# text = Don, you know, you used to work for me one time
1	Don	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	used	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	work	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	one	O	-	-
13	time	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dolly_Parton_You_Can_t_Make_Old_Friends-016
# text = When Saint Peter opens the gate
1	When	O	-	-
2	Saint	B-PER	-	-
3	Peter	I-PER	-	-
4	opens	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	gate	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_The_Conversation-029
# text = How he sure did love Miss Audrey and raisin' hell
1	How	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	sure	O	-	-
4	did	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-
6	Miss	B-PER	-	-
7	Audrey	I-PER	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	raisin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	hell	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Uptown_Poker_Club
# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_The_Uptown_Poker_Club-001
# text = Well now Bill Jackson went to poor ol' Dub
1	Well	O	-	-
2	now	O	-	-
3	Bill	B-PER	-	-
4	Jackson	I-PER	-	-
5	went	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	poor	O	-	-
8	ol	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	Dub	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_I_See_Jesus-018
# text = Work is over now I'm coming to Thee
1	Work	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	over	O	-	-
4	now	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	coming	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	Thee	0	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Johnny_Cash_A_Boy_Named_Sue-022
# text = Well, it was Gatlinburg in mid-July
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	Gatlinburg	B-LOC	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	mid	O	-	-
8	-	O	-	-
9	July	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bill_Monroe_Molly_and_Tenbrooks-011
# text = Come back to old Kentucky, got beat with all ease
1	Come	O	-	-
2	back	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	old	O	-	-
5	Kentucky	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	got	O	-	-
8	beat	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	all	O	-	-
11	ease	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Sixteen_Tons-007
# text = St Peter don't you call me I can't go
1	St	B-PER	-	-
2	Peter	I-PER	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	call	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	can	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	go	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-050
# text = Good, let's go for a ride Earl
1	Good	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	let	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	go	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	ride	O	-	-
10	Earl	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jimmie_Rodgers_Ben_Dewberry_s_Final_Run-025
# text = Ben never lived to tell that awful tale
1	Ben	B-PER	-	-
2	never	O	-	-
3	lived	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	tell	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	awful	O	-	-
8	tale	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Chicks_Goodbye_Earl-008
# text = And all she found was Earl
1	And	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	she	O	-	-
4	found	O	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	Earl	B-PER	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_Filipino_Baby
# sent_id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_Filipino_Baby-001
# text = When the warship's left Manila sailing proudly o'er the sea
1	When	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	warship	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	left	O	-	-
7	Manila	B-LOC	-	-
8	sailing	O	-	-
9	proudly	O	-	-
10	o	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	er	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	sea	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Big_City-017
# text = Hey, Big City, turn me loose and set me free
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Big	B-LOC	-	-
4	City	I-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	turn	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	loose	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	set	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	free	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Okie_From_Muskogee-008
# text = Like the hippies out in San Francisco do
1	Like	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	hippies	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	San	B-LOC	-	-
7	Francisco	I-LOC	-	-
8	do	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Shotgun_Willie
# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Shotgun_Willie-001
# text = Shotgun Willie sits around in his underwear
1	Shotgun	B-PER	-	-
2	Willie	I-PER	-	-
3	sits	O	-	-
4	around	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	his	O	-	-
7	underwear	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Willie_Nelson_Pancho_And_Lefty-009
# text = Pancho was a bandit boy
1	Pancho	B-PER	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	bandit	O	-	-
5	boy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_It_s_All_Going_to_Pot-030
# text = When I caught her makin' eyes at Merle
1	When	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	caught	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	makin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	eyes	O	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	Merle	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Garth_Brooks_Unanswered_Prayers-022
# text = Some of God's greatest gifts are unanswered prayers
1	Some	O	-	-
2	of	O	-	-
3	God	B-PER	-	-
4	'	I-PER	-	-
5	s	I-PER	-	-
6	greatest	O	-	-
7	gifts	O	-	-
8	are	O	-	-
9	unanswered	O	-	-
10	prayers	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Louvin_Brothers_The_Christian_Life-005
# text = I won't lose a friend by heeding God's call
1	I	O	-	-
2	won	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	lose	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	friend	O	-	-
8	by	O	-	-
9	heeding	O	-	-
10	God	B-PER	-	-
11	'	I-PER	-	-
12	s	I-PER	-	-
13	call	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Lonesome_On_ry_and_Mean-004
# text = And down to New Orleans
1	And	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	New	B-LOC	-	-
5	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Bare_Marie_Laveau-029
# text = Then Marie started mumbling her fangs started gnashing
1	Then	O	-	-
2	Marie	B-PER	-	-
3	started	O	-	-
4	mumbling	O	-	-
5	her	O	-	-
6	fangs	O	-	-
7	started	O	-	-
8	gnashing	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__Born_To_Boogie-012
# text = I met Elvis and Marilyn and Johnny B. Goode
1	I	O	-	-
2	met	O	-	-
3	Elvis	B-PER	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Marilyn	B-PER	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
8	B	I-PER	-	-
9	.	I-PER	-	-
10	Goode	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Merle_Haggard_Are_the_Good_Times_Really_Over_I_Wish_a_Buck_Was_Still_Silver_-004
# text = And before the Vietnam War came along
1	And	O	-	-
2	before	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Vietnam	0	-	-
5	War	O	-	-
6	came	O	-	-
7	along	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Carrying_Your_Love_With_Me-007
# text = West Virginia down to Tennessee
1	West	B-LOC	-	-
2	Virginia	I-LOC	-	-
3	down	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Williams_Jr__All_My_Rowdy_Friends_Have_Settled_Down_-012
# text = And Waylon's staying home and loving Jessi more these days
1	And	O	-	-
2	Waylon	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	staying	O	-	-
6	home	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	loving	O	-	-
9	Jessi	B-PER	-	-
10	more	O	-	-
11	these	O	-	-
12	days	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Reed_Big_Daddy-009
# text = Big Daddy's Alabamy bound
1	Big	B-PER	-	-
2	Daddy	I-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	Alabamy	B-LOC	-	-
6	bound	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Kentucky_In_The_Morning-009
# text = Kentucky in the morning
1	Kentucky	B-LOC	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	morning	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_Dangerous_Dan_McGrew-053
# text = While the man from the creeks lay clutched to the breast of the lady that's known as Lou
1	While	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	man	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	creeks	O	-	-
7	lay	O	-	-
8	clutched	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	breast	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	lady	O	-	-
15	that	O	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	s	O	-	-
18	known	O	-	-
19	as	O	-	-
20	Lou	B-PER	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Hello_Darlin_
# sent_id = lyrics-Conway_Twitty_Hello_Darlin_-001
# text = Hello Darlin', nice to see you, it's been a long time
1	Hello	O	-	-
2	Darlin	0	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	nice	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	see	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	been	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	long	O	-	-
16	time	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_The_Conversation-031
# text = To the stories only Hank could tell
1	To	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	stories	O	-	-
4	only	O	-	-
5	Hank	B-PER	-	-
6	could	O	-	-
7	tell	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Strait_Give_It_Away-006
# text = That night in Frisco Bay
1	That	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	Frisco	B-LOC	-	-
5	Bay	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Carter_Family_My_Clinch_Mountain_Home-002
# text = Many years ago we parted, my little Ruth and I
1	Many	O	-	-
2	years	O	-	-
3	ago	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	parted	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	little	O	-	-
9	Ruth	B-PER	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Hadacol_Boogie-005
# text = The Hadacol Boogie
1	The	0	-	-
2	Hadacol	O	-	-
3	Boogie	0	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Waylon_Jennings_Luckenbach_Texas_Back_to_the_Basics_of_Love_-026
# text = Out in Luckenbach, Texas there ain't nobody feelin' no pain
1	Out	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	Luckenbach	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
6	there	O	-	-
7	ain	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	t	O	-	-
10	nobody	O	-	-
11	feelin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	no	O	-	-
14	pain	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Hank_Snow_He_ll_Understand_and_Say_Well_Done-006
# text = Hung on the cross He was God's only son
1	Hung	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	cross	O	-	-
5	He	O	-	-
6	was	O	-	-
7	God	B-PER	-	-
8	'	I-PER	-	-
9	s	I-PER	-	-
10	only	O	-	-
11	son	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ernest_Tubb_Two_Glasses_Joe-010
# text = And this is that you know so fill two glasses Joe and leave me here alone to cry
1	And	O	-	-
2	this	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	know	O	-	-
7	so	O	-	-
8	fill	O	-	-
9	two	O	-	-
10	glasses	O	-	-
11	Joe	B-PER	-	-
12	and	O	-	-
13	leave	O	-	-
14	me	O	-	-
15	here	O	-	-
16	alone	O	-	-
17	to	O	-	-
18	cry	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jerry_Lee_Lewis_Billy_Boy-048
# text = Is she fit to be a wife, Charming Billy?
1	Is	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	fit	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	wife	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Charming	B-PER	-	-
10	Billy	I-PER	-	-
11	?	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Margie_s_At_The_Lincoln_Park_Inn
# sent_id = lyrics-Tom_T_Hall_Margie_s_At_The_Lincoln_Park_Inn-001
# text = My name's in the paper where I took the Boy Scouts to hike
1	My	O	-	-
2	name	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	paper	O	-	-
8	where	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	took	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Boy	B-ORG	-	-
13	Scouts	I-ORG	-	-
14	to	O	-	-
15	hike	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charley_Pride_Lord_Build_Me_A_Cabin_In_Glory-005
# text = Lord build me just a cabin in the corner of Gloryland
1	Lord	B-PER	-	-
2	build	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	just	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	cabin	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	corner	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	Gloryland	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tennessee_Ernie_Ford_Dixie-010
# text = To arms! To arms! And conquer peace for Dixie
1	To	O	-	-
2	arms	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-
4	To	O	-	-
5	arms	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	And	O	-	-
8	conquer	O	-	-
9	peace	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	Dixie	B-LOC	-	-
