# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_This_Is_How_We_Do-023
# text = Sucking real bad at Mariah Carey-oke (Oh-oh)
1	Sucking	O	-	-
2	real	O	-	-
3	bad	O	-	-
4	at	O	-	-
5	Mariah	B-PER	-	-
6	Carey	I-PER	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	oke	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Oh	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	oh	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-011
# text = Brando, The King And I,
1	Brando	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	The	O	-	-
4	King	O	-	-
5	And	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Surfin_U_S_A_-026
# text = Pacific Palisades
1	Pacific	B-LOC	-	-
2	Palisades	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-006
# text = There's a place called Kokomo
1	There	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	place	O	-	-
6	called	O	-	-
7	Kokomo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Glamorous-026
# text = I still go to Taco Bell
1	I	O	-	-
2	still	O	-	-
3	go	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	Taco	B-LOC	-	-
6	Bell	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Maroon_5_Moves_Like_Jagger-019
# text = With them moves like Jagger
1	With	O	-	-
2	them	O	-	-
3	moves	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Jagger	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Pop-002
# text = (Yo, BT)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Yo	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	BT	B-PER	-	-
5	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Swish_Swish-057
# text = I only rock with Queens, so I'm makin' hits with Katy
1	I	O	-	-
2	only	O	-	-
3	rock	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	Queens	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	so	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	m	O	-	-
11	makin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	hits	O	-	-
14	with	O	-	-
15	Katy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Wide_Awake-011
# text = Gravity hurts, you made it so sweet
1	Gravity	O	-	-
2	hurts	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	made	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	so	O	-	-
8	sweet	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_O_Holy_Night-014
# text = O night when Christ was born
1	O	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	when	O	-	-
4	Christ	B-PER	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	born	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Waterloo-009
# text = Waterloo, couldn't escape if I wanted to
1	Waterloo	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	couldn	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	escape	O	-	-
7	if	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	wanted	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Smooth_Criminal-031
# text = Annie, are you okay? Annie, are you okay?
1	Annie	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	are	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	okay	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	Annie	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	are	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	okay	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Backstreet_Boys_No_Place-004
# text = And there ain't no way to touch your body over the phone
1	And	O	-	-
2	there	O	-	-
3	ain	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	no	O	-	-
7	way	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	touch	O	-	-
10	your	O	-	-
11	body	O	-	-
12	over	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	phone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Sign_O_The_Times-004
# text = At home, there are seventeen-year-old boys and their idea of fun is being in a gang called The Disciples, high on crack, totin' a machine gun
1	At	O	-	-
2	home	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	there	O	-	-
5	are	O	-	-
6	seventeen	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	year	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	old	O	-	-
11	boys	O	-	-
12	and	O	-	-
13	their	O	-	-
14	idea	O	-	-
15	of	O	-	-
16	fun	O	-	-
17	is	O	-	-
18	being	O	-	-
19	in	O	-	-
20	a	O	-	-
21	gang	O	-	-
22	called	O	-	-
23	The	B-ORG	-	-
24	Disciples	I-ORG	-	-
25	,	O	-	-
26	high	O	-	-
27	on	O	-	-
28	crack	O	-	-
29	,	O	-	-
30	totin	O	-	-
31	'	O	-	-
32	a	O	-	-
33	machine	O	-	-
34	gun	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Daniel-015
# text = Oh God, it looks like Daniel
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	God	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	looks	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	Daniel	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cyndi_Lauper_The_World_Is_Stone-031
# text = I'm not taking the call
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	not	O	-	-
5	taking	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	call	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman-006
# text = I met him out for dinner on a Friday night
1	I	O	-	-
2	met	O	-	-
3	him	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	for	O	-	-
6	dinner	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	Friday	O	-	-
10	night	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_1999-008
# text = Drive 'round listening to Shady like, oh
1	Drive	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	round	O	-	-
4	listening	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Shady	B-PER	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	oh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-034
# text = Brenda and Eddie were still goin' steady in the summer of '75
1	Brenda	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Eddie	B-PER	-	-
4	were	O	-	-
5	still	O	-	-
6	goin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	steady	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	summer	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	75	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Sting_Desert_Rose
# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Desert_Rose-001
# text = Layli, layli, oh
1	Layli	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	layli	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	oh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_This_Is_How_We_Do-022
# text = Day drinking at the Wildcat
1	Day	O	-	-
2	drinking	O	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Wildcat	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Like_a_Girl-027
# text = Lauryn Hill told me everything is everything (We can do it)
1	Lauryn	B-PER	-	-
2	Hill	I-PER	-	-
3	told	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	everything	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	everything	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	We	O	-	-
10	can	O	-	-
11	do	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-010
# text = She got Arthur on the table with Johnny riding a shotgun
1	She	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	Arthur	B-PER	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	table	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
9	riding	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	shotgun	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Confident-039
# text = Chance? The Rapper? IGH!
1	Chance	B-PER	-	-
2	?	O	-	-
3	The	I-PER	-	-
4	Rapper	I-PER	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	IGH	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Mary_Jane_Shoes-017
# text = When I step into my shoes, make the lady wanna (Hey)
1	When	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	step	O	-	-
4	into	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	shoes	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	make	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	lady	O	-	-
11	wanna	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Hey	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_If_You_Had_My_Love-004
# text = Would you lie to me and call me "baby"?
1	Would	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	lie	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	call	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	"	O	-	-
10	baby	O	-	-
11	"	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Pink-006
# text = It's her (Ayy), and her (Ayy), and me, and you
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Ayy	O	-	-
7	)	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	her	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Ayy	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	and	O	-	-
16	me	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	and	O	-	-
19	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-003
# text = South Pacific
1	South	B-LOC	-	-
2	Pacific	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Only_the_Good_Die_Young-008
# text = For things that you might have done
1	For	O	-	-
2	things	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	might	O	-	-
6	have	O	-	-
7	done	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_California_Gurls-054
# text = 'Cause you representin' California (Oh-oh, yeah)
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	representin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	California	B-LOC	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Oh	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	oh	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	yeah	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Crazy_in_love-022
# text = It's the beat that my heart skips when I'm with you
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	beat	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	heart	O	-	-
9	skips	O	-	-
10	when	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	with	O	-	-
15	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Speed_Drive-008
# text = Got a classic, real deep, Van Gogh
1	Got	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	classic	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	real	O	-	-
6	deep	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Van	B-PER	-	-
9	Gogh	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-005
# text = I met her on Grafton Street right outside of the bar
1	I	O	-	-
2	met	O	-	-
3	her	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	Grafton	B-LOC	-	-
6	Street	I-LOC	-	-
7	right	O	-	-
8	outside	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	bar	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Dirty_Diana-021
# text = Diana, Diana
1	Diana	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Diana	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Backstreet_Boys_Larger_Than_Life-022
# text = Ooh-ooh (Yeah)
1	Ooh	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	ooh	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Yeah	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_GIRL_LIKE_ME-008
# text = I want a girl like Shakira, eh
1	I	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	girl	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Shakira	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	eh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Gimme_More-044
# text = Gimme, gimme (Danja, Danja, Danja, Danja)
1	Gimme	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	gimme	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Danja	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Danja	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Danja	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Danja	B-PER	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_All_This_Time-021
# text = Father, if Jesus exists then how come he never lives here?
1	Father	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	if	O	-	-
4	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
5	exists	O	-	-
6	then	O	-	-
7	how	O	-	-
8	come	O	-	-
9	he	O	-	-
10	never	O	-	-
11	lives	O	-	-
12	here	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Zanzibar-024
# text = Tell the waitress I'll come back to Zanzibar
1	Tell	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	waitress	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	ll	O	-	-
7	come	O	-	-
8	back	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	Zanzibar	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman-002
# text = Candyman, Candyman
1	Candyman	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Candyman	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Naked_In_Manhattan-034
# text = I just want to touch you (Naked in Manhattan)
1	I	O	-	-
2	just	O	-	-
3	want	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	touch	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Naked	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Manhattan	B-LOC	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman-012
# text = A sweet-talkin', sugar-coated Candyman
1	A	O	-	-
2	sweet	O	-	-
3	-	O	-	-
4	talkin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	sugar	O	-	-
8	-	O	-	-
9	coated	O	-	-
10	Candyman	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Naked_In_Manhattan-019
# text = Oh, I've never done it, naked in Manhattan
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ve	O	-	-
6	never	O	-	-
7	done	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	naked	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	Manhattan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_I_Want_You_Back-006
# text = Joey: I...
1	Joey	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Oops_I_Did_It_Again-029
# text = Got lost in this game, oh, baby (Baby)
1	Got	O	-	-
2	lost	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	this	O	-	-
5	game	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	oh	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	baby	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Baby	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kelly_Clarkson_Catch_My_Breath-009
# text = Catching my breath, letting it go
1	Catching	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	breath	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	letting	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	go	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Backstreet_Boys_Get_Down_You_re_the_One_for_Me_-026
# text = AJ, hit it
1	AJ	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	hit	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Guilty_Pleasure-021
# text = Pothead, you're a cinephile
1	Pothead	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	re	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	cinephile	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Eenie_Meenie-017
# text = 'Cause shorty is a eenie-meenie-miney-mo lover
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	shorty	B-PER	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	eenie	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	meenie	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	miney	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	mo	O	-	-
13	lover	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Any_Time_Any_Place-034
# text = I don't wanna stop just because (I don't wanna stop)
1	I	O	-	-
2	don	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	wanna	O	-	-
6	stop	O	-	-
7	just	O	-	-
8	because	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	don	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	t	O	-	-
14	wanna	O	-	-
15	stop	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-036
# text = Little Rock, Pasternak
1	Little	B-LOC	-	-
2	Rock	I-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Pasternak	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Whitney_Houston_My_Love_Is_Your_Love-010
# text = (In World War 3)
1	(	O	-	-
2	In	O	-	-
3	World	O	-	-
4	War	O	-	-
5	3	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sabrina_Carpenter_Sharpest_Tool-021
# text = Found God at your ex's house, always
1	Found	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	your	O	-	-
5	ex	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	house	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	always	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Englishman_In_New_York-004
# text = I'm an Englishman in New York
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	an	O	-	-
5	Englishman	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	New	B-LOC	-	-
8	York	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-015
# text = Hot, like Mexico, rejoice
1	Hot	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	Mexico	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	rejoice	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Oh_Santa_-042
# text = Oh, Santa Claus
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Santa	B-PER	-	-
4	Claus	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sabrina_Carpenter_A_Nonsense_Christmas-035
# text = I need that Charles Dickens (No)
1	I	O	-	-
2	need	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	Charles	B-PER	-	-
5	Dickens	I-PER	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	No	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Doin_Time-005
# text = Me, me and Louie, we gonna run to the party
1	Me	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Louie	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	we	O	-	-
8	gonna	O	-	-
9	run	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	party	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Escapade-014
# text = Let me take you on an escapade
1	Let	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	an	O	-	-
7	escapade	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_No_Strings_Attached-004
# text = Hey yeah
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Controversy-039
# text = Do I believe in God? Do I believe in me? Let me tell you
1	Do	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	believe	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	Do	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	believe	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-
13	Let	O	-	-
14	me	O	-	-
15	tell	O	-	-
16	you	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-ABBA_Fernando
# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Fernando-001
# text = Can you hear the drums, Fernando?
1	Can	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	hear	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	drums	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Fernando	B-PER	-	-
8	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_When_Doves_Cry-034
# text = When doves cry (When doves cry, they cry)
1	When	O	-	-
2	doves	O	-	-
3	cry	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	When	O	-	-
6	doves	O	-	-
7	cry	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	they	O	-	-
10	cry	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Backstreet_Boys_Inconsolable-018
# text = I climb the walls, yeah
1	I	O	-	-
2	climb	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	walls	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_September-023
# text = Our souls were singin'
1	Our	O	-	-
2	souls	O	-	-
3	were	O	-	-
4	singin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Smooth_Criminal-034
# text = Choo-cha, choo-cha
1	Choo	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	cha	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	choo	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	cha	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cyndi_Lauper_Christmas_Conga-013
# text = String up the new lights
1	String	O	-	-
2	up	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	new	O	-	-
5	lights	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Baby-031
# text = I'm gone (Yeah-yeah-yeah, yeah-yeah-yeah)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	gone	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Yeah	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	yeah	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	yeah	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	yeah	O	-	-
13	-	O	-	-
14	yeah	O	-	-
15	-	O	-	-
16	yeah	O	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Suit_Tie-061
# text = Show you a few things about love, love, love
1	Show	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	few	O	-	-
5	things	O	-	-
6	about	O	-	-
7	love	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	love	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	love	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Suit_Tie-037
# text = Get out your seat, Hov
1	Get	O	-	-
2	out	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	seat	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Hov	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-P_nk_Never_Gonna_Not_Dance_Again-034
# text = (I'm never gonna not gonna dance again)
1	(	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	never	O	-	-
6	gonna	O	-	-
7	not	O	-	-
8	gonna	O	-	-
9	dance	O	-	-
10	again	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_Amazing-019
# text = I think you're amazing
1	I	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	re	O	-	-
6	amazing	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-038
# text = And Eddie could never afford to live that kind of life”
1	And	O	-	-
2	Eddie	B-PER	-	-
3	could	O	-	-
4	never	O	-	-
5	afford	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	live	O	-	-
8	that	O	-	-
9	kind	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	life	O	-	-
12	”	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_7_Things-035
# text = (Sha, sha)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Sha	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	sha	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Born_To_Die-031
# text = (Louder)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Louder	O	-	-
3	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_Heal_the_Pain-012
# text = How can I help you
1	How	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	help	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Waiting_for_Tonight-027
# text = Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh-oh
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	oh	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	oh	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	oh	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	oh	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	oh	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	oh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Irreplaceable-012
# text = Talkin' 'bout how I'll never ever find a man like you
1	Talkin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	bout	O	-	-
5	how	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	ll	O	-	-
9	never	O	-	-
10	ever	O	-	-
11	find	O	-	-
12	a	O	-	-
13	man	O	-	-
14	like	O	-	-
15	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Finesse-036
# text = Don't it feel so good to be us? Ayy (Baby)
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	feel	O	-	-
6	so	O	-	-
7	good	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	be	O	-	-
10	us	O	-	-
11	?	O	-	-
12	Ayy	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Baby	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Rich_Girl-038
# text = See Stefani and her L.A.M.B
1	See	O	-	-
2	Stefani	B-PER	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	L	B-ORG	-	-
6	.	I-ORG	-	-
7	A	I-ORG	-	-
8	.	I-ORG	-	-
9	M	I-ORG	-	-
10	.	I-ORG	-	-
11	B	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Daniel-006
# text = They say Spain is pretty, though I've never been
1	They	O	-	-
2	say	O	-	-
3	Spain	B-LOC	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	pretty	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	though	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ve	O	-	-
11	never	O	-	-
12	been	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Maroon_5_Moves_Like_Jagger-014
# text = All the moves like Jagger
1	All	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	moves	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Jagger	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Unlock_It-028
# text = Unlock the swag, Rae Sremmurd (Sremmurd, yuh)
1	Unlock	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	swag	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Rae	B-PER	-	-
6	Sremmurd	I-PER	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Sremmurd	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	yuh	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Señorita-030
# text = Ah, ah, arms (Bring it down, h!) (Baby, won't you lay in my)
1	Ah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	ah	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	arms	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Bring	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	down	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	h	O	-	-
12	!	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Baby	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	won	O	-	-
18	'	O	-	-
19	t	O	-	-
20	you	O	-	-
21	lay	O	-	-
22	in	O	-	-
23	my	O	-	-
24	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-One_Direction_Live_While_We_re_Young-014
# text = And live while we're young
1	And	O	-	-
2	live	O	-	-
3	while	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	re	O	-	-
7	young	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_GIRL_LIKE_ME-057
# text = Ones who look like Selena
1	Ones	O	-	-
2	who	O	-	-
3	look	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Selena	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Barbra_Streisand_New_York_State_of_Mind-021
# text = I'm in a New York, I'm in a New York state of mind...
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	New	B-LOC	-	-
7	York	I-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	New	B-LOC	-	-
15	York	I-LOC	-	-
16	state	O	-	-
17	of	O	-	-
18	mind	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-
20	.	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Good_as_Hell-014
# text = (Feeling good as hell)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Feeling	O	-	-
3	good	O	-	-
4	as	O	-	-
5	hell	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-046
# text = Bring my people back to Venice
1	Bring	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	people	O	-	-
4	back	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Venice	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_They_Don_t_Care_About_Us-041
# text = But if Martin Luther was livin'
1	But	O	-	-
2	if	O	-	-
3	Martin	B-PER	-	-
4	Luther	I-PER	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	livin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Baby_Boy-004
# text = Sean da Paul 'longside Beyoncé
1	Sean	B-PER	-	-
2	da	I-PER	-	-
3	Paul	I-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	longside	O	-	-
6	Beyoncé	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Whitney_Houston_Exhale_Shoop_Shoop_-010
# text = Shoo Be Doop Shoop Shoop
1	Shoo	O	-	-
2	Be	O	-	-
3	Doop	O	-	-
4	Shoop	O	-	-
5	Shoop	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_See_You_Again-006
# text = I've got a way of knowin' when something is right
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	way	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	knowin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	when	O	-	-
11	something	O	-	-
12	is	O	-	-
13	right	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_FEEL_THE_BEAT-032
# text = Mami, look at how cute you are, yeah
1	Mami	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	look	O	-	-
4	at	O	-	-
5	how	O	-	-
6	cute	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	are	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	yeah	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Blondie_Denis
# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Denis-001
# text = Oh Denis doo-be-do
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	Denis	B-PER	-	-
3	doo	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	do	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Bennie_And_The_Jets-006
# text = Say, Candy and Ronnie, have you seen them yet?
1	Say	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Candy	B-PER	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Ronnie	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	have	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	seen	O	-	-
10	them	O	-	-
11	yet	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rihanna_What_s_My_Name_-042
# text = To every word you whisper
1	To	O	-	-
2	every	O	-	-
3	word	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	whisper	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Gimme_More-049
# text = Ah, you gonna have to remove me
1	Ah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	gonna	O	-	-
5	have	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	remove	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Jenny_from_the_Block_Track_Masters_Remix_-015
# text = Make the money, get the mansion, bring the homies with us (Southside Bronx)
1	Make	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	money	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	get	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	mansion	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	bring	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	homies	O	-	-
12	with	O	-	-
13	us	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Southside	O	-	-
16	Bronx	I-LOC	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Backstreet_Boys_No_Place-002
# text = Seen the sun setting on the beach in Mexico
1	Seen	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	sun	O	-	-
4	setting	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	beach	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Mexico	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_Love_Story_Taylor_s_Version_-013
# text = Romeo, take me somewhere we can be alone
1	Romeo	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	somewhere	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	can	O	-	-
8	be	O	-	-
9	alone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_She_s_Always_a_Woman-035
# text = But she can't be convicted
1	But	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	can	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	convicted	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_If_U_Seek_Amy-028
# text = Oh, baby, baby, if you seek Amy tonight (Oh)
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	baby	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	baby	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	if	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	seek	O	-	-
10	Amy	B-PER	-	-
11	tonight	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Oh	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Labels_Or_Love-006
# text = I be looking for labels, I ain't looking for love
1	I	O	-	-
2	be	O	-	-
3	looking	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	labels	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	ain	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	looking	O	-	-
12	for	O	-	-
13	love	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Rumors-042
# text = Lizzo, teach me about big girl coochie (Okay)
1	Lizzo	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	teach	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	about	O	-	-
6	big	O	-	-
7	girl	O	-	-
8	coochie	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Okay	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Chained_To_The_Rhythm-034
# text = They greed over the people
1	They	O	-	-
2	greed	O	-	-
3	over	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	people	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Hey_Mama-017
# text = And then drop bombs like we in the Middle East
1	And	O	-	-
2	then	O	-	-
3	drop	O	-	-
4	bombs	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Middle	B-LOC	-	-
10	East	I-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Bubble_Pop_Electric
# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Bubble_Pop_Electric-001
# text = C'mon, Johnny! When you gonna get here?
1	C	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	mon	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	When	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	gonna	O	-	-
10	get	O	-	-
11	here	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Single_Ladies_Put_a_Ring_on_It_-022
# text = What it really feels like to miss Bey
1	What	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	really	O	-	-
4	feels	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	miss	O	-	-
8	Bey	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_Midnight_Sky-026
# text = You know it's true, you know it's true
1	You	O	-	-
2	know	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	true	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	know	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	true	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_4_Minutes-007
# text = Hey, uh, c'mon, Madonna
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	uh	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	c	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	mon	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Madonna	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_2_Be_Loved_Am_I_Ready_-031
# text = Think you like that, think you like that
1	Think	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	think	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_California_Gurls-030
# text = California girls, we're unforgettable (California)
1	California	B-LOC	-	-
2	girls	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	re	O	-	-
7	unforgettable	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	California	B-LOC	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-031
# text = Tried Peggy Sue, tried Peggy Lou
1	Tried	O	-	-
2	Peggy	B-PER	-	-
3	Sue	I-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	tried	O	-	-
6	Peggy	B-PER	-	-
7	Lou	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Santa_Claus_Is_Comin_to_Town-015
# text = Santa Claus is comin' to town (Yeah)
1	Santa	B-PER	-	-
2	Claus	I-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	comin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	town	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Yeah	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-004
# text = Finger on the pump, make the 6 straight jump from SoCal
1	Finger	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	pump	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	make	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	6	O	-	-
9	straight	O	-	-
10	jump	O	-	-
11	from	O	-	-
12	SoCal	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_U_Got_The_Look-011
# text = Crucial, I think I want you
1	Crucial	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	think	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	want	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_On_The_Floor-007
# text = Get on the floor, RedOne
1	Get	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	floor	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	RedOne	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Make_Me_-025
# text = Out in Vegas or a little bar
1	Out	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	Vegas	B-LOC	-	-
4	or	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	little	O	-	-
7	bar	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_My_Kink_Is_Karma-008
# text = I heard from Katie
1	I	O	-	-
2	heard	O	-	-
3	from	O	-	-
4	Katie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_After_Midnight-016
# text = I love a little "uh-huh", let's watch the sunrise
1	I	O	-	-
2	love	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	little	O	-	-
5	"	O	-	-
6	uh	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	huh	O	-	-
9	"	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	let	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	watch	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	sunrise	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Jenny_from_the_Block_Track_Masters_Remix_-054
# text = I'm still, I'm still Jenny from the block (Bronx)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	still	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	still	O	-	-
10	Jenny	B-PER	-	-
11	from	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	block	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Bronx	B-LOC	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_All_Too_Well_10_Minute_Version_Taylor_s_Version_From_The_Vault_-093
# text = Wind in my hair, I was there, I was there
1	Wind	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	hair	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	was	O	-	-
8	there	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	was	O	-	-
12	there	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Rumors-020
# text = No, I ain't fuck Drake yet (Ha)
1	No	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	ain	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	fuck	O	-	-
8	Drake	B-PER	-	-
9	yet	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Ha	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-049
# text = (Oh, my) Barbara Ann
1	(	O	-	-
2	Oh	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
7	Ann	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Labels_Or_Love-018
# text = No emotional baggage, just big bags filled with Dior (Oh)
1	No	O	-	-
2	emotional	O	-	-
3	baggage	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	just	O	-	-
6	big	O	-	-
7	bags	O	-	-
8	filled	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	Dior	B-ORG	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Oh	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Piano_Man-014
# text = And you've got us feelin' alright
1	And	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	ve	O	-	-
5	got	O	-	-
6	us	O	-	-
7	feelin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	alright	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Pop-046
# text = (BT)
1	(	O	-	-
2	BT	B-PER	-	-
3	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_September-013
# text = Ba duda, badu, ba duda, badu
1	Ba	O	-	-
2	duda	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	badu	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	ba	O	-	-
7	duda	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	badu	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Nikita-013
# text = Oh, Nikita, is the other side
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Nikita	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	other	O	-	-
8	side	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_BURNITUP_-011
# text = Janet Jackson come soon to your town
1	Janet	B-PER	-	-
2	Jackson	I-PER	-	-
3	come	O	-	-
4	soon	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	town	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Bubble_Pop_Electric-006
# text = Yeah, Gwennie-Gwen-Gwen?
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Gwennie	B-PER	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	Gwen	B-PER	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	Gwen	B-PER	-	-
8	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Beautiful_Liar-004
# text = Oh, Shakira, Shakira (Hey)
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Shakira	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Shakira	B-PER	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Hey	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Exactly_How_I_Feel-022
# text = That's exactly how I feel (How I feel, it's Gucci)
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	exactly	O	-	-
5	how	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	feel	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	How	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	feel	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	it	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	s	O	-	-
16	Gucci	B-ORG	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Lucky-017
# text = "I'm Roger Johnson for Pop News, standing outside the arena waiting for Lucky"
1	"	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	Roger	B-PER	-	-
6	Johnson	I-PER	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	Pop	B-ORG	-	-
9	News	I-ORG	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	standing	O	-	-
12	outside	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	arena	O	-	-
15	waiting	O	-	-
16	for	O	-	-
17	Lucky	B-PER	-	-
18	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Chiquitita-007
# text = Chiquitita, tell me the truth
1	Chiquitita	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	tell	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	truth	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Beautiful_Liar-006
# text = I know things about him that you wouldn't wanna read about
1	I	O	-	-
2	know	O	-	-
3	things	O	-	-
4	about	O	-	-
5	him	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	wouldn	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	wanna	O	-	-
12	read	O	-	-
13	about	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Hungry-035
# text = El Chapo
1	El	B-PER	-	-
2	Chapo	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_P_Y_T_Pretty_Young_Thing_-045
# text = I want to love you, P.Y.T., P.Y.T
1	I	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	love	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	P	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Y	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	T	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	P	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	Y	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	T	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Rip_Her_To_Shreds-032
# text = She makin' out with King Kong
1	She	O	-	-
2	makin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	King	B-PER	-	-
7	Kong	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Only_the_Good_Die_Young-016
# text = So come on, Virginia, show me a sign
1	So	O	-	-
2	come	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	show	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	sign	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-041
# text = The whole damn world took effect to Ferg
1	The	O	-	-
2	whole	O	-	-
3	damn	O	-	-
4	world	O	-	-
5	took	O	-	-
6	effect	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Ferg	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_I_Want_You_Back-007
# text = Justin: I...
1	Justin	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_On_The_Floor-048
# text = That badonkadonk is like a trunk
1	That	O	-	-
2	badonkadonk	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	trunk	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_September-012
# text = Ba duda, ba duda, ba duda, badu
1	Ba	O	-	-
2	duda	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	ba	O	-	-
5	duda	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	ba	O	-	-
8	duda	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	badu	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-P_nk_Can_We_Pretend-037
# text = But you'd already know
1	But	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	d	O	-	-
5	already	O	-	-
6	know	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-061
# text = Stockholm saying (La-la-la-la-la)
1	Stockholm	B-LOC	-	-
2	saying	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	La	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	la	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	la	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	la	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	la	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Ghost
# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Ghost-001
# text = Youngblood thinks there's always tomorrow
1	Youngblood	B-PER	-	-
2	thinks	O	-	-
3	there	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	always	O	-	-
7	tomorrow	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Escapade-027
# text = Minneapolis!
1	Minneapolis	B-LOC	-	-
2	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-022
# text = Joseph Stalin, Malenkov
1	Joseph	B-PER	-	-
2	Stalin	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Malenkov	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_La_Isla_Bonita-002
# text = Last night I dreamt of San Pedro
1	Last	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	dreamt	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	San	B-LOC	-	-
7	Pedro	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cyndi_Lauper_Christmas_Conga-020
# text = And break those resolutions
1	And	O	-	-
2	break	O	-	-
3	those	O	-	-
4	resolutions	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_My_Humps-011
# text = Karan, they be sharing all their money
1	Karan	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	sharing	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	their	O	-	-
8	money	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Maroon_5_One_More_Night-039
# text = That I'll only stay with you one more night (Yeah, yeah)
1	That	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	ll	O	-	-
5	only	O	-	-
6	stay	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	one	O	-	-
10	more	O	-	-
11	night	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Yeah	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	yeah	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Oh_Santa_-033
# text = But I believe in you, Saint Nick
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	believe	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Saint	B-PER	-	-
8	Nick	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Ultraviolence-019
# text = We could go back to New York
1	We	O	-	-
2	could	O	-	-
3	go	O	-	-
4	back	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	New	B-LOC	-	-
7	York	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Here_I_Come-029
# text = I represent Los Angeles city (Hey)
1	I	O	-	-
2	represent	O	-	-
3	Los	B-LOC	-	-
4	Angeles	I-LOC	-	-
5	city	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Hey	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-067
# text = Lil' Kim (Hey, hey, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh)
1	Lil	B-PER	-	-
2	'	I-PER	-	-
3	Kim	I-PER	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Hey	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	hey	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	uh	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	uh	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	uh	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	uh	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	uh	O	-	-
18	,	O	-	-
19	uh	O	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	uh	O	-	-
22	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Zanzibar-003
# text = Ali, don't you go downtown
1	Ali	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	go	O	-	-
8	downtown	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Naked_In_Manhattan-028
# text = In New York, you can try things
1	In	O	-	-
2	New	B-LOC	-	-
3	York	I-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	can	O	-	-
7	try	O	-	-
8	things	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-024
# text = My pretty little Galway Girl
1	My	O	-	-
2	pretty	O	-	-
3	little	O	-	-
4	Galway	B-LOC	-	-
5	Girl	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-051
# text = Belgians in the Congo
1	Belgians	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Congo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Bitch_I_m_Madonna-031
# text = (Bitch, bitch, I'm Madonna, bitch, I'm Madonna) You can't mess with this lucky star
1	(	O	-	-
2	Bitch	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	bitch	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	Madonna	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	bitch	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	m	O	-	-
16	Madonna	B-PER	-	-
17	)	O	-	-
18	You	O	-	-
19	can	O	-	-
20	'	O	-	-
21	t	O	-	-
22	mess	O	-	-
23	with	O	-	-
24	this	O	-	-
25	lucky	O	-	-
26	star	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_No_Strings_Attached-033
# text = JC: Ah...
1	JC	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Ah	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Heartbreaker-068
# text = But she knows she loves Jay because
1	But	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	knows	O	-	-
4	she	O	-	-
5	loves	O	-	-
6	Jay	B-PER	-	-
7	because	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Adele_Hello-006
# text = I'm in California dreaming about who we used to be
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	California	B-LOC	-	-
6	dreaming	O	-	-
7	about	O	-	-
8	who	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	used	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	be	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Suit_Tie-043
# text = Stoute got gout from having the best of the best
1	Stoute	B-PER	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	gout	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	having	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	best	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	best	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Christmas_Baby_Please_Come_Home_-008
# text = (Christmas) The church bells in town
1	(	O	-	-
2	Christmas	O	-	-
3	)	O	-	-
4	The	O	-	-
5	church	O	-	-
6	bells	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	town	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_You_Need_To_Calm_Down-017
# text = Why are you mad when you could be GLAAD? (You could be GLAAD)
1	Why	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	mad	O	-	-
5	when	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	could	O	-	-
8	be	O	-	-
9	GLAAD	B-ORG	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	You	O	-	-
13	could	O	-	-
14	be	O	-	-
15	GLAAD	B-ORG	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Guess_featuring_billie_eilish-027
# text = Charli, call me if you're with it
1	Charli	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	call	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	if	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	re	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Eenie_Meenie-037
# text = Shorty is a eenie-meenie-miney-mo lover (Eenie-meenie-miney-mo; Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
1	Shorty	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	eenie	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	meenie	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	miney	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	mo	O	-	-
11	lover	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Eenie	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	meenie	O	-	-
16	-	O	-	-
17	miney	O	-	-
18	-	O	-	-
19	mo	O	-	-
20	;	O	-	-
21	Yeah	O	-	-
22	,	O	-	-
23	yeah	O	-	-
24	,	O	-	-
25	yeah	O	-	-
26	,	O	-	-
27	yeah	O	-	-
28	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Little_Saint_Nick-008
# text = (Oooooh, little Saint Nick)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Oooooh	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	little	O	-	-
5	Saint	B-PER	-	-
6	Nick	I-PER	-	-
7	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_My_Love-028
# text = 'Cause girl, I've never been more sure (That, baby, it's you)
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	girl	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	ve	O	-	-
8	never	O	-	-
9	been	O	-	-
10	more	O	-	-
11	sure	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	That	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	baby	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	it	O	-	-
18	'	O	-	-
19	s	O	-	-
20	you	O	-	-
21	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_On_The_Floor-054
# text = I get on the floor and act a fool if you let me, dale
1	I	O	-	-
2	get	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	floor	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	act	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	fool	O	-	-
10	if	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	let	O	-	-
13	me	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	dale	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Suit_Tie-009
# text = You ready, JT?
1	You	O	-	-
2	ready	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	JT	B-PER	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Backstreet_Boys_Everybody_Backstreet_s_Back_-009
# text = Got a question for you, better answer now, yeah
1	Got	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	question	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	better	O	-	-
8	answer	O	-	-
9	now	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-009
# text = She took Jamie as a chaser, Jack for the fun
1	She	O	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	Jamie	B-PER	-	-
4	as	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	chaser	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Jack	B-PER	-	-
9	for	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	fun	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Versace_on_the_Floor-020
# text = No, don't be afraid to show it all
1	No	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	afraid	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	show	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	all	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Oh_Santa_-041
# text = Santa gon' come and make him mine, mine (Oh, oh, oh)
1	Santa	B-PER	-	-
2	gon	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	come	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	make	O	-	-
7	him	O	-	-
8	mine	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	mine	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Oh	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	oh	O	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	oh	O	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Pump_It-015
# text = From London back down to the U.S. (S. S.)
1	From	O	-	-
2	London	B-LOC	-	-
3	back	O	-	-
4	down	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	U	B-LOC	-	-
8	.	I-LOC	-	-
9	S	I-LOC	-	-
10	.	I-LOC	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	S	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	S	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_GIRL_LIKE_ME-023
# text = Ah-ah-ah, you're lookin' for
1	Ah	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	ah	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	ah	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	re	O	-	-
10	lookin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	for	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-019
# text = Oh, you'd drop a dime in the box, play a song about New Orleans
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	drop	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	dime	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	box	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	play	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	song	O	-	-
16	about	O	-	-
17	New	B-LOC	-	-
18	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Touch_My_Body
# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Touch_My_Body-001
# text = MC
1	MC	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Backstreet_Boys_We_ve_Got_It_Goin_On-024
# text = Backstreet’s got the special effects
1	Backstreet	B-ORG	-	-
2	’	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	special	O	-	-
7	effects	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Make_Me_Like_You-028
# text = Thank God
1	Thank	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Beg_for_You-012
# text = Yeah, yeah, yeah, uh, yeah
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	yeah	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	uh	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-P_nk_Never_Gonna_Not_Dance_Again-016
# text = I want my life to be a Whitney Houston song (I wanna dance)
1	I	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	life	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	Whitney	B-PER	-	-
9	Houston	I-PER	-	-
10	song	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	wanna	O	-	-
14	dance	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Crazy_in_love-036
# text = Soprano, the ROC handle like Van Exel
1	Soprano	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	ROC	B-ORG	-	-
5	handle	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	Van	B-ORG	-	-
8	Exel	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Pink_Pony_Club-014
# text = Pink Pony Club, I'm gonna keep on dancing down in
1	Pink	B-LOC	-	-
2	Pony	I-LOC	-	-
3	Club	I-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	gonna	O	-	-
9	keep	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-
11	dancing	O	-	-
12	down	O	-	-
13	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Made_For_Now-043
# text = Made for now (Janet Jackson)
1	Made	O	-	-
2	for	O	-	-
3	now	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Janet	B-PER	-	-
6	Jackson	I-PER	-	-
7	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Valerie_BBC_Radio_1_Live_Lounge_-026
# text = Oh, Valerie
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Valerie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Super_Trouper-006
# text = When I called you last night from Glasgow
1	When	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	called	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	last	O	-	-
6	night	O	-	-
7	from	O	-	-
8	Glasgow	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Hollaback_Girl-005
# text = 'Cause I ain't no Hollaback Girl
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	ain	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	no	O	-	-
8	Hollaback	B-LOC	-	-
9	Girl	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Just_Dance-002
# text = RedOne
1	RedOne	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Coldplay_Viva_La_Vida-028
# text = Roman Cavalry choirs are singing
1	Roman	B-PER	-	-
2	Cavalry	I-PER	-	-
3	choirs	O	-	-
4	are	O	-	-
5	singing	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_RITMO_Bad_Boys_for_Life_-016
# text = La Rosalía me dice que luzco guay (La Rosalía)
1	La	B-PER	-	-
2	Rosalía	I-PER	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	dice	O	-	-
5	que	O	-	-
6	luzco	O	-	-
7	guay	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	La	B-PER	-	-
10	Rosalía	I-PER	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-P_nk_Just_Like_a_Pill-009
# text = I said I tried to call the nurse again
1	I	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	tried	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	call	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	nurse	O	-	-
9	again	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kelly_Clarkson_My_Life_Would_Suck_Without_You-021
# text = Either way I found out
1	Either	O	-	-
2	way	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	found	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Wanna_Be_Startin_Somethin_-027
# text = Billie Jean is always talkin' when nobody else is talkin'
1	Billie	B-PER	-	-
2	Jean	I-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	always	O	-	-
5	talkin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	when	O	-	-
8	nobody	O	-	-
9	else	O	-	-
10	is	O	-	-
11	talkin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Coffee-003
# text = I'd suggest the jazz bar on Mary Ann Street, but
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	d	O	-	-
4	suggest	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	jazz	O	-	-
7	bar	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	Mary	B-LOC	-	-
10	Ann	I-LOC	-	-
11	Street	I-LOC	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	but	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Merry_Christmas_Happy_Holidays-059
# text = God sends you His love (Oh, yeah)
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	sends	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	His	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Oh	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yeah	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Fuck_Me_Pumps-027
# text = Don't do nothing for ya
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	do	O	-	-
5	nothing	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	ya	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Maroon_5_Daylight-022
# text = This is way too hard
1	This	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	way	O	-	-
4	too	O	-	-
5	hard	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Partition-006
# text = Brooklyn brim with my eyes sittin' low
1	Brooklyn	B-LOC	-	-
2	brim	O	-	-
3	with	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	eyes	O	-	-
6	sittin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	low	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-022
# text = L.A. got the people saying (La-la-la-la-la)
1	L	B-LOC	-	-
2	.	I-LOC	-	-
3	A	I-LOC	-	-
4	.	I-LOC	-	-
5	got	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	people	O	-	-
8	saying	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	La	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	la	O	-	-
13	-	O	-	-
14	la	O	-	-
15	-	O	-	-
16	la	O	-	-
17	-	O	-	-
18	la	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Billie_Jean-048
# text = Yeah, Billie Jean is not my lover, uh
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Billie	B-PER	-	-
4	Jean	I-PER	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	not	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	lover	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	uh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Jerome-019
# text = Jerome, ooh, Jerome
1	Jerome	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	ooh	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Jerome	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Always_Remember_Us_This_Way-004
# text = It's buried in my soul
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	buried	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	soul	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Barracuda-029
# text = Ooh, oh, Barra-Barracuda
1	Ooh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	oh	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Barra	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	Barracuda	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Glamorous-016
# text = By the glamorous
1	By	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	glamorous	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Ain_t_No_Other_Man-003
# text = I could feel it from the start
1	I	O	-	-
2	could	O	-	-
3	feel	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	start	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rihanna_Disturbia-025
# text = Disconnected, no one calls (The phone don't even ring)
1	Disconnected	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	no	O	-	-
4	one	O	-	-
5	calls	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	The	O	-	-
8	phone	O	-	-
9	don	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	even	O	-	-
13	ring	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Wouldn_t_It_Be_Nice-019
# text = It only makes it worse to live without it
1	It	O	-	-
2	only	O	-	-
3	makes	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	worse	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	live	O	-	-
8	without	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Drink_You_Away-010
# text = I've tried Jack, I've tried Jim, I’ve tried all of their friends
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	tried	O	-	-
5	Jack	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	ve	O	-	-
10	tried	O	-	-
11	Jim	B-PER	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	’	O	-	-
15	ve	O	-	-
16	tried	O	-	-
17	all	O	-	-
18	of	O	-	-
19	their	O	-	-
20	friends	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_BURNITUP_-050
# text = Ah, now bring that beat back, Mr. DJ
1	Ah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	now	O	-	-
4	bring	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	beat	O	-	-
7	back	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Mr	B-PER	-	-
10	.	I-PER	-	-
11	DJ	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Rumors-028
# text = But haters do what they do (Uh)
1	But	O	-	-
2	haters	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	what	O	-	-
5	they	O	-	-
6	do	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Uh	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_London_Bridge-036
# text = Cali callabo
1	Cali	B-LOC	-	-
2	callabo	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Dance_Again-038
# text = Mami let me open your treasure chest (Hahaha)
1	Mami	O	-	-
2	let	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	open	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	treasure	O	-	-
7	chest	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Hahaha	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Single_Ladies_Put_a_Ring_on_It_-028
# text = To infinity (Infinity) and beyond (And beyond)
1	To	O	-	-
2	infinity	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Infinity	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	beyond	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	And	O	-	-
10	beyond	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Here_I_Come-030
# text = Hacienda Heights is the vicinity (Yeah)
1	Hacienda	B-LOC	-	-
2	Heights	I-LOC	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	vicinity	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Yeah	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Tenerife_Sea-020
# text = Just say the word and I will disappear
1	Just	O	-	-
2	say	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	word	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	will	O	-	-
8	disappear	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Just_Got_Paid-006
# text = Chris: Just All: got paid
1	Chris	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Just	O	-	-
4	All	O	-	-
5	:	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	paid	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Rock_with_you-008
# text = And we can ride the boogie
1	And	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	can	O	-	-
4	ride	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	boogie	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Till_the_World_Ends-006
# text = If you want this good -ish, sicker than the remix
1	If	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	want	O	-	-
4	this	O	-	-
5	good	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	ish	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	sicker	O	-	-
10	than	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	remix	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-024
# text = Rockefeller, Campanella
1	Rockefeller	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Campanella	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Me_Mr_Jones-022
# text = Mr. Destiny, 9 and 14
1	Mr	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Destiny	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	9	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	14	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Piece_of_Me-004
# text = Don't matter if I step on the scene, or sneak away to the Philippines
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	matter	O	-	-
5	if	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	step	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	scene	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	or	O	-	-
13	sneak	O	-	-
14	away	O	-	-
15	to	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	Philippines	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Tiny_Dancer-005
# text = Ballerina, you must've seen her
1	Ballerina	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	must	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	ve	O	-	-
7	seen	O	-	-
8	her	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Beg_for_You-026
# text = Don't make me beg for you
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	make	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	beg	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Smooth_Criminal-037
# text = Then he struck you, a crescendo Annie
1	Then	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	struck	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	crescendo	O	-	-
8	Annie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Girlfriend-030
# text = Did you know that love could be a shield? Yeah
1	Did	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	know	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-
6	could	O	-	-
7	be	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	shield	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	Yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_All_This_Time-015
# text = I'd bury him at sea
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	d	O	-	-
4	bury	O	-	-
5	him	O	-	-
6	at	O	-	-
7	sea	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rihanna_Bitch_Better_Have_My_Money-002
# text = Mula-la
1	Mula	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	la	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Selena_Gomez_Fetish-035
# text = I'll be South Beach in the drop top gleamin'
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	South	B-LOC	-	-
6	Beach	I-LOC	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	drop	O	-	-
10	top	O	-	-
11	gleamin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kelly_Clarkson_Heartbeat_Song-025
# text = Baby, you make me feel alive and brand new
1	Baby	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	make	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	feel	O	-	-
7	alive	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	brand	O	-	-
10	new	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-045
# text = Lauren, Katharine, Lana too
1	Lauren	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Katharine	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Lana	B-PER	-	-
6	too	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-One_Direction_No_Control-004
# text = Just a fingerprint of lipstick's not enough
1	Just	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	fingerprint	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	lipstick	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	not	O	-	-
9	enough	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Spice_Girls_Holler-006
# text = Darkchild, Darkchild, come on
1	Darkchild	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Darkchild	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	come	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Coldplay_Christmas_Lights-005
# text = I took my feet to Oxford Street
1	I	O	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	feet	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Oxford	B-LOC	-	-
7	Street	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_I_Want_You_Back-008
# text = JC: I...
1	JC	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Beg_for_You-015
# text = Beg for you, bеg for you (Yeah; Rina Sawayama)
1	Beg	O	-	-
2	for	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	bеg	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Yeah	O	-	-
10	;	O	-	-
11	Rina	B-PER	-	-
12	Sawayama	I-PER	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Break_the_Rules-008
# text = I'm so alive
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	so	O	-	-
5	alive	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-024
# text = Hal, and his famous ashtray!
1	Hal	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	his	O	-	-
5	famous	O	-	-
6	ashtray	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Music-018
# text = Hey Mr. DJ, put a record on
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	Mr	B-PER	-	-
3	.	I-PER	-	-
4	DJ	I-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	put	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	record	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Life_Goes_On-048
# text = You need to speed your loyalty up like Bugatti
1	You	O	-	-
2	need	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	speed	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	loyalty	O	-	-
7	up	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Bugatti	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-044
# text = Lady Marmalade (Ooh, yeah, yeah)
1	Lady	O	-	-
2	Marmalade	B-PER	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Ooh	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	yeah	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	yeah	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo
# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-001
# text = Aruba, Jamaica, ooh, I wanna take ya
1	Aruba	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Jamaica	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	ooh	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	wanna	O	-	-
9	take	O	-	-
10	ya	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billie_Eilish_What_Was_I_Made_For_-016
# text = I'm sad again, don't tell my boyfriend
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	sad	O	-	-
5	again	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	don	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	t	O	-	-
10	tell	O	-	-
11	my	O	-	-
12	boyfriend	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-020
# text = I never heard Carrickfergus ever sung so sweet
1	I	O	-	-
2	never	O	-	-
3	heard	O	-	-
4	Carrickfergus	B-PER	-	-
5	ever	O	-	-
6	sung	O	-	-
7	so	O	-	-
8	sweet	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Glamorous-042
# text = Half a million for the stones, takin' trips from here to Rome
1	Half	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	million	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	stones	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	takin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	trips	O	-	-
11	from	O	-	-
12	here	O	-	-
13	to	O	-	-
14	Rome	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Whitney_Houston_My_Love_Is_Your_Love-033
# text = And the chains of Amistad couldn't hold us (Can't hold us)
1	And	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	chains	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	Amistad	B-ORG	-	-
6	couldn	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	hold	O	-	-
10	us	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Can	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	t	O	-	-
15	hold	O	-	-
16	us	O	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Diet_Mountain_Dew-004
# text = Diet Mountain Dew, baby, New York City
1	Diet	O	-	-
2	Mountain	O	-	-
3	Dew	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	baby	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	New	B-LOC	-	-
8	York	I-LOC	-	-
9	City	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Black_or_White-048
# text = Shamone, don't (Yeah, yeah, yeah)
1	Shamone	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Yeah	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yeah	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	yeah	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Hungry-039
# text = Ferrari Fergie
1	Ferrari	B-PER	-	-
2	Fergie	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Beautiful-023
# text = Yes, words can't bring you down, oh no
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	words	O	-	-
4	can	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	bring	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	down	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	oh	O	-	-
12	no	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Filthy-037
# text = Look closer, through the trees
1	Look	O	-	-
2	closer	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	through	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	trees	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Ultraviolence-018
# text = Jim taught me that, loving him was never enough
1	Jim	B-PER	-	-
2	taught	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	loving	O	-	-
7	him	O	-	-
8	was	O	-	-
9	never	O	-	-
10	enough	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Darling_Nikki-030
# text = Oh, Nikki, oh
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Nikki	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	oh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Rip_Her_To_Shreds-008
# text = She thinks she's Brenda Starr
1	She	O	-	-
2	thinks	O	-	-
3	she	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	Brenda	B-PER	-	-
7	Starr	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Pink-017
# text = Hey, Barbie, I like your style
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Barbie	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	your	O	-	-
8	style	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Rapture-014
# text = France Soir c'est pas Flash et Nous Deux
1	France	B-LOC	-	-
2	Soir	O	-	-
3	c	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	est	O	-	-
6	pas	O	-	-
7	Flash	O	-	-
8	et	O	-	-
9	Nous	O	-	-
10	Deux	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Finesse-005
# text = When I walk in witchu (When I walk in witchu)
1	When	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	walk	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	witchu	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	When	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	walk	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	witchu	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Bloody_Mary-004
# text = When Punktious comes to kill the king upon his throne
1	When	O	-	-
2	Punktious	B-PER	-	-
3	comes	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	kill	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	king	O	-	-
8	upon	O	-	-
9	his	O	-	-
10	throne	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Darling_Nikki-031
# text = Come back, Nikki, come back
1	Come	O	-	-
2	back	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Nikki	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	come	O	-	-
7	back	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Drunk_in_Love-045
# text = "Now eat the cake, Anna Mae," said, "Eat the cake, Anna Mae"
1	"	O	-	-
2	Now	O	-	-
3	eat	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	cake	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Anna	B-PER	-	-
8	Mae	I-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	"	O	-	-
11	said	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	"	O	-	-
14	Eat	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	cake	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	Anna	B-PER	-	-
19	Mae	I-PER	-	-
20	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Speed_Drive-006
# text = Kawaii like we're in Tokyo
1	Kawaii	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	re	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Tokyo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_You_Already_Know-031
# text = And since I came in the game, they careers on death row
1	And	O	-	-
2	since	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	came	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	game	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	they	O	-	-
10	careers	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	death	O	-	-
13	row	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-077
# text = China's under martial law
1	China	B-LOC	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	under	O	-	-
5	martial	O	-	-
6	law	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Emotions-012
# text = In the morning when I rise
1	In	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	morning	O	-	-
4	when	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	rise	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Brooklyn_Baby-012
# text = He plays guitar while I sing Lou Reed
1	He	O	-	-
2	plays	O	-	-
3	guitar	O	-	-
4	while	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	sing	O	-	-
7	Lou	B-PER	-	-
8	Reed	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Help_Me_Rhonda-005
# text = For you to help me, Rhonda
1	For	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	help	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Rhonda	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Smooth_Criminal-036
# text = It was your doom, Annie
1	It	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	doom	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Annie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_The_Downeaster_Alexa_-005
# text = We took on diesel back in Montauk yesterday
1	We	O	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	diesel	O	-	-
5	back	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Montauk	B-LOC	-	-
8	yesterday	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Holiday-029
# text = Come on, let's celebrate
1	Come	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	let	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	s	O	-	-
7	celebrate	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-065
# text = Richard Nixon back again
1	Richard	B-PER	-	-
2	Nixon	I-PER	-	-
3	back	O	-	-
4	again	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-040
# text = Barbara Ann, Barbara Ann
1	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
2	Ann	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
5	Ann	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Chained_To_The_Rhythm-030
# text = Ayy, up inna your high place, liars
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	inna	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	high	O	-	-
7	place	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	liars	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-042
# text = Ginger Rogers dance on air
1	Ginger	B-PER	-	-
2	Rogers	I-PER	-	-
3	dance	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	air	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Dirty_Diana-022
# text = It's Diana, -iana, -iana
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	Diana	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	iana	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	iana	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Bubble_Pop_Electric-058
# text = Johnny, get outta here!
1	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	get	O	-	-
4	outta	O	-	-
5	here	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_New_York_State_of_Mind-005
# text = On the Hudson River line
1	On	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Hudson	B-LOC	-	-
4	River	I-LOC	-	-
5	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Heal_the_World-032
# text = Be God's glow
1	Be	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	glow	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Fantasy-007
# text = Darling, if you only knew
1	Darling	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	if	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	only	O	-	-
6	knew	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_California_Girls-019
# text = I wish they all could be California (Girls, girls, girls yeah, I dig the—)
1	I	O	-	-
2	wish	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	could	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	California	B-LOC	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Girls	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	girls	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	girls	O	-	-
14	yeah	O	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	I	O	-	-
17	dig	O	-	-
18	the	O	-	-
19	—	O	-	-
20	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Into_the_Groove-013
# text = We might be lovers if the rhythm's right
1	We	O	-	-
2	might	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	lovers	O	-	-
5	if	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	rhythm	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	right	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_National_Anthem-005
# text = Take me to the Hamptons, Bugatti Veyron
1	Take	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Hamptons	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Bugatti	O	-	-
8	Veyron	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kelly_Clarkson_Miss_Independent-043
# text = How beautiful love could truly be
1	How	O	-	-
2	beautiful	O	-	-
3	love	O	-	-
4	could	O	-	-
5	truly	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Barbra_Streisand_I_Finally_Found_Someone-008
# text = The best things begin
1	The	O	-	-
2	best	O	-	-
3	things	O	-	-
4	begin	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-012
# text = Barbara Ann, bar, bar, bar, Barbara Ann
1	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
2	Ann	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	bar	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	bar	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	bar	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
11	Ann	I-PER	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Elton_John_Saturday_Night_s_Alright_For_Fighting_
# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Saturday_Night_s_Alright_For_Fighting_-001
# text = It's getting late, have you seen my mates?
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	getting	O	-	-
5	late	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	have	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	seen	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	mates	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-039
# text = Grace Kelly, Harlow, Jean
1	Grace	B-PER	-	-
2	Kelly	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Harlow	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Jean	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Fernando-006
# text = They were closer now, Fernando
1	They	O	-	-
2	were	O	-	-
3	closer	O	-	-
4	now	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Fernando	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Valerie_BBC_Radio_1_Live_Lounge_-012
# text = Valerie, yeah
1	Valerie	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Beauty_And_A_Beat-003
# text = Nicki Minaj
1	Nicki	B-PER	-	-
2	Minaj	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Jenny_from_the_Block_Track_Masters_Remix_-037
# text = Put God first and can't forget to stay real (Real)
1	Put	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	first	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	can	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	t	O	-	-
8	forget	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	stay	O	-	-
11	real	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Real	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-037
# text = Mickey Mantle, Kerouac
1	Mickey	B-PER	-	-
2	Mantle	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Kerouac	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-020
# text = Take my hand (Ah, bar, bar, bar, bar, Barbara Ann)
1	Take	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	hand	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Ah	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	bar	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	bar	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	bar	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	bar	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
16	Ann	I-PER	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_California_Girls-009
# text = I wish they all could be California girls
1	I	O	-	-
2	wish	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	could	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	California	B-LOC	-	-
8	girls	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Dirty_Diana-038
# text = C'mon! (Dirty Diana)
1	C	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	mon	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Dirty	O	-	-
7	Diana	B-PER	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_1999-006
# text = Nike Airs, All That
1	Nike	B-ORG	-	-
2	Airs	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	All	O	-	-
5	That	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Whitney_Houston_I_Look_to_You-005
# text = Winter storms have come
1	Winter	O	-	-
2	storms	O	-	-
3	have	O	-	-
4	come	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-023
# text = Brooklyn saying (La-la-la-la-la)
1	Brooklyn	B-LOC	-	-
2	saying	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	La	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	la	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	la	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	la	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	la	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_California_Gurls-060
# text = California
1	California	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Bennie_And_The_Jets-024
# text = Bennie, Bennie, Bennie, Bennie, Bennie, Bennie, Bennie, Bennie and the Jets, the Jets, the Jets
1	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
16	and	O	-	-
17	the	O	-	-
18	Jets	B-ORG	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	the	O	-	-
21	Jets	B-ORG	-	-
22	,	O	-	-
23	the	O	-	-
24	Jets	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Just_One_Lifetime-012
# text = Sting come sing out fi everybody
1	Sting	B-PER	-	-
2	come	O	-	-
3	sing	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	fi	O	-	-
6	everybody	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Versace_on_the_Floor-021
# text = I'll be right here ready to hold you
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	right	O	-	-
6	here	O	-	-
7	ready	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	hold	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-025
# text = Alejandro, Alejandro
1	Alejandro	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Alejandro	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Me_Mr_Jones-019
# text = Side from Sammy you're my best black Jew (Best black Jew)
1	Side	O	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	Sammy	B-PER	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	re	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	best	O	-	-
9	black	O	-	-
10	Jew	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Best	O	-	-
13	black	O	-	-
14	Jew	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Special-010
# text = That's why I move the way I move and why I'm so in love with me
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	why	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	move	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	way	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	move	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	why	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	m	O	-	-
16	so	O	-	-
17	in	O	-	-
18	love	O	-	-
19	with	O	-	-
20	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Someone_To_Call_My_Lover-004
# text = "You gotta do it different, J, this time"
1	"	O	-	-
2	You	O	-	-
3	gotta	O	-	-
4	do	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	different	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	J	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	this	O	-	-
11	time	O	-	-
12	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_thank_u_next-028
# text = 'Cause her name is Ari
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	her	O	-	-
4	name	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	Ari	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_You_Already_Know-021
# text = Now Fergie back with a bag full of tricksies, what
1	Now	O	-	-
2	Fergie	B-PER	-	-
3	back	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	bag	O	-	-
7	full	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	tricksies	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	what	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_No_Strings_Attached-030
# text = Lance: Ah...
1	Lance	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Ah	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_We_Can_t_Stop-017
# text = Dancin' with Molly
1	Dancin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	with	O	-	-
4	Molly	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Dance_Again-048
# text = Little bit of voli, and she'll open sesame
1	Little	O	-	-
2	bit	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	voli	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	she	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	ll	O	-	-
10	open	O	-	-
11	sesame	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_Jesus_to_a_Child-039
# text = Was Jesus to a child
1	Was	O	-	-
2	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	child	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Guess_featuring_billie_eilish-020
# text = The ones I picked out for you in Tokyo
1	The	O	-	-
2	ones	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	picked	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Tokyo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_No_Strings_Attached-032
# text = Justin: Ah...
1	Justin	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Ah	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_New_York_State_of_Mind-026
# text = 'Cause I'm in a, I'm in a New York
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	New	B-LOC	-	-
15	York	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Just_Dance-024
# text = I can't remember, but it's alright, a-alright (Woo)
1	I	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	remember	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	but	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	alright	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	alright	O	-	-
16	(	O	-	-
17	Woo	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sabrina_Carpenter_emails_i_can_t_send-023
# text = I mean, as they say in Chicago
1	I	O	-	-
2	mean	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	as	O	-	-
5	they	O	-	-
6	say	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Chicago	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-032
# text = Tried Mary Lou, but I knew she wouldn't do
1	Tried	O	-	-
2	Mary	B-PER	-	-
3	Lou	I-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	but	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	knew	O	-	-
8	she	O	-	-
9	wouldn	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	do	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman-043
# text = Candyman
1	Candyman	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-035
# text = Greta Garbo, and Monroe
1	Greta	B-PER	-	-
2	Garbo	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Monroe	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Radio-020
# text = Now I'm in L.A. and it's paradise
1	Now	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	L	B-LOC	-	-
7	.	I-LOC	-	-
8	A	I-LOC	-	-
9	.	I-LOC	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	paradise	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Medellín-042
# text = No' vamo', no' vamo', no vamo' pa' Medallo (Ay, qué rico)
1	No	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	vamo	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	no	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	vamo	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	no	O	-	-
12	vamo	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	pa	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	Medallo	B-LOC	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Ay	O	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	qué	O	-	-
21	rico	O	-	-
22	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_All_I_Have-043
# text = I thought my tender touch could lock you down (Yeah)
1	I	O	-	-
2	thought	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	tender	O	-	-
5	touch	O	-	-
6	could	O	-	-
7	lock	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	down	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Yeah	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Just_Dance-030
# text = Shorty, I can see that you got so much energy
1	Shorty	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	can	O	-	-
5	see	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-
10	much	O	-	-
11	energy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_We_Can_t_Stop-002
# text = It's our party, we can say what we want (Mike WILL Made-It, ooh)
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	our	O	-	-
5	party	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	we	O	-	-
8	can	O	-	-
9	say	O	-	-
10	what	O	-	-
11	we	O	-	-
12	want	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Mike	B-PER	-	-
15	WILL	I-PER	-	-
16	Made	I-PER	-	-
17	-	I-PER	-	-
18	It	I-PER	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	ooh	O	-	-
21	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billie_Eilish_everything_i_wanted-008
# text = So I stepped off the Golden, mm
1	So	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	stepped	O	-	-
4	off	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Golden	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	mm	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Sloop_John_B-008
# text = So hoist up the John B's sail
1	So	O	-	-
2	hoist	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	John	B-PER	-	-
6	B	I-PER	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	sail	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Denis-004
# text = Denis Denis, oh with your eyes so blue
1	Denis	B-PER	-	-
2	Denis	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	oh	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	eyes	O	-	-
8	so	O	-	-
9	blue	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Don_t_Phunk_With_My_Heart-003
# text = Yeah
1	Yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_34_35-046
# text = We can take it from the top (From the top)
1	We	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	top	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	From	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	top	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_Love_Story
# sent_id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_Love_Story-001
# text = We were both young when I first saw you
1	We	O	-	-
2	were	O	-	-
3	both	O	-	-
4	young	O	-	-
5	when	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	first	O	-	-
8	saw	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-068
# text = Mýa (*Oh, oh, ooh, yeah*)
1	Mýa	B-PER	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	*	O	-	-
4	Oh	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	oh	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	ooh	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	yeah	O	-	-
11	*	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-ABBA_Chiquitita
# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Chiquitita-001
# text = Chiquitita, tell me what's wrong
1	Chiquitita	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	tell	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	what	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	wrong	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Labels_Or_Love-033
# text = Buying things is hard to say, rocking Christian Audigier
1	Buying	O	-	-
2	things	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	hard	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	say	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	rocking	O	-	-
9	Christian	B-PER	-	-
10	Audigier	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Hungry-025
# text = Rolls Royce and we call this Wraith (Woo)
1	Rolls	B-ORG	-	-
2	Royce	I-ORG	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	call	O	-	-
6	this	O	-	-
7	Wraith	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Woo	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Wake_Up_in_the_Sky-024
# text = Unforgettable (Woo), like Nat King Cole (Huh)
1	Unforgettable	O	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	Woo	O	-	-
4	)	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	Nat	B-PER	-	-
8	King	I-PER	-	-
9	Cole	I-PER	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Huh	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Heartbreaker-080
# text = Heartbreaker, you got the best of me (Boy, if I do)
1	Heartbreaker	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	best	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Boy	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	if	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	do	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_Jesus_to_a_Child-003
# text = You smiled at me like Jesus to a child
1	You	O	-	-
2	smiled	O	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	child	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Partition-025
# text = Yoncé all on his mouth like liquor
1	Yoncé	B-PER	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	his	O	-	-
5	mouth	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	liquor	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Naked_In_Manhattan-035
# text = I want all of your love (Naked in Manhattan)
1	I	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	all	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	love	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Naked	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Manhattan	B-LOC	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Don_t_Lie-048
# text = Hmm, yo, I'm lyin' to my girl
1	Hmm	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yo	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	lyin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	my	O	-	-
12	girl	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Rumors-041
# text = And my records live in the top ten
1	And	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	records	O	-	-
4	live	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	top	O	-	-
8	ten	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Any_Time_Any_Place-012
# text = You feel so good inside of my love
1	You	O	-	-
2	feel	O	-	-
3	so	O	-	-
4	good	O	-	-
5	inside	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	love	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Celine_Dion_O_Holy_Night-010
# text = O night when Christ was born
1	O	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	when	O	-	-
4	Christ	B-PER	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	born	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Can_t_Hold_Us_Down-056
# text = And Lil' Kim and Christina Aguilera got your back
1	And	O	-	-
2	Lil	B-PER	-	-
3	'	I-PER	-	-
4	Kim	I-PER	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	Christina	B-PER	-	-
7	Aguilera	I-PER	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	your	O	-	-
10	back	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Don_t_Phunk_With_My_Heart-029
# text = That's how much I'm in love wit’ chu
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	how	O	-	-
5	much	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	love	O	-	-
11	wit	O	-	-
12	’	O	-	-
13	chu	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-One_Direction_Strong-008
# text = Don't wanna wait till it's gone
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	wanna	O	-	-
5	wait	O	-	-
6	till	O	-	-
7	it	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	gone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Club_classics-013
# text = Tight like Mike kinda flow
1	Tight	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	Mike	B-PER	-	-
4	kinda	O	-	-
5	flow	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Can_t_Hold_Us_Down-050
# text = Cats take my ideas and put they name on it
1	Cats	O	-	-
2	take	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	ideas	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	put	O	-	-
7	they	O	-	-
8	name	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-065
# text = Christina (Hey, oh)
1	Christina	B-PER	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	Hey	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	oh	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_It_s_Still_Rock_and_Roll_to_Me-024
# text = You could really be a Beau Brummel baby
1	You	O	-	-
2	could	O	-	-
3	really	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	Beau	B-PER	-	-
7	Brummel	I-PER	-	-
8	baby	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Bubble_Pop_Electric-003
# text = You just get yourself dolled up, alright Toots?
1	You	O	-	-
2	just	O	-	-
3	get	O	-	-
4	yourself	O	-	-
5	dolled	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	alright	O	-	-
9	Toots	B-PER	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-041
# text = (Fernando)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Fernando	B-PER	-	-
3	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Casual-032
# text = Two weeks and your mom invites me to her Long Beach house
1	Two	O	-	-
2	weeks	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	your	O	-	-
5	mom	O	-	-
6	invites	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	her	O	-	-
10	Long	B-LOC	-	-
11	Beach	I-LOC	-	-
12	house	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Pink-003
# text = Hey, Barbie (Hey), she's so cool
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Barbie	B-PER	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Hey	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	she	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	so	O	-	-
12	cool	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Chiquitita-015
# text = Chiquitita, you and I know
1	Chiquitita	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	know	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-037
# text = Marlon Brando, Jimmy Dean
1	Marlon	B-PER	-	-
2	Brando	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Jimmy	B-PER	-	-
5	Dean	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Guess_featuring_billie_eilish-019
# text = It's that lacy black pair with the little bows
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	lacy	O	-	-
6	black	O	-	-
7	pair	O	-	-
8	with	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	little	O	-	-
11	bows	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Formation-008
# text = You mix that negro with that Creole, make a Texas bama
1	You	O	-	-
2	mix	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	negro	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	Creole	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	make	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
12	bama	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Labels_Or_Love-029
# text = Gucci, Fendi, Prada purses, purchasing them finer things
1	Gucci	B-ORG	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Fendi	B-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Prada	B-ORG	-	-
6	purses	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	purchasing	O	-	-
9	them	O	-	-
10	finer	O	-	-
11	things	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_This_Is_How_We_Do-039
# text = This is how we do, do-do-do-do (It's how we do, straight stunting like that)
1	This	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	how	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	do	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	do	O	-	-
8	-	O	-	-
9	do	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	do	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	do	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	It	O	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	s	O	-	-
18	how	O	-	-
19	we	O	-	-
20	do	O	-	-
21	,	O	-	-
22	straight	O	-	-
23	stunting	O	-	-
24	like	O	-	-
25	that	O	-	-
26	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_We_Belong_Together-024
# text = Bobby Womack's on the radio
1	Bobby	B-PER	-	-
2	Womack	I-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	radio	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-P_nk_So_What-024
# text = I guess I'll go sit with drum boy
1	I	O	-	-
2	guess	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ll	O	-	-
6	go	O	-	-
7	sit	O	-	-
8	with	O	-	-
9	drum	O	-	-
10	boy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-037
# text = Bye, Fernando
1	Bye	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Fernando	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Dance_Again-007
# text = No way, José
1	No	O	-	-
2	way	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	José	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Bad_Habits-002
# text = Ooh, ooh
1	Ooh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	ooh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-018
# text = I just booked a Paris ticket
1	I	O	-	-
2	just	O	-	-
3	booked	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	Paris	B-LOC	-	-
6	ticket	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Soulmate-009
# text = But I'm solo in Soho, sippin' Soju in Malibu
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	solo	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Soho	B-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	sippin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	Soju	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	Malibu	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Just_Can_t_Get_Enough-021
# text = Honey got me runnin' like I'm Flo-Jo
1	Honey	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	runnin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	m	O	-	-
10	Flo	B-PER	-	-
11	-	I-PER	-	-
12	Jo	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-P_nk_A_Million_Dreams-025
# text = Oh, a million dreams for the world we’re gonna make
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	million	O	-	-
5	dreams	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	world	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	’	O	-	-
11	re	O	-	-
12	gonna	O	-	-
13	make	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Here_I_Come-040
# text = Buy you Long Island, but my name ain't Gilligan
1	Buy	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	Long	B-LOC	-	-
4	Island	I-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	but	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	name	O	-	-
9	ain	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	Gilligan	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_FEEL_THE_BEAT-036
# text = Mami, tienes tetas grandes pero natural
1	Mami	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	tienes	O	-	-
4	tetas	O	-	-
5	grandes	O	-	-
6	pero	O	-	-
7	natural	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Zanzibar-005
# text = Me, I'm just another face at Zanzibar
1	Me	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	just	O	-	-
7	another	O	-	-
8	face	O	-	-
9	at	O	-	-
10	Zanzibar	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Judas-030
# text = And Judas is the demon I cling to
1	And	O	-	-
2	Judas	B-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	demon	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	cling	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_The_Longest_Time-011
# text = Now I know that happiness goes on
1	Now	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	know	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	happiness	O	-	-
6	goes	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_FEEL_THE_BEAT-057
# text = Mami, dame dulce, dame caramel
1	Mami	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	dame	O	-	-
4	dulce	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	dame	O	-	-
7	caramel	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-034
# text = Princess Grace, Peyton Place
1	Princess	O	-	-
2	Grace	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Peyton	B-LOC	-	-
5	Place	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Russians-010
# text = From Oppenheimer's deadly toy?
1	From	O	-	-
2	Oppenheimer	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	deadly	O	-	-
6	toy	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Exactly_How_I_Feel-030
# text = The fye close by like it's Whitney
1	The	O	-	-
2	fye	O	-	-
3	close	O	-	-
4	by	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	Whitney	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Wake_Up_in_the_Sky-025
# text = Gucci Barry White, I'm singing to your ho (Well damn)
1	Gucci	B-PER	-	-
2	Barry	B-PER	-	-
3	White	I-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	singing	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	your	O	-	-
11	ho	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Well	O	-	-
14	damn	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Hey_Mama-047
# text = From the crew (BEP)
1	From	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	crew	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	BEP	B-ORG	-	-
6	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Nothing_Compares_2_U-011
# text = It's been so lonely without you here
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	so	O	-	-
6	lonely	O	-	-
7	without	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	here	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-037
# text = Go down to Kokomo
1	Go	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	Kokomo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_The_One_That_Got_Away-014
# text = I was June, and you were my Johnny Cash
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	June	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	were	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
10	Cash	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Little_Saint_Nick-017
# text = With a half a dozen deer with Rudy to lead
1	With	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	half	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	dozen	O	-	-
6	deer	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	Rudy	B-PER	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	lead	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Morning_Is_Coming-003
# text = Only when I see Sting
1	Only	O	-	-
2	when	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	see	O	-	-
5	Sting	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Union_City_Blue-015
# text = I say, "He's my Union City man"
1	I	O	-	-
2	say	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	He	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	Union	B-LOC	-	-
10	City	I-LOC	-	-
11	man	O	-	-
12	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Coldplay_Speed_of_Sound-027
# text = Japan and China all lit up
1	Japan	B-LOC	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	China	B-LOC	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	lit	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Adele_Turning_Tables-009
# text = I can't give you the heart you think you gave me
1	I	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	give	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	heart	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	think	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	gave	O	-	-
13	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-007
# text = She said, "Hello, hey, Joe, you wanna give it a go?"
1	She	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	Hello	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	hey	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Joe	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	wanna	O	-	-
13	give	O	-	-
14	it	O	-	-
15	a	O	-	-
16	go	O	-	-
17	?	O	-	-
18	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-010
# text = Gitchie, gitchie, ya-ya, here (Here, oh)
1	Gitchie	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	gitchie	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	ya	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	ya	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	here	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Here	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	oh	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_A_Little_Work-002
# text = 'Bout time I talk to somebody, shrink my head
1	'	O	-	-
2	Bout	O	-	-
3	time	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	talk	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	somebody	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	shrink	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	head	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_FEEL_THE_BEAT-028
# text = Baby girl, you my superstar
1	Baby	O	-	-
2	girl	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	superstar	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Surfin_Safari-011
# text = At Huntington and Malibu, they're shooting the pier
1	At	O	-	-
2	Huntington	B-LOC	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	Malibu	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	they	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	re	O	-	-
9	shooting	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	pier	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Touch_My_Body-028
# text = And float away with you in the Caribbean Sea
1	And	O	-	-
2	float	O	-	-
3	away	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	Caribbean	B-LOC	-	-
9	Sea	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-075
# text = AIDS, crack, Bernie Goetz
1	AIDS	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	crack	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Bernie	B-PER	-	-
6	Goetz	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Celine_Dion_Happy_Xmas_War_Is_Over_-010
# text = And a happy New Year
1	And	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	happy	O	-	-
4	New	O	-	-
5	Year	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Surfin_Safari-016
# text = They're kicking out in Doheny too
1	They	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	kicking	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Doheny	B-LOC	-	-
8	too	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Bennie_And_The_Jets-013
# text = B-B-B-Bennie and the Jets
1	B	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	B	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	B	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Jets	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_RITMO_Bad_Boys_for_Life_-020
# text = Como Canelo en el ring nada me asusta
1	Como	O	-	-
2	Canelo	B-LOC	-	-
3	en	O	-	-
4	el	O	-	-
5	ring	O	-	-
6	nada	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	asusta	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Intentions-023
# text = You're my rock, my Colorado
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	rock	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	Colorado	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_California-013
# text = Thought I'd be cool in California
1	Thought	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	d	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	cool	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	California	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Billie_Jean-032
# text = Billie Jean is not my lover (Hoo)
1	Billie	B-PER	-	-
2	Jean	I-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	not	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	lover	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Hoo	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_We_Can_t_Stop-043
# text = We can do what we want, do what we want to (Ayy)
1	We	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	what	O	-	-
5	we	O	-	-
6	want	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	do	O	-	-
9	what	O	-	-
10	we	O	-	-
11	want	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Ayy	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_Party_In_The_U_S_A_-006
# text = Look to my right, and I see the Hollywood sign
1	Look	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	right	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	see	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
11	sign	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Dirty_Diana-034
# text = C'mon! (Dirty Diana) (Hey, hey)
1	C	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	mon	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Dirty	O	-	-
7	Diana	B-PER	-	-
8	)	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Hey	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	hey	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-064
# text = And here we are waving Brenda and Eddie goodbye
1	And	O	-	-
2	here	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	are	O	-	-
5	waving	O	-	-
6	Brenda	B-PER	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	Eddie	B-PER	-	-
9	goodbye	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Maroon_5_Memories-008
# text = And the memories bring back, memories bring back you
1	And	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	memories	O	-	-
4	bring	O	-	-
5	back	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	memories	O	-	-
8	bring	O	-	-
9	back	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-041
# text = Gene Kelly, Fred Astaire
1	Gene	B-PER	-	-
2	Kelly	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Fred	B-PER	-	-
5	Astaire	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kelly_Clarkson_Catch_My_Breath-025
# text = The beauty in everything
1	The	O	-	-
2	beauty	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	everything	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Summer_Love-031
# text = Come on, baby, please, 'cause I'm on my knees
1	Come	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	baby	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	please	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	cause	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	m	O	-	-
13	on	O	-	-
14	my	O	-	-
15	knees	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Guess_featuring_billie_eilish
# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Guess_featuring_billie_eilish-001
# text = Hey, Billie, you there?
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Billie	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	there	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_God_Only_Knows-016
# text = God only knows what I'd be without you (God only knows)
1	God	O	-	-
2	only	O	-	-
3	knows	O	-	-
4	what	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	d	O	-	-
8	be	O	-	-
9	without	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	God	B-PER	-	-
13	only	O	-	-
14	knows	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-017
# text = Do you remember those days hanging out at the Village Green?
1	Do	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	remember	O	-	-
4	those	O	-	-
5	days	O	-	-
6	hanging	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Village	B-LOC	-	-
11	Green	I-LOC	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_London_Bridge-034
# text = Fergie like' 'em long time, my girls support, right? (Oh, shit)
1	Fergie	B-PER	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	em	O	-	-
6	long	O	-	-
7	time	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	my	O	-	-
10	girls	O	-	-
11	support	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	right	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-
15	(	O	-	-
16	Oh	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	shit	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_If_You_Had_My_Love-032
# text = And if somehow you knew that your love would be untrue (I need to know, be untrue)
1	And	O	-	-
2	if	O	-	-
3	somehow	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	knew	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	your	O	-	-
8	love	O	-	-
9	would	O	-	-
10	be	O	-	-
11	untrue	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	need	O	-	-
15	to	O	-	-
16	know	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	be	O	-	-
19	untrue	O	-	-
20	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_New_York_State_of_Mind-017
# text = The New York Times, the Daily News
1	The	B-ORG	-	-
2	New	I-ORG	-	-
3	York	I-ORG	-	-
4	Times	I-ORG	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	the	B-ORG	-	-
7	Daily	B-ORG	-	-
8	News	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_I_m_Into_You-038
# text = I'm into you (Ayy, hahah!)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	into	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Ayy	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	hahah	O	-	-
10	!	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_4_In_The_Morning-009
# text = And all I know is
1	And	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Die_With_A_Smile-004
# text = And I don't know what it all means
1	And	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	know	O	-	-
7	what	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	all	O	-	-
10	means	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_The_Climb-028
# text = Sometimes you're gonna have to lose
1	Sometimes	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	re	O	-	-
5	gonna	O	-	-
6	have	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	lose	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Spice_Girls_Spice_Up_Your_Life-024
# text = Arriba! (*Ariba!*)
1	Arriba	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	*	O	-	-
5	Ariba	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	*	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-P_nk_TRUSTFALL-003
# text = Picture a place where it all doesn't hurt
1	Picture	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	place	O	-	-
4	where	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	doesn	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	t	O	-	-
10	hurt	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billie_Eilish_Therefore_I_Am-023
# text = I'm sorry
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	sorry	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Drunk_in_Love-043
# text = Beat the box up like Mike in '97, I bite
1	Beat	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	box	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Mike	B-PER	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	97	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	bite	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kelly_Clarkson_Stronger_What_Doesn_t_Kill_You_-012
# text = Stand a little taller
1	Stand	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	little	O	-	-
4	taller	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_That_s_The_Way_Love_Goes-021
# text = I'm gonna give you all my love (That's the way love goes)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	gonna	O	-	-
5	give	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	all	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	love	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	That	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	way	O	-	-
16	love	O	-	-
17	goes	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_What_You_Waiting_For_-032
# text = You Harajuku girls
1	You	O	-	-
2	Harajuku	B-LOC	-	-
3	girls	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_Into_You-023
# text = Made too many mistakes
1	Made	O	-	-
2	too	O	-	-
3	many	O	-	-
4	mistakes	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-015
# text = You're my pretty little Galway Girl
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	pretty	O	-	-
6	little	O	-	-
7	Galway	B-LOC	-	-
8	Girl	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Mirrors-046
# text = Show me how to fight for now (You show me, baby)
1	Show	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	how	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	fight	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	now	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	You	O	-	-
10	show	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	baby	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_I_Want_Your_Sex_Pts_1_2-057
# text = Don't you know I love it 'til it hurts me baby?
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	know	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	love	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	til	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	hurts	O	-	-
13	me	O	-	-
14	baby	O	-	-
15	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_You_Already_Know-055
# text = Come and see me at a venue near you
1	Come	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	see	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	at	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	venue	O	-	-
8	near	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Holy-030
# text = But they don't see you how I see you, Parlay and Desi
1	But	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	see	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	how	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	see	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Parlay	B-PER	-	-
14	and	O	-	-
15	Desi	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Gimme_More-002
# text = I see you
1	I	O	-	-
2	see	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Bloody_Mary-021
# text = I'll wait on mountaintops in Paris, cold
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	wait	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	mountaintops	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Paris	B-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	cold	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Rock_Your_Body-049
# text = Don't be so quick to walk away (I like the way you look right now)
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	so	O	-	-
6	quick	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	walk	O	-	-
9	away	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	like	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	way	O	-	-
15	you	O	-	-
16	look	O	-	-
17	right	O	-	-
18	now	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Seven_Days-031
# text = It makes me think
1	It	O	-	-
2	makes	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	think	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_That_s_What_I_Like-013
# text = Julio, serve that scampi (Julio!)
1	Julio	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	serve	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	scampi	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Julio	B-PER	-	-
8	!	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Rock_That_Body-016
# text = Galactic comb and Mr. Spock
1	Galactic	O	-	-
2	comb	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	Mr	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	Spock	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billie_Eilish_i_love_you-026
# text = I'm in your arms in Central Park
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	arms	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Central	B-LOC	-	-
9	Park	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Lust_For_Life-011
# text = Take off, take off, take off all your clothes
1	Take	O	-	-
2	off	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	take	O	-	-
5	off	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	take	O	-	-
8	off	O	-	-
9	all	O	-	-
10	your	O	-	-
11	clothes	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_My_Love-034
# text = But he still has fans from Peru to Japan
1	But	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	still	O	-	-
4	has	O	-	-
5	fans	O	-	-
6	from	O	-	-
7	Peru	B-LOC	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Japan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Fernando-019
# text = Now we're old and grey, Fernando
1	Now	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	re	O	-	-
5	old	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	grey	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Fernando	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Ultraviolence-006
# text = Jim brought me back, reminded me of when we were kids
1	Jim	B-PER	-	-
2	brought	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	back	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	reminded	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	when	O	-	-
10	we	O	-	-
11	were	O	-	-
12	kids	O	-	-
