# sent_id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_Love_Story-021
# text = 'Cause you were Romeo, I was a scarlet letter
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	were	O	-	-
5	Romeo	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	was	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	scarlet	O	-	-
11	letter	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Ultraviolence-018
# text = Jim taught me that, loving him was never enough
1	Jim	B-PER	-	-
2	taught	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	loving	O	-	-
7	him	O	-	-
8	was	O	-	-
9	never	O	-	-
10	enough	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Suit_Tie-037
# text = Get out your seat, Hov
1	Get	O	-	-
2	out	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	seat	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Hov	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Rip_Her_To_Shreds-015
# text = Yeah, you know her, "Vera Vogue" on parade
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	her	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	"	O	-	-
8	Vera	B-PER	-	-
9	Vogue	I-PER	-	-
10	"	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	parade	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-015
# text = To Bermuda, Bahama, come on, pretty mama
1	To	O	-	-
2	Bermuda	B-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Bahama	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	come	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	pretty	O	-	-
10	mama	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Bloody_Mary-004
# text = When Punktious comes to kill the king upon his throne
1	When	O	-	-
2	Punktious	B-PER	-	-
3	comes	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	kill	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	king	O	-	-
8	upon	O	-	-
9	his	O	-	-
10	throne	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Pink_Pony_Club-002
# text = But I can't ignore the crazy visions of me in L.A.
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	can	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	ignore	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	crazy	O	-	-
9	visions	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	L	B-LOC	-	-
14	.	I-LOC	-	-
15	A	I-LOC	-	-
16	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_Don_t_Let_the_Sun_Go_Down_on_Me-026
# text = Mr. Elton John
1	Mr	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Elton	B-PER	-	-
4	John	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Little_Saint_Nick-017
# text = With a half a dozen deer with Rudy to lead
1	With	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	half	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	dozen	O	-	-
6	deer	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	Rudy	B-PER	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	lead	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_The_Sweet_Escape
# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_The_Sweet_Escape-001
# text = Konvict, Konvict, Konvict
1	Konvict	B-ORG	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Konvict	B-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Konvict	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-005
# text = He met Marmalade down in old Moulin Rouge
1	He	O	-	-
2	met	O	-	-
3	Marmalade	B-PER	-	-
4	down	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	old	O	-	-
7	Moulin	B-LOC	-	-
8	Rouge	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_California_Gurls-057
# text = California girls, we're undeniable (-Niable)
1	California	B-LOC	-	-
2	girls	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	re	O	-	-
7	undeniable	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	Niable	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-One_Direction_Olivia-014
# text = I live for you, I long for you, Olivia (Ayy, ayy)
1	I	O	-	-
2	live	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	long	O	-	-
8	for	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Olivia	B-PER	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Ayy	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	ayy	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Dance_Again-035
# text = Modern day Hugh Hef' (Uh, yes)
1	Modern	O	-	-
2	day	O	-	-
3	Hugh	B-PER	-	-
4	Hef	I-PER	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Uh	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yes	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_Party_In_The_U_S_A_
# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_Party_In_The_U_S_A_-001
# text = I hopped off the plane at LAX
1	I	O	-	-
2	hopped	O	-	-
3	off	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	plane	O	-	-
6	at	O	-	-
7	LAX	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman-014
# text = He took me to the Spider Club at Hollywood and Vine
1	He	O	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Spider	B-LOC	-	-
7	Club	I-LOC	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	Vine	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Coldplay_Viva_La_Vida-013
# text = I hear Jerusalem bells a-ringin'
1	I	O	-	-
2	hear	O	-	-
3	Jerusalem	B-LOC	-	-
4	bells	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	ringin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Barracuda-008
# text = Now wouldn't you, Barracuda?
1	Now	O	-	-
2	wouldn	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Barracuda	B-PER	-	-
8	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_7_Things-035
# text = (Sha, sha)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Sha	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	sha	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-025
# text = Alejandro, Alejandro
1	Alejandro	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Alejandro	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Rich_Girl-029
# text = From the hoods of Japan, Harajuku Girls
1	From	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	hoods	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	Japan	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Harajuku	B-LOC	-	-
8	Girls	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Bloody_Mary-027
# text = Oh (Gaga)
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	Gaga	B-PER	-	-
4	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-056
# text = Frisco saying (La-la-la-la-la)
1	Frisco	B-PER	-	-
2	saying	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	La	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	la	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	la	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	la	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	la	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Eenie_Meenie-018
# text = Shorty is a eenie-meenie-miney-mo lover
1	Shorty	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	eenie	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	meenie	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	miney	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	mo	O	-	-
11	lover	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Señorita-006
# text = All the way from Memphis, Tennessee
1	All	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	way	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	Memphis	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_The_One_That_Got_Away-014
# text = I was June, and you were my Johnny Cash
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	June	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	were	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
10	Cash	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Piano_Man-015
# text = Now John at the bar is a friend of mine
1	Now	O	-	-
2	John	B-PER	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	bar	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	friend	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	mine	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_California_Gurls-062
# text = California (Hahahaha)
1	California	B-LOC	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	Hahahaha	O	-	-
4	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-007
# text = She said, "Hello, hey, Joe, you wanna give it a go?"
1	She	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	Hello	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	hey	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Joe	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	wanna	O	-	-
13	give	O	-	-
14	it	O	-	-
15	a	O	-	-
16	go	O	-	-
17	?	O	-	-
18	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Jenny_from_the_Block_Track_Masters_Remix_-054
# text = I'm still, I'm still Jenny from the block (Bronx)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	still	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	still	O	-	-
10	Jenny	B-PER	-	-
11	from	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	block	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Bronx	B-LOC	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Only_the_Good_Die_Young-016
# text = So come on, Virginia, show me a sign
1	So	O	-	-
2	come	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	show	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	sign	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Only_the_Good_Die_Young
# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Only_the_Good_Die_Young-001
# text = Come out, Virginia, don't let me wait
1	Come	O	-	-
2	out	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	don	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	let	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	wait	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Bad_Romance-003
# text = Roma, roma-ma
1	Roma	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	roma	B-LOC	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	ma	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Chained_To_The_Rhythm-030
# text = Ayy, up inna your high place, liars
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	inna	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	high	O	-	-
7	place	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	liars	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Femininomenon-016
# text = (Get it hot) Get it hot like Papa John
1	(	O	-	-
2	Get	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	hot	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	Get	O	-	-
7	it	O	-	-
8	hot	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	Papa	B-PER	-	-
11	John	I-PER	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman
# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman-001
# text = Tarzan and Jane were swingin' on a vine
1	Tarzan	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Jane	B-PER	-	-
4	were	O	-	-
5	swingin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	vine	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-037
# text = Bye, Fernando
1	Bye	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Fernando	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Glamorous-042
# text = Half a million for the stones, takin' trips from here to Rome
1	Half	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	million	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	stones	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	takin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	trips	O	-	-
11	from	O	-	-
12	here	O	-	-
13	to	O	-	-
14	Rome	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Rip_Her_To_Shreds-008
# text = She thinks she's Brenda Starr
1	She	O	-	-
2	thinks	O	-	-
3	she	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	Brenda	B-PER	-	-
7	Starr	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-One_Direction_Olivia-031
# text = Don't let me go, Olivia
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	let	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	go	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Olivia	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_California-013
# text = Thought I'd be cool in California
1	Thought	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	d	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	cool	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	California	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Dance_Again-048
# text = Little bit of voli, and she'll open sesame
1	Little	O	-	-
2	bit	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	voli	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	she	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	ll	O	-	-
10	open	O	-	-
11	sesame	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Jenny_from_the_Block_Track_Masters_Remix_-006
# text = Yeah, yo, yo (Southside Bronx)
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yo	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	yo	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Southside	O	-	-
8	Bronx	I-LOC	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Billie_Jean-013
# text = Billie Jean is not my lover, uh
1	Billie	B-PER	-	-
2	Jean	I-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	not	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	lover	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	uh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_London_Bridge-036
# text = Cali callabo
1	Cali	B-LOC	-	-
2	callabo	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Gimme_More-048
# text = And the unstoppable Danja
1	And	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	unstoppable	O	-	-
4	Danja	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_It_s_Still_Rock_and_Roll_to_Me-029
# text = Alright Richie!
1	Alright	O	-	-
2	Richie	B-PER	-	-
3	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_I_m_Into_You-038
# text = I'm into you (Ayy, hahah!)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	into	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Ayy	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	hahah	O	-	-
10	!	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_California_Gurls-054
# text = 'Cause you representin' California (Oh-oh, yeah)
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	representin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	California	B-LOC	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Oh	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	oh	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	yeah	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Candle_In_The_Wind-027
# text = More than just our Marilyn Monroe
1	More	O	-	-
2	than	O	-	-
3	just	O	-	-
4	our	O	-	-
5	Marilyn	B-PER	-	-
6	Monroe	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_I_Want_You_Back-005
# text = Lance: I...
1	Lance	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Hollaback_Girl-006
# text = I ain't no Hollaback Girl
1	I	O	-	-
2	ain	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	no	O	-	-
6	Hollaback	O	-	-
7	Girl	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Spice_Girls_Christmas_Wrapping-035
# text = Emma:
1	Emma	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Barracuda-032
# text = Barracuda, Barracuda
1	Barracuda	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Barracuda	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_On_The_Floor-045
# text = Dale, así me gusta, así me gusta, así me gusta
1	Dale	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	así	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	gusta	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	así	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	gusta	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	así	O	-	-
12	me	O	-	-
13	gusta	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Maria-009
# text = Maria
1	Maria	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Unlock_It-044
# text = [Breakdown: Charli XCX & Kim
1	[	O	-	-
2	Breakdown	O	-	-
3	:	O	-	-
4	Charli	B-PER	-	-
5	XCX	I-PER	-	-
6	&	O	-	-
7	Kim	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-045
# text = (Roberto)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Roberto	B-PER	-	-
3	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Drink_You_Away-010
# text = I've tried Jack, I've tried Jim, I’ve tried all of their friends
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	tried	O	-	-
5	Jack	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	ve	O	-	-
10	tried	O	-	-
11	Jim	B-PER	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	’	O	-	-
15	ve	O	-	-
16	tried	O	-	-
17	all	O	-	-
18	of	O	-	-
19	their	O	-	-
20	friends	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-065
# text = Christina (Hey, oh)
1	Christina	B-PER	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	Hey	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	oh	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Lust_For_Life-002
# text = Climb up the H of the Hollywood sign (Yeah)
1	Climb	O	-	-
2	up	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	H	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
8	sign	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Yeah	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-039
# text = Barbara Ann, Barbara Ann (Oh, yeah)
1	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
2	Ann	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
5	Ann	I-PER	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Oh	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yeah	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Celine_Dion_O_Holy_Night-010
# text = O night when Christ was born
1	O	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	when	O	-	-
4	Christ	B-PER	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	born	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Coldplay_Speed_of_Sound-027
# text = Japan and China all lit up
1	Japan	B-LOC	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	China	B-LOC	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	lit	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_My_Love-034
# text = But he still has fans from Peru to Japan
1	But	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	still	O	-	-
4	has	O	-	-
5	fans	O	-	-
6	from	O	-	-
7	Peru	B-LOC	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Japan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-063
# text = You on that Cali shit
1	You	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	Cali	B-LOC	-	-
5	shit	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_No_Sleeep-045
# text = Butterflies like MJ, had to fit it in
1	Butterflies	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	MJ	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	had	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	fit	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billie_Eilish_i_love_you-026
# text = I'm in your arms in Central Park
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	arms	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Central	B-LOC	-	-
9	Park	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_All_That_I_Got_The_Make_Up_Song_-042
# text = Without the L'Oreal
1	Without	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	L	B-ORG	-	-
4	'	I-ORG	-	-
5	Oreal	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Sympathy_is_a_knife-006
# text = George says I'm just paranoid
1	George	B-PER	-	-
2	says	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	just	O	-	-
7	paranoid	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sabrina_Carpenter_Espresso-030
# text = Switch it up like Nintendo (Yes)
1	Switch	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Nintendo	B-ORG	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Yes	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Barracuda-029
# text = Ooh, oh, Barra-Barracuda
1	Ooh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	oh	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Barra	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	Barracuda	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-P_nk_Can_We_Pretend-026
# text = How our daddy issues took us to LA
1	How	O	-	-
2	our	O	-	-
3	daddy	O	-	-
4	issues	O	-	-
5	took	O	-	-
6	us	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	LA	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-014
# text = Saw Barbara Ann, so I thought I'd take a chance
1	Saw	O	-	-
2	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
3	Ann	I-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	so	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	thought	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	d	O	-	-
11	take	O	-	-
12	a	O	-	-
13	chance	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Chunky-035
# text = Chunky
1	Chunky	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-031
# text = Tried Peggy Sue, tried Peggy Lou
1	Tried	O	-	-
2	Peggy	B-PER	-	-
3	Sue	I-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	tried	O	-	-
6	Peggy	B-PER	-	-
7	Lou	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-070
# text = Moulin Rouge (Oh-ooh, *da-da*)
1	Moulin	B-LOC	-	-
2	Rouge	I-LOC	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Oh	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	ooh	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	*	O	-	-
9	da	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	da	O	-	-
12	*	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_God_is_a_woman-035
# text = You'll believe God (God is a woman)
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	believe	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	God	B-PER	-	-
8	is	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	woman	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Heartbreaker-068
# text = But she knows she loves Jay because
1	But	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	knows	O	-	-
4	she	O	-	-
5	loves	O	-	-
6	Jay	B-PER	-	-
7	because	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-039
# text = (Alejandro)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Alejandro	B-PER	-	-
3	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Smokin_Out_The_Window-004
# text = Must've spent thirty-five, forty-five thousand up in Tiffany's (Oh no)
1	Must	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	spent	O	-	-
5	thirty	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	five	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	forty	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	five	O	-	-
12	thousand	O	-	-
13	up	O	-	-
14	in	O	-	-
15	Tiffany	B-LOC	-	-
16	'	I-LOC	-	-
17	s	I-LOC	-	-
18	(	O	-	-
19	Oh	O	-	-
20	no	O	-	-
21	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Barbra_Streisand_New_York_State_of_Mind-005
# text = I'm in a New York state of mind
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	New	B-LOC	-	-
7	York	I-LOC	-	-
8	state	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	mind	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Here_I_Come-043
# text = What's the dilly? You can call me Willy
1	What	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	dilly	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	You	O	-	-
8	can	O	-	-
9	call	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	Willy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Born_To_Die-025
# text = All the answers, honey (Louder)
1	All	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	answers	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	honey	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Louder	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Coffee-003
# text = I'd suggest the jazz bar on Mary Ann Street, but
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	d	O	-	-
4	suggest	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	jazz	O	-	-
7	bar	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	Mary	B-LOC	-	-
10	Ann	I-LOC	-	-
11	Street	I-LOC	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	but	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_GIRL_LIKE_ME-062
# text = In East L.A. I like the chicanas
1	In	O	-	-
2	East	O	-	-
3	L	B-LOC	-	-
4	.	I-LOC	-	-
5	A	I-LOC	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	chicanas	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Touch_My_Body-028
# text = And float away with you in the Caribbean Sea
1	And	O	-	-
2	float	O	-	-
3	away	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	Caribbean	B-LOC	-	-
9	Sea	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-029
# text = Miami saying (La-la-la-la-la)
1	Miami	B-LOC	-	-
2	saying	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	La	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	la	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	la	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	la	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	la	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_What_You_Waiting_For_-029
# text = I can't wait to go back and do Japan
1	I	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	wait	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	go	O	-	-
8	back	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	do	O	-	-
11	Japan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Heroes_And_Villains-007
# text = Once at night, cotillion squared the fight
1	Once	O	-	-
2	at	O	-	-
3	night	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	cotillion	O	-	-
6	squared	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	fight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_You_May_Be_Right-008
# text = I walked through Bedford-Stuy alone
1	I	O	-	-
2	walked	O	-	-
3	through	O	-	-
4	Bedford	B-LOC	-	-
5	-	I-LOC	-	-
6	Stuy	I-LOC	-	-
7	alone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Sorry-021
# text = Przepraszam
1	Przepraszam	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Ghost
# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Ghost-001
# text = Youngblood thinks there's always tomorrow
1	Youngblood	B-PER	-	-
2	thinks	O	-	-
3	there	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	always	O	-	-
7	tomorrow	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Video_Games-024
# text = Watchin' all our friends fall in and out of Old Paul's, this is my idea of fun
1	Watchin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	all	O	-	-
4	our	O	-	-
5	friends	O	-	-
6	fall	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	out	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	Old	B-LOC	-	-
12	Paul	I-LOC	-	-
13	'	I-LOC	-	-
14	s	I-LOC	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	this	O	-	-
17	is	O	-	-
18	my	O	-	-
19	idea	O	-	-
20	of	O	-	-
21	fun	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Madonna_Music
# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Music-001
# text = Hey, Mr. DJ, put a record on
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Mr	B-PER	-	-
4	.	I-PER	-	-
5	DJ	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	put	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	record	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Judas-013
# text = But I'm still in love with Judas, baby
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	still	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	love	O	-	-
8	with	O	-	-
9	Judas	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	baby	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-026
# text = Ale-Alejandro, Ale-Alejandro
1	Ale	O	B-PER	-
2	-	O	I-PER	-
3	Alejandro	I-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Ale	O	B-PER	-
6	-	O	I-PER	-
7	Alejandro	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Rich_Girl-022
# text = I'd get me four Harajuku girls to (Uh-huh)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	d	O	-	-
4	get	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	four	O	-	-
7	Harajuku	B-LOC	-	-
8	girls	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Uh	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	huh	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Me_Mr_Jones-012
# text = Rulers one thing, but come Brixton
1	Rulers	O	-	-
2	one	O	-	-
3	thing	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	but	O	-	-
6	come	O	-	-
7	Brixton	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Dirrty-084
# text = Another Rockwilder production
1	Another	O	-	-
2	Rockwilder	B-ORG	-	-
3	production	-	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Bennie_And_The_Jets-010
# text = Oh, Bennie, she's really keen
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	she	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	really	O	-	-
9	keen	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-052
# text = Germany saying (La-la-la-la-la)
1	Germany	B-LOC	-	-
2	saying	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	La	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	la	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	la	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	la	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	la	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Fernando-014
# text = For liberty, Fernando
1	For	O	-	-
2	liberty	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Fernando	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Guess_featuring_billie_eilish-027
# text = Charli, call me if you're with it
1	Charli	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	call	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	if	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	re	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Darling_Nikki-031
# text = Come back, Nikki, come back
1	Come	O	-	-
2	back	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Nikki	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	come	O	-	-
7	back	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_Side_To_Side
# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_Side_To_Side-001
# text = I've been here all night (Ariana)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	here	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	night	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Ariana	B-PER	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Formation-007
# text = My daddy Alabama, momma Louisiana
1	My	O	-	-
2	daddy	O	-	-
3	Alabama	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	momma	O	-	-
6	Louisiana	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Naked_In_Manhattan-017
# text = Like that one sex scene that's in Mulholland Drive
1	Like	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	one	O	-	-
4	sex	O	-	-
5	scene	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Mulholland	B-LOC	-	-
11	Drive	I-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Womanizer
# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Womanizer-001
# text = Superstar, where you from? How's it goin'?
1	Superstar	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	where	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	How	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	goin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-044
# text = Buddy Holly, Ben-Hur
1	Buddy	B-PER	-	-
2	Holly	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Ben	B-ORG	-	-
5	-	I-ORG	-	-
6	Hur	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_Bubble_Pop_Electric-003
# text = You just get yourself dolled up, alright Toots?
1	You	O	-	-
2	just	O	-	-
3	get	O	-	-
4	yourself	O	-	-
5	dolled	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	alright	O	-	-
9	Toots	B-PER	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rihanna_Bitch_Better_Have_My_Money-008
# text = Ballin' bigger than LeBron
1	Ballin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	bigger	O	-	-
4	than	O	-	-
5	LeBron	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Let_s_Go_Crazy-010
# text = So when you call up that shrink in Beverly Hills
1	So	O	-	-
2	when	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	call	O	-	-
5	up	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	shrink	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Beverly	B-LOC	-	-
10	Hills	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-013
# text = Down in Kokomo
1	Down	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	Kokomo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Bitch_I_m_Madonna-030
# text = (Bitch, I'm Madonna, bitch, I'm Madonna) Who do you think you are?
1	(	O	-	-
2	Bitch	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	Madonna	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	bitch	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	Madonna	B-PER	-	-
15	)	O	-	-
16	Who	O	-	-
17	do	O	-	-
18	you	O	-	-
19	think	O	-	-
20	you	O	-	-
21	are	O	-	-
22	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Gwen_Stefani_You_Make_It_Feel_Like_Christmas-012
# text = Like a present sent from God
1	Like	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	present	O	-	-
4	sent	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-072
# text = Wheel of Fortune, Sally Ride
1	Wheel	O	-	-
2	of	O	-	-
3	Fortune	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Sally	B-PER	-	-
6	Ride	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-011
# text = Brando, The King And I,
1	Brando	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	The	O	-	-
4	King	O	-	-
5	And	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-009
# text = Barbara Ann (Bar, bar, bar, bar, Barbara Ann)
1	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
2	Ann	I-PER	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Bar	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	bar	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	bar	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	bar	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
13	Ann	I-PER	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Diet_Mountain_Dew-017
# text = Let's take Jesus off the dashboard
1	Let	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	take	O	-	-
5	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
6	off	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	dashboard	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Lady_Marmalade-056
# text = Gitchie, gitchie, ya-ya, da-da (Da-da, yeah)
1	Gitchie	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	gitchie	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	ya	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	ya	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	da	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	da	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Da	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	da	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	yeah	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Imma_Be-033
# text = I'ma be ya brother, but my name ain't Lehman
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ma	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	ya	O	-	-
6	brother	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	but	O	-	-
9	my	O	-	-
10	name	O	-	-
11	ain	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	t	O	-	-
14	Lehman	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Wanna_Be_Startin_Somethin_-027
# text = Billie Jean is always talkin' when nobody else is talkin'
1	Billie	B-PER	-	-
2	Jean	I-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	always	O	-	-
5	talkin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	when	O	-	-
8	nobody	O	-	-
9	else	O	-	-
10	is	O	-	-
11	talkin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Cuz_I_Love_You-008
# text = Little bit of Lizzo and some Mo
1	Little	O	-	-
2	bit	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	Lizzo	B-PER	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	some	O	-	-
7	Mo	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Surfin_U_S_A_-008
# text = Surfin' U.S.A
1	Surfin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	U	B-LOC	-	-
4	.	I-LOC	-	-
5	S	I-LOC	-	-
6	.	I-LOC	-	-
7	A	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Candle_In_The_Wind-024
# text = Was that Marilyn was found in the nude
1	Was	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	Marilyn	B-PER	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	found	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	nude	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Fuck_Me_Pumps-033
# text = So you did Miami, 'cause you got there for free
1	So	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	did	O	-	-
4	Miami	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	cause	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	got	O	-	-
10	there	O	-	-
11	for	O	-	-
12	free	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Here_I_Come-029
# text = I represent Los Angeles city (Hey)
1	I	O	-	-
2	represent	O	-	-
3	Los	B-LOC	-	-
4	Angeles	I-LOC	-	-
5	city	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Hey	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Just_Can_t_Get_Enough-032
# text = She got me feelin' like Mr. Roboto​
1	She	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	feelin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	Mr	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Roboto	B-PER	-	-
10	​	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_Fastlove_Pt_1-036
# text = Stupid cupid keeps on calling me
1	Stupid	O	-	-
2	cupid	O	-	-
3	keeps	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	calling	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_After_the_Afterparty-036
# text = Don't need Ibiza
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	need	O	-	-
5	Ibiza	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sabrina_Carpenter_A_Nonsense_Christmas-017
# text = You'll be Santa Claus and I'll be Mrs.
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	Santa	B-PER	-	-
6	Claus	I-PER	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ll	O	-	-
11	be	O	-	-
12	Mrs	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Bennie_And_The_Jets-013
# text = B-B-B-Bennie and the Jets
1	B	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	B	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	B	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	Bennie	B-PER	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Jets	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-020
# text = Take my hand (Ah, bar, bar, bar, bar, Barbara Ann)
1	Take	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	hand	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Ah	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	bar	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	bar	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	bar	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	bar	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
16	Ann	I-PER	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sabrina_Carpenter_A_Nonsense_Christmas-004
# text = I might change your contact to "Has a Huge North Pole"
1	I	O	-	-
2	might	O	-	-
3	change	O	-	-
4	your	O	-	-
5	contact	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	"	O	-	-
8	Has	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	Huge	O	-	-
11	North	B-LOC	-	-
12	Pole	I-LOC	-	-
13	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Crazy_in_love-034
# text = O.G. Big Homie, the one and only (oh, no)
1	O	B-PER	-	-
2	.	I-PER	-	-
3	G	I-PER	-	-
4	.	I-PER	-	-
5	Big	B-PER	-	-
6	Homie	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	one	O	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	only	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	oh	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	no	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-010
# text = She got Arthur on the table with Johnny riding a shotgun
1	She	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	Arthur	b-PER	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	table	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	Johnny	B-PER	-	-
9	riding	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	shotgun	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-032
# text = Ooh, I wanna take you down to Kokomo
1	Ooh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	wanna	O	-	-
5	take	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	down	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Kokomo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Spice_Girls_Spice_Up_Your_Life-024
# text = Arriba! (*Ariba!*)
1	Arriba	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	*	O	-	-
5	Ariba	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	*	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_thank_u_next
# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_thank_u_next-001
# text = Thought I'd end up with Sean
1	Thought	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	d	O	-	-
5	end	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	Sean	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Dance_Again-038
# text = Mami let me open your treasure chest (Hahaha)
1	Mami	O	-	-
2	let	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	open	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	treasure	O	-	-
7	chest	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Hahaha	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-004
# text = Finger on the pump, make the 6 straight jump from SoCal
1	Finger	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	pump	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	make	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	6	O	-	-
9	straight	O	-	-
10	jump	O	-	-
11	from	O	-	-
12	SoCal	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Holy-023
# text = But I don't know (Chance the Rapper)
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	know	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Chance	B-PER	-	-
9	the	I-PER	-	-
10	Rapper	I-PER	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Only_the_Good_Die_Young-039
# text = Well, come out, come out, come out, Virginia, don't let me wait
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	come	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	come	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	come	O	-	-
10	out	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	don	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	t	O	-	-
17	let	O	-	-
18	me	O	-	-
19	wait	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Merry_Christmas_Happy_Holidays-024
# text = God sends you His love
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	sends	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	His	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Judas-029
# text = Jesus is my virtue
1	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	virtue	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-054
# text = Dylan, Berlin
1	Dylan	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Berlin	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Truth_Hurts-036
# text = Minnesota Vikings
1	Minnesota	B-LOC	-	-
2	Vikings	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Crocodile_Rock-022
# text = Burning up to the Crocodile Rock
1	Burning	O	-	-
2	up	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Crocodile	B-LOC	-	-
6	Rock	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Just_Got_Paid-004
# text = JC: Just
1	JC	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Just	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_God_is_a_woman-033
# text = Yeah, yeah (God is a woman, yeah)
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	woman	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	yeah	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Moon_Over_Bourbon_Street-024
# text = The streets of New Orleans
1	The	O	-	-
2	streets	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	New	B-LOC	-	-
5	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Surfin_U_S_A_-015
# text = And down Doheny Way
1	And	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	Doheny	B-LOC	-	-
4	Way	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Sloop_John_B-016
# text = Sheriff John Stone
1	Sheriff	O	-	-
2	John	B-PER	-	-
3	Stone	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Naked_In_Manhattan-037
# text = Naked in Manhattan
1	Naked	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	Manhattan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_On_The_Floor-056
# text = My name ain't Keith, but I see why you sweat me (Hahaha)
1	My	O	-	-
2	name	O	-	-
3	ain	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	Keith	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	but	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	see	O	-	-
11	why	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	sweat	O	-	-
14	me	O	-	-
15	(	O	-	-
16	Hahaha	O	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Pink_Pony_Club-015
# text = West Hollywood, I'm gonna keep on dancing at the
1	West	B-LOC	-	-
2	Hollywood	I-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	gonna	O	-	-
8	keep	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	dancing	O	-	-
11	at	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_New_York_State_of_Mind-005
# text = On the Hudson River line
1	On	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Hudson	B-LOC	-	-
4	River	I-LOC	-	-
5	line	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-027
# text = Tokyo saying (La-la-la-la-la)
1	Tokyo	B-LOC	-	-
2	saying	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	La	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	la	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	la	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	la	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	la	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_On_The_Floor-054
# text = I get on the floor and act a fool if you let me, dale
1	I	O	-	-
2	get	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	floor	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	act	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	fool	O	-	-
10	if	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	let	O	-	-
13	me	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	dale	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_Jesus_to_a_Child-003
# text = You smiled at me like Jesus to a child
1	You	O	-	-
2	smiled	O	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	child	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Special-007
# text = I've been the same since I've been drivin' slow on Bissonnet
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	same	O	-	-
7	since	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ve	O	-	-
11	been	O	-	-
12	drivin	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	slow	O	-	-
15	on	O	-	-
16	Bissonnet	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_No_Strings_Attached-033
# text = JC: Ah...
1	JC	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Ah	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Union_City_Blue-012
# text = Skyline, passion, Union City blue
1	Skyline	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	passion	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Union	B-LOC	-	-
6	City	I-LOC	-	-
7	blue	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-009
# text = To London, to Brazil, to Quebec
1	To	O	-	-
2	London	B-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	Brazil	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Quebec	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Daniel-006
# text = They say Spain is pretty, though I've never been
1	They	O	-	-
2	say	O	-	-
3	Spain	B-LOC	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	pretty	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	though	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ve	O	-	-
11	never	O	-	-
12	been	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Home_for_Christmas
# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Home_for_Christmas-001
# text = Justin:
1	Justin	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Hungry-035
# text = El Chapo
1	El	B-PER	-	-
2	Chapo	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-022
# text = Joseph Stalin, Malenkov
1	Joseph	B-PER	-	-
2	Stalin	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Malenkov	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Britney_Spears_Lucky-017
# text = "I'm Roger Johnson for Pop News, standing outside the arena waiting for Lucky"
1	"	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	Roger	B-PER	-	-
6	Johnson	I-PER	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	Pop	B-ORG	-	-
9	News	I-ORG	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	standing	O	-	-
12	outside	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	arena	O	-	-
15	waiting	O	-	-
16	for	O	-	-
17	Lucky	B-PER	-	-
18	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_thank_u_next-028
# text = 'Cause her name is Ari
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	her	O	-	-
4	name	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	Ari	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Alejandro-044
# text = (Don't call my name, don't call my name) Ale-Alejandro, Ale-Alejandro
1	(	O	-	-
2	Don	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	call	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	name	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	don	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	call	O	-	-
13	my	O	-	-
14	name	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-
16	Ale	B-PER	-	-
17	-	I-PER	-	-
18	Alejandro	I-PER	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	Ale	B-PER	-	-
21	-	I-PER	-	-
22	Alejandro	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Love_Never_Felt_So_Good-023
# text = Michael
1	Michael	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Dark_Horse-028
# text = She eat your heart out like Jeffrey Dahmer (Woo)
1	She	O	-	-
2	eat	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	heart	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	Jeffrey	B-PER	-	-
8	Dahmer	I-PER	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Woo	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_God_is_a_woman-004
# text = You'll believe God is a woman
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	believe	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	woman	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Smooth_Criminal-010
# text = So, Annie, are you okay? Are you okay, Annie?
1	So	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Annie	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	are	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	okay	O	-	-
8	?	O	-	-
9	Are	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	okay	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Annie	B-PER	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-040
# text = To London, Jamaica, then France
1	To	O	-	-
2	London	B-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Jamaica	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	then	O	-	-
7	France	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_That_s_What_I_Like-010
# text = I'll rent a beach house in Miami (-ami)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	rent	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	beach	O	-	-
7	house	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Miami	B-LOC	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	ami	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Fergalicious-025
# text = Fergalicious def- (Def-)
1	Fergalicious	B-PER	-	-
2	def	O	-	-
3	-	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Def	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_La_Isla_Bonita-002
# text = Last night I dreamt of San Pedro
1	Last	O	-	-
2	night	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	dreamt	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	San	B-LOC	-	-
7	Pedro	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Pink-022
# text = It's her (Ayy), and her (Ayy), and me (Ayy), and you
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Ayy	O	-	-
7	)	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	her	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Ayy	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	and	O	-	-
16	me	O	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Ayy	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	and	O	-	-
22	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-033
# text = Port au Prince, I want to catch a glimpse
1	Port	B-LOC	-	-
2	au	I-LOC	-	-
3	Prince	I-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	want	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	catch	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	glimpse	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_Love_Story-013
# text = Romeo, take me somewhere we can be alone
1	Romeo	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	somewhere	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	can	O	-	-
8	be	O	-	-
9	alone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Smokin_Out_The_Window-007
# text = Put me in a jam with her ex-man in the UFC
1	Put	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	jam	O	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	her	O	-	-
8	ex	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	man	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	UFC	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-056
# text = Lawrence of Arabia
1	Lawrence	B-ORG	-	-
2	of	I-ORG	-	-
3	Arabia	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-032
# text = Elvis Presley, Disneyland
1	Elvis	B-PER	-	-
2	Presley	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Disneyland	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Supermarket_Flowers-015
# text = When God takes you back
1	When	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	takes	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	back	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Barbra_Streisand_New_York_State_of_Mind-021
# text = I'm in a New York, I'm in a New York state of mind...
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	New	B-LOC	-	-
7	York	I-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	New	B-LOC	-	-
15	York	I-LOC	-	-
16	state	O	-	-
17	of	O	-	-
18	mind	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-
20	.	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_The_Downeaster_Alexa_-004
# text = But tonight I am Nantucket bound
1	But	O	-	-
2	tonight	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	am	O	-	-
5	Nantucket	B-LOC	-	-
6	bound	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Club_classics-013
# text = Tight like Mike kinda flow
1	Tight	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	Mike	B-PER	-	-
4	kinda	O	-	-
5	flow	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Drunk_in_Love-043
# text = Beat the box up like Mike in '97, I bite
1	Beat	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	box	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Mike	B-PER	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	97	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	bite	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Selena_Gomez_Slow_Down-003
# text = Mr. TSA, I'm ready for inspection
1	Mr	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	TSA	B-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	ready	O	-	-
9	for	O	-	-
10	inspection	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-051
# text = Vogue
1	Vogue	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cyndi_Lauper_She_Bop-002
# text = In the pages of a Blueboy magazine
1	In	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	pages	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	Blueboy	B-ORG	-	-
7	magazine	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-039
# text = Oh, but there we were, waving Brenda and Eddie goodbye
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	but	O	-	-
4	there	O	-	-
5	we	O	-	-
6	were	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	waving	O	-	-
9	Brenda	B-PER	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	Eddie	B-PER	-	-
12	goodbye	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Nikita-013
# text = Oh, Nikita, is the other side
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Nikita	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	other	O	-	-
8	side	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-052
# text = Hemingway, Eichmann
1	Hemingway	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Eichmann	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Eenie_Meenie-017
# text = 'Cause shorty is a eenie-meenie-miney-mo lover
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	shorty	B-PER	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	eenie	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	meenie	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	miney	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	mo	O	-	-
13	lover	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Made_For_Now
# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Made_For_Now-001
# text = Janet Jackson
1	Janet	B-PER	-	-
2	Jackson	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Controversy-005
# text = Do I believe in God?
1	Do	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	believe	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Obsessed-012
# text = But you in LA, and I'm out at Jermaine's
1	But	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	LA	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	m	O	-	-
10	out	O	-	-
11	at	O	-	-
12	Jermaine	B-PER	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	s	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Just_Got_Paid-006
# text = Chris: Just All: got paid
1	Chris	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Just	O	-	-
4	All	O	-	-
5	:	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	paid	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Chiquitita-015
# text = Chiquitita, you and I know
1	Chiquitita	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	know	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Backstreet_Boys_Get_Down_You_re_the_One_for_Me_-026
# text = AJ, hit it
1	AJ	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	hit	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Wide_Awake-030
# text = God knows that I tried
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	knows	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	tried	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Soulmate-009
# text = But I'm solo in Soho, sippin' Soju in Malibu
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	solo	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Soho	B-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	sippin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	Soju	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	Malibu	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_True-021
# text = Listening to Marvin (All night long)
1	Listening	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	Marvin	B-PER	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	All	O	-	-
6	night	O	-	-
7	long	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Unlock_It-045
# text = Petras]
1	Petras	B-PER	-	-
2	]	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Judas-025
# text = Judas, kiss me, if offenced
1	Judas	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	kiss	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	if	O	-	-
7	offenced	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_Karma-018
# text = Spiderboy, king of thieves
1	Spiderboy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	king	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	thieves	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Movin_Out_Anthony_s_Song_-004
# text = Anthony works in the grocery store
1	Anthony	B-PER	-	-
2	works	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	grocery	O	-	-
6	store	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_La_Isla_Bonita-023
# text = La Isla Bonita
1	La	B-PER	-	-
2	Isla	O	-	-
3	Bonita	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-058
# text = Ole Miss, John Glenn
1	Ole	B-LOC	-	-
2	Miss	I-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	John	B-PER	-	-
5	Glenn	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Nikita-020
# text = Nikita, do you count the stars at night?
1	Nikita	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	count	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	stars	O	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	night	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Crazy_in_love-035
# text = Stick bony, but the pockets is fat like Tony (oh, no)
1	Stick	O	-	-
2	bony	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	but	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	pockets	O	-	-
7	is	O	-	-
8	fat	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	Tony	B-PER	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	oh	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	no	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Fernando-008
# text = I was so afraid, Fernando
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	so	O	-	-
4	afraid	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Fernando	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Maroon_5_Moves_Like_Jagger-014
# text = All the moves like Jagger
1	All	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	moves	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Jagger	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Englishman_In_New_York-004
# text = I'm an Englishman in New York
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	an	O	-	-
5	Englishman	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	New	B-LOC	-	-
8	York	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Russians-010
# text = From Oppenheimer's deadly toy?
1	From	O	-	-
2	Oppenheimer	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	deadly	O	-	-
6	toy	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-George_Michael_Praying_for_Time-035
# text = 'Cause God's stopped keeping score"
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	God	B-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	stopped	O	-	-
7	keeping	O	-	-
8	score	O	-	-
9	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Judas-003
# text = Judas, Juda-ah-ah
1	Judas	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Juda	I-PER	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	ah	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	ah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Coldplay_Higher_Power-010
# text = Drocer nekorb a ekil m'I
1	Drocer	B-ORG	-	-
2	nekorb	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	ekil	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Better_in_Color-003
# text = J. F. Kennedys, kiss hood celebrities
1	J	B-PER	-	-
2	.	I-PER	-	-
3	F	I-PER	-	-
4	.	I-PER	-	-
5	Kennedys	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	kiss	O	-	-
8	hood	O	-	-
9	celebrities	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Union_City_Blue-015
# text = I say, "He's my Union City man"
1	I	O	-	-
2	say	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	He	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	Union	B-LOC	-	-
10	City	I-LOC	-	-
11	man	O	-	-
12	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Play-034
# text = Play, come on play that song (Now, Mr. DJ)
1	Play	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	come	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	play	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	song	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Now	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Mr	B-PER	-	-
12	.	I-PER	-	-
13	DJ	I-PER	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Miley_Cyrus_Party_In_The_U_S_A_-042
# text = Yeah (Yeah), it's a party in the U.S.A.
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	Yeah	O	-	-
4	)	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	party	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	U	B-LOC	-	-
14	.	I-LOC	-	-
15	S	I-LOC	-	-
16	.	I-LOC	-	-
17	A	I-LOC	-	-
18	.	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Adele_Skyfall-015
# text = Skyfall is where we start
1	Skyfall	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	where	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	start	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Rehab-005
# text = I'd rather be at home with Ray
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	d	O	-	-
4	rather	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	at	O	-	-
7	home	O	-	-
8	with	O	-	-
9	Ray	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Rip_Her_To_Shreds-020
# text = Dressed in a Robert Hall sweater
1	Dressed	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	Robert	B-PER	-	-
5	Hall	I-PER	-	-
6	sweater	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman-045
# text = (Tarzan and Jane were swingin' on a vine)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Tarzan	B-PER	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	Jane	B-PER	-	-
5	were	O	-	-
6	swingin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	vine	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Surfin_U_S_A_-028
# text = Redondo Beach LA
1	Redondo	B-LOC	-	-
2	Beach	I-LOC	-	-
3	LA	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Dirty_Diana-035
# text = C'mon! (Dirty Diana, no) (Hey, baby, won't you-)
1	C	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	mon	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Dirty	O	-	-
7	Diana	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	no	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Hey	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	baby	O	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	won	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-
18	t	O	-	-
19	you	O	-	-
20	-	O	-	-
21	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Help_Me_Rhonda-003
# text = Well, Rhonda you look so fine (Look so fine)
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Rhonda	B-PER	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	look	O	-	-
6	so	O	-	-
7	fine	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Look	O	-	-
10	so	O	-	-
11	fine	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Cupid-015
# text = Cupid, help me if you will, so
1	Cupid	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	help	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	if	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	will	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Help_Me_Rhonda-014
# text = Help me, Rhonda, help, help me Rhonda
1	Help	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Rhonda	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	help	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	help	O	-	-
9	me	O	-	-
10	Rhonda	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-042
# text = When I come from Kansas City
1	When	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	come	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	Kansas	B-LOC	-	-
6	City	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-035
# text = Trouble in the Suez
1	Trouble	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Suez	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Suit_Tie-009
# text = You ready, JT?
1	You	O	-	-
2	ready	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	JT	B-PER	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_No_Strings_Attached-030
# text = Lance: Ah...
1	Lance	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-
3	Ah	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Brooklyn_Baby-045
# text = 'Cause I'm a Brooklyn baby
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	Brooklyn	B-LOC	-	-
8	baby	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Taylor_Swift_Look_What_You_Made_Me_Do-033
# text = "I'm sorry, the old Taylor can't come to the phone right now"
1	"	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	sorry	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	old	O	-	-
9	Taylor	B-PER	-	-
10	can	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	come	O	-	-
14	to	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	phone	O	-	-
17	right	O	-	-
18	now	O	-	-
19	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Guess_featuring_billie_eilish-020
# text = The ones I picked out for you in Tokyo
1	The	O	-	-
2	ones	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	picked	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Tokyo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-021
# text = Way down in Kokomo
1	Way	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	Kokomo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Selena_Gomez_Fetish-025
# text = If I were you, I'd do me too (It's Gucci)
1	If	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	were	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	d	O	-	-
9	do	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	too	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	It	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	s	O	-	-
16	Gucci	B-ORG	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_P_Y_T_Pretty_Young_Thing_-045
# text = I want to love you, P.Y.T., P.Y.T
1	I	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	love	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	P	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Y	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	T	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	P	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	Y	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	T	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Help_Me_Rhonda-005
# text = For you to help me, Rhonda
1	For	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	help	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Rhonda	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-012
# text = Then put Van on the jukebox, got up to dance
1	Then	O	-	-
2	put	O	-	-
3	Van	B-PER	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	jukebox	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	up	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	dance	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-062
# text = Ohh, and that's all I heard about Brenda and Eddie
1	Ohh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	s	O	-	-
7	all	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	heard	O	-	-
10	about	O	-	-
11	Brenda	B-PER	-	-
12	and	O	-	-
13	Eddie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Pop-046
# text = (BT)
1	(	O	-	-
2	BT	B-PER	-	-
3	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_Escapade-027
# text = Minneapolis!
1	Minneapolis	B-LOC	-	-
2	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Where_Is_The_Love_-008
# text = The Bloods and the Crips and the KKK
1	The	O	-	-
2	Bloods	B-ORG	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Crips	B-ORG	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	KKK	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Naked_In_Manhattan-021
# text = Touch me, baby (Naked in Manhattan)
1	Touch	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	baby	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Naked	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Manhattan	B-LOC	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Juice-003
# text = Louis down to my drawers
1	Louis	B-PER	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	drawers	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Guess_featuring_billie_eilish-014
# text = Send 'em to The Dare, yeah, I think he's with it
1	Send	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	em	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	The	B-PER	-	-
6	Dare	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	yeah	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	think	O	-	-
12	he	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	s	O	-	-
15	with	O	-	-
16	it	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Bon_Appétit
# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Bon_Appétit-001
# text = Ayy, yeah
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Confident-039
# text = Chance? The Rapper? IGH!
1	Chance	B-PER	-	-
2	?	O	-	-
3	The	I-PER	-	-
4	Rapper	I-PER	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	IGH	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_After_Last_Night-009
# text = See, normally, I don't stutter, but you d-d-d-d-do it to me (Silk Sonic)
1	See	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	normally	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	don	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	stutter	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	but	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	d	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	d	O	-	-
16	-	O	-	-
17	d	O	-	-
18	-	O	-	-
19	d	O	-	-
20	-	O	-	-
21	do	O	-	-
22	it	O	-	-
23	to	O	-	-
24	me	O	-	-
25	(	O	-	-
26	Silk	B-ORG	-	-
27	Sonic	I-ORG	-	-
28	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_Dangerous_Woman-004
# text = 'Cause it's my business, God as my witness
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	business	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	God	B-PER	-	-
10	as	O	-	-
11	my	O	-	-
12	witness	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_I_m_Into_You-050
# text = I'm into you, I'm into you (Ayy)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	into	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	m	O	-	-
10	into	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Ayy	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Surfin_U_S_A_-029
# text = All over La Jolla
1	All	O	-	-
2	over	O	-	-
3	La	B-LOC	-	-
4	Jolla	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Galway_Girl-005
# text = I met her on Grafton Street right outside of the bar
1	I	O	-	-
2	met	O	-	-
3	her	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	Grafton	B-LOC	-	-
6	Street	I-LOC	-	-
7	right	O	-	-
8	outside	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	bar	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-049
# text = Kingston saying (La-la-la-la-la)
1	Kingston	B-LOC	-	-
2	saying	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	La	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	la	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	la	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	la	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	la	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_They_Don_t_Care_About_Us-021
# text = You're ripping me off my pride, oh, for God's sake
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	ripping	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	off	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	pride	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	oh	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	for	O	-	-
13	God	B-PER	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	s	O	-	-
16	sake	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_On_The_Floor-048
# text = That badonkadonk is like a trunk
1	That	O	-	-
2	badonkadonk	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	trunk	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Merry_Christmas_Happy_Holidays-059
# text = God sends you His love (Oh, yeah)
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	sends	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	His	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Oh	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yeah	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Fergalicious-066
# text = I'm Fergalicious (T-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	Fergalicious	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	T	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	-	O	-	-
14	t	O	-	-
15	-	O	-	-
16	t	O	-	-
17	-	O	-	-
18	t	O	-	-
19	-	O	-	-
20	t	O	-	-
21	-	O	-	-
22	t	O	-	-
23	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Happiness_is_a_butterfly-020
# text = Hollywood and Vine, Black Rabbit in the alley
1	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Vine	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Black	B-ORG	-	-
6	Rabbit	I-ORG	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	alley	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Here_I_Come-044
# text = Or call me Billy
1	Or	O	-	-
2	call	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	Billy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Pop-002
# text = (Yo, BT)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Yo	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	BT	B-PER	-	-
5	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Poker_Face-002
# text = I wanna hold 'em like they do in Texas, please (Woo)
1	I	O	-	-
2	wanna	O	-	-
3	hold	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	em	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	they	O	-	-
8	do	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	please	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Woo	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-ABBA_Fernando
# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Fernando-001
# text = Can you hear the drums, Fernando?
1	Can	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	hear	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	drums	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Fernando	B-PER	-	-
8	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_You_Already_Know-018
# text = Beez got me feeling like a gypsy
1	Beez	B-PER	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	feeling	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	gypsy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Celine_Dion_The_Prayer-026
# text = Ognuno trovi amor
1	Ognuno	O	-	-
2	trovi	O	-	-
3	amor	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Dirty_Diana-033
# text = C'mon! (Dirty Diana, no)
1	C	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	mon	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Dirty	O	-	-
7	Diana	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	no	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Mistletoe-009
# text = (With you) Shawty, with you (Yeah, you know?)
1	(	O	-	-
2	With	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	)	O	-	-
5	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Yeah	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	know	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Perfect-022
# text = Darlin', just hold my hand
1	Darlin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	just	O	-	-
5	hold	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	hand	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Timberlake_Until_The_End_Of_Time-055
# text = Break it down one more time, Justin
1	Break	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	down	O	-	-
4	one	O	-	-
5	more	O	-	-
6	time	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Justin	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Chiquitita-007
# text = Chiquitita, tell me the truth
1	Chiquitita	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	tell	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	truth	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Black_Eyed_Peas_Hey_Mama-047
# text = From the crew (BEP)
1	From	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	crew	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	BEP	B-ORG	-	-
6	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Waterloo-007
# text = Waterloo, I was defeated, you won the war
1	Waterloo	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	defeated	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	won	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	war	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sabrina_Carpenter_Why-023
# text = You start your night sippin' by the Kilo
1	You	O	-	-
2	start	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	night	O	-	-
5	sippin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	by	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Kilo	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Baby_Boy-004
# text = Sean da Paul 'longside Beyoncé
1	Sean	B-PER	-	-
2	da	I-PER	-	-
3	Paul	I-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	longside	O	-	-
6	Beyoncé	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Hungry-039
# text = Ferrari Fergie
1	Ferrari	B-PER	-	-
2	Fergie	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Good_Hurt-018
# text = You can call me Medusa
1	You	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	call	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	Medusa	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Raspberry_Beret-005
# text = My boss was Mr. McGee
1	My	O	-	-
2	boss	O	-	-
3	was	O	-	-
4	Mr	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	McGee	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Pink-017
# text = Hey, Barbie, I like your style
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Barbie	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	your	O	-	-
8	style	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_All_This_Time-021
# text = Father, if Jesus exists then how come he never lives here?
1	Father	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	if	O	-	-
4	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
5	exists	O	-	-
6	then	O	-	-
7	how	O	-	-
8	come	O	-	-
9	he	O	-	-
10	never	O	-	-
11	lives	O	-	-
12	here	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_All_i_want_for_christmass-012
# text = Santa Claus won't make me happy with a toy on Christmas Day
1	Santa	B-PER	-	-
2	Claus	I-PER	-	-
3	won	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	make	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	happy	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	toy	O	-	-
12	on	O	-	-
13	Christmas	O	-	-
14	Day	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-003
# text = South Pacific
1	South	B-LOC	-	-
2	Pacific	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_National_Anthem-034
# text = Keep me safe in his bell tower hotel
1	Keep	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	safe	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	his	O	-	-
6	bell	O	-	-
7	tower	O	-	-
8	hotel	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Labels_Or_Love-034
# text = Manolo or Polo, taking photos in my Cartier
1	Manolo	B-ORG	-	-
2	or	O	-	-
3	Polo	B-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	taking	O	-	-
6	photos	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	Cartier	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-026
# text = Roy Cohn, Juan Peron
1	Roy	B-PER	-	-
2	Cohn	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Juan	B-PER	-	-
5	Peron	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Sloop_John_B-018
# text = So hoist up the John B's sail (Hoist up the John B's sail)
1	So	O	-	-
2	hoist	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	John	B-PER	-	-
6	B	I-PER	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	sail	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Hoist	O	-	-
12	up	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	John	B-PER	-	-
15	B	I-PER	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	s	O	-	-
18	sail	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Michael_Jackson_Smooth_Criminal-030
# text = Annie, are you okay? Are you okay?
1	Annie	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	are	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	okay	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	Are	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	okay	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-031
# text = Davy Crockett, Peter Pan
1	Davy	B-PER	-	-
2	Crockett	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Peter	B-PER	-	-
5	Pan	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Mistletoe-018
# text = (With you) Shawty, with you (Oh)
1	(	O	-	-
2	With	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	)	O	-	-
5	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Oh	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Pink_Pony_Club-022
# text = Oh, Santa Monica, you've been too good to me
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Santa	B-LOC	-	-
4	Monica	I-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	ve	O	-	-
9	been	O	-	-
10	too	O	-	-
11	good	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Mary_Jane_Shoes-025
# text = Whoa, my Mary Jane's (One, two)
1	Whoa	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	Mary	B-PER	-	-
5	Jane	I-PER	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	One	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	two	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_I_m_Into_You-005
# text = Hi, I'm Tune, the man on the moon
1	Hi	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	Tune	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	man	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	moon	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_Me_Mr_Jones-019
# text = Side from Sammy you're my best black Jew (Best black Jew)
1	Side	O	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	Sammy	B-PER	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	re	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	best	O	-	-
9	black	O	-	-
10	Jew	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Best	O	-	-
13	black	O	-	-
14	Jew	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Charli_xcx_Unlock_It-032
# text = Bring me out to London, yeah (U.K.)
1	Bring	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	out	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	London	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	yeah	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	U	B-LOC	-	-
10	.	I-LOC	-	-
11	K	I-LOC	-	-
12	.	I-LOC	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Formation-008
# text = You mix that negro with that Creole, make a Texas bama
1	You	O	-	-
2	mix	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	negro	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	Creole	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	make	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	Texas	B-LOC	-	-
12	bama	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_You_Already_Know-024
# text = I keep a bar like Esco
1	I	O	-	-
2	keep	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	bar	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Esco	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Rapture-050
# text = 'Cause the man from Mars
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	man	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	Mars	B-LOC	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Sting_Desert_Rose
# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Desert_Rose-001
# text = Layli, layli, oh
1	Layli	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	layli	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	oh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-045
# text = Lauren, Katharine, Lana too
1	Lauren	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Katharine	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Lana	B-PER	-	-
6	too	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_I_m_Into_You-023
# text = I'm into you (Ayy)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	into	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Ayy	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-050
# text = Chubby Checker, Psycho
1	Chubby	B-PER	-	-
2	Checker	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Psycho	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_California_Girls-005
# text = The Midwest farmer's daughters
1	The	O	-	-
2	Midwest	B-LOC	-	-
3	farmer	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	daughters	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ed_Sheeran_Beautiful_People-002
# text = L.A. on a Saturday night in the summer
1	L	B-LOC	-	-
2	.	I-LOC	-	-
3	A	I-LOC	-	-
4	.	I-LOC	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	Saturday	O	-	-
8	night	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	summer	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Super_Graphic_Ultra_Modern_Girl-024
# text = Walk that walk from Tokyo to New York
1	Walk	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	walk	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	Tokyo	B-LOC	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	New	B-LOC	-	-
8	York	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Elton_John_Tiny_Dancer-010
# text = Handing tickets out for God
1	Handing	O	-	-
2	tickets	O	-	-
3	out	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-004
# text = Jamaica
1	Jamaica	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-036
# text = Dietrich and DiMaggio
1	Dietrich	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	DiMaggio	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madonna_Vogue-026
# text = Beauty's where you find it
1	Beauty	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	where	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	find	O	-	-
7	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_School_Nights-025
# text = You become King Kong
1	You	O	-	-
2	become	O	-	-
3	King	B-PER	-	-
4	Kong	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lizzo_Like_a_Girl-027
# text = Lauryn Hill told me everything is everything (We can do it)
1	Lauryn	B-PER	-	-
2	Hill	I-PER	-	-
3	told	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	everything	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	everything	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	We	O	-	-
10	can	O	-	-
11	do	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Glamorous-004
# text = It's Fergie
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	Fergie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-056
# text = Brenda and Eddie had it already by the summer of '75
1	Brenda	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Eddie	B-PER	-	-
4	had	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	already	O	-	-
7	by	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	summer	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	75	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_BURNITUP_-035
# text = (Missy!)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Missy	B-PER	-	-
3	!	O	-	-
4	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Pink_Pony_Club-014
# text = Pink Pony Club, I'm gonna keep on dancing down in
1	Pink	B-LOC	-	-
2	Pony	I-LOC	-	-
3	Club	I-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	gonna	O	-	-
9	keep	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-
11	dancing	O	-	-
12	down	O	-	-
13	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Bon_Appétit-048
# text = Every single night (Ayy)
1	Every	O	-	-
2	single	O	-	-
3	night	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Ayy	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_That_s_What_I_Like-002
# text = I got a condo in Manhattan
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	condo	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Manhattan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Dirrty-062
# text = Yo, Christina (What?), better hop in here
1	Yo	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Christina	B-PER	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	What	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	)	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	better	O	-	-
10	hop	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	here	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_We_Didn_t_Start_the_Fire-023
# text = Nasser and Prokofiev
1	Nasser	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Prokofiev	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-038
# text = Atlanta, north south Cac-ill-ac
1	Atlanta	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	north	O	-	-
4	south	O	-	-
5	Cac	B-ORG	-	-
6	-	I-ORG	-	-
7	ill	I-ORG	-	-
8	-	I-ORG	-	-
9	ac	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Brooklyn_Baby-012
# text = He plays guitar while I sing Lou Reed
1	He	O	-	-
2	plays	O	-	-
3	guitar	O	-	-
4	while	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	sing	O	-	-
7	Lou	B-PER	-	-
8	Reed	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_London_Bridge-006
# text = Polow
1	Polow	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_Mary_Jane_Shoes-006
# text = Whoa, my Mary Jane's
1	Whoa	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	Mary	B-PER	-	-
5	Jane	I-PER	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Rip_Her_To_Shreds-032
# text = She makin' out with King Kong
1	She	O	-	-
2	makin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	King	B-PER	-	-
7	Kong	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ariana_Grande_God_is_a_woman-032
# text = Yeah, yeah (God is a woman)
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	woman	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Kiss-017
# text = Little Girl Wendy's Parade
1	Little	O	-	-
2	Girl	O	-	-
3	Wendy	B-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	Parade	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Pink_Pony_Club-005
# text = I'm having wicked dreams of leaving Tennessee
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	having	O	-	-
5	wicked	O	-	-
6	dreams	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	leaving	O	-	-
9	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Partition-027
# text = Beyoncé, Beyoncé?
1	Beyoncé	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Beyoncé	B-PER	-	-
4	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lady_Gaga_Judas-030
# text = And Judas is the demon I cling to
1	And	O	-	-
2	Judas	B-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	demon	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	cling	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Barbara_Ann-049
# text = (Oh, my) Barbara Ann
1	(	O	-	-
2	Oh	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	Barbara	B-PER	-	-
7	Ann	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Kokomo-014
# text = Aruba, Jamaica, ooh, I wanna take you
1	Aruba	B-LOC	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Jamaica	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	ooh	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	wanna	O	-	-
9	take	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fergie_L_A_LOVE_la_la_-008
# text = Just got to New York like a net on a jet
1	Just	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	New	B-LOC	-	-
5	York	I-LOC	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	net	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	jet	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Dark_Horse
# sent_id = lyrics-Katy_Perry_Dark_Horse-001
# text = Katy Perry, Juicy J
1	Katy	B-PER	-	-
2	Perry	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Juicy	B-PER	-	-
5	J	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-ABBA_Money_Money_Money-020
# text = To Las Vegas or Monaco
1	To	O	-	-
2	Las	B-LOC	-	-
3	Vegas	I-LOC	-	-
4	or	O	-	-
5	Monaco	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Janet_Jackson_No_Sleeep-021
# text = Cole world (Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
1	Cole	B-PER	-	-
2	world	I-PER	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Yeah	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	yeah	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	yeah	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	yeah	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	yeah	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Billy_Joel_Scenes_from_an_Italian_Restaurant-019
# text = Oh, you'd drop a dime in the box, play a song about New Orleans
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	drop	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	dime	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	box	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	play	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	song	O	-	-
16	about	O	-	-
17	New	B-LOC	-	-
18	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lana_Del_Rey_Chemtrails_Over_The_Country_Club-025
# text = Suburbia, The Brentwood Market
1	Suburbia	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	The	B-LOC	-	-
4	Brentwood	I-LOC	-	-
5	Market	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Coldplay_Christmas_Lights-015
# text = Like some drunken Elvis singing
1	Like	O	-	-
2	some	O	-	-
3	drunken	O	-	-
4	Elvis	B-PER	-	-
5	singing	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Santa_Claus_Is_Comin_to_Town-026
# text = Santa Claus is comin'— (Santa Claus)
1	Santa	B-PER	-	-
2	Claus	I-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	comin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	—	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Santa	B-PER	-	-
9	Claus	I-PER	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beyoncé_Crazy_in_love-032
# text = Young Hov, y'all know when the flow is loco
1	Young	B-PER	-	-
2	Hov	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	y	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	when	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	flow	O	-	-
11	is	O	-	-
12	loco	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Touch_My_Body
# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Touch_My_Body-001
# text = MC
1	MC	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Prince_Controversy-039
# text = Do I believe in God? Do I believe in me? Let me tell you
1	Do	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	believe	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	Do	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	believe	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-
13	Let	O	-	-
14	me	O	-	-
15	tell	O	-	-
16	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Beach_Boys_Little_Saint_Nick-021
# text = (Ooooooooh, merry Christmas Saint Nick)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Ooooooooh	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	merry	O	-	-
5	Christmas	O	-	-
6	Saint	O	-	-
7	Nick	I-PER	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mariah_Carey_Obsessed-056
# text = (He's all up in my George Foreman)
1	(	O	-	-
2	He	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	all	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	George	B-PER	-	-
10	Foreman	I-PER	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Goin_In-029
# text = Put me in a cell, feet down, Flo Rida, hey
1	Put	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	cell	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	feet	O	-	-
8	down	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Flo	B-PER	-	-
11	Rida	I-LOC	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	hey	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Blondie_Denis
# sent_id = lyrics-Blondie_Denis-001
# text = Oh Denis doo-be-do
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	Denis	B-PER	-	-
3	doo	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	do	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Justin_Bieber_Peaches-027
# text = Left her baggage for Rimowa
1	Left	O	-	-
2	her	O	-	-
3	baggage	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	Rimowa	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Jenny_from_the_Block_Track_Masters_Remix_-015
# text = Make the money, get the mansion, bring the homies with us (Southside Bronx)
1	Make	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	money	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	get	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	mansion	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	bring	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	homies	O	-	-
12	with	O	-	-
13	us	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Southside	O	-	-
16	Bronx	I-LOC	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sting_Russians-005
# text = Mr. Khrushchev said, "We will bury you"
1	Mr	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Khrushchev	B-PER	-	-
4	said	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	"	O	-	-
7	We	O	-	-
8	will	O	-	-
9	bury	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_Pink_Pony_Club-024
# text = Still love you and Tennessee, you're always on my mind
1	Still	O	-	-
2	love	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Tennessee	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	re	O	-	-
10	always	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	my	O	-	-
13	mind	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Amy_Winehouse_The_Girl_From_Ipanema-002
# text = The girl from Ipanema goes walking and
1	The	O	-	-
2	girl	O	-	-
3	from	O	-	-
4	Ipanema	B-LOC	-	-
5	goes	O	-	-
6	walking	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_That_s_What_I_Like-013
# text = Julio, serve that scampi (Julio!)
1	Julio	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	serve	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	scampi	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Julio	B-PER	-	-
8	!	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-_NSYNC_Just_Got_Paid-007
# text = Justin:
1	Justin	B-PER	-	-
2	:	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jennifer_Lopez_Goin_In-026
# text = Officer on duty, J.Lo what they call her
1	Officer	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	duty	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	J	B-PER	-	-
6	.	I-PER	-	-
7	Lo	I-PER	-	-
8	what	O	-	-
9	they	O	-	-
10	call	O	-	-
11	her	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Selena_Gomez_Good_For_You-018
# text = Could even make that Tiffany jealous
1	Could	O	-	-
2	even	O	-	-
3	make	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	Tiffany	B-PER	-	-
6	jealous	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bruno_Mars_Locked_out_of_Heaven-013
# text = I've been locked outta heaven
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ve	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	locked	O	-	-
6	outta	O	-	-
7	heaven	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Chappell_Roan_California-009
# text = Come get me out of California
1	Come	O	-	-
2	get	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	out	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	California	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Christina_Aguilera_Candyman-004
# text = Sweet sugar, Candyman
1	Sweet	O	-	-
2	sugar	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Candyman	B-PER	-	-

