# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Rock_Box-019
# text = Jam Master cut the record up and down and cross-fades
1	Jam	B-PER	-	-
2	Master	I-PER	-	-
3	cut	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	record	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	down	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	cross	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	fades	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Hard_Work_Pays_Off-013
# text = Fendi my underwear
1	Fendi	B-ORG	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	underwear	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_N95-054
# text = Say what I want about you niggas, I'm like Oprah, dawg
1	Say	O	-	-
2	what	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	want	O	-	-
5	about	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	niggas	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	like	O	-	-
13	Oprah	B-PER	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	dawg	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_Runaway_Love-058
# text = Erica is stuck up in a world on her own
1	Erica	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	stuck	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	world	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	her	O	-	-
10	own	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Hit_Em_Up-068
# text = Coppin' pleas in de Janeiro
1	Coppin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	pleas	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	de	B-LOC	-	-
6	Janeiro	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Can_t_Trust_it-037
# text = Little Rock where they be dockin' this boat
1	Little	B-LOC	-	-
2	Rock	I-LOC	-	-
3	where	O	-	-
4	they	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	dockin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	this	O	-	-
9	boat	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly__1-009
# text = No resident of France; but you swear I'm from Paris
1	No	O	-	-
2	resident	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	France	B-LOC	-	-
5	;	O	-	-
6	but	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	swear	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	from	O	-	-
13	Paris	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_Fashion_Killa-029
# text = Oliver Peoples (Yeah)
1	Oliver	B-ORG	-	-
2	Peoples	I-ORG	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Yeah	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Brown_Get_Away-037
# text = Bob and Ted'd rated number one so flow on it
1	Bob	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Ted	B-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	rated	O	-	-
7	number	O	-	-
8	one	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-
10	flow	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_E_I_-028
# text = Uh-ohhhhhhhhhhhhhh, if the head right, Nelly there ery'night
1	Uh	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	ohhhhhhhhhhhhhh	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	if	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	head	O	-	-
8	right	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Nelly	B-PER	-	-
11	there	O	-	-
12	ery	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	night	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cardi_B_Best_Life-046
# text = Reach like 'Bron James, pep talk from Yoncé
1	Reach	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	Bron	B-PER	-	-
5	James	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	pep	O	-	-
8	talk	O	-	-
9	from	O	-	-
10	Yoncé	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Protect_Ya_Neck-021
# text = Terrorize the jam like troops in Pakistan
1	Terrorize	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	jam	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	troops	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Pakistan	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Rainbows-020
# text = Hope, they don't know (They don't know nothin')
1	Hope	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	don	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	They	O	-	-
10	don	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	know	O	-	-
14	nothin	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Rick_Morty-025
# text = Rick and Morty, nigga, jump on spaceships
1	Rick	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Morty	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	nigga	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	jump	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	spaceships	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Iggy_Azalea_Kream-004
# text = Look at Wallis
1	Look	O	-	-
2	at	O	-	-
3	Wallis	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tyler_The_Creator_She-041
# text = We can begin the pretend game, I wanna be Finn from Adventure Time, yeah
1	We	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	begin	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	pretend	O	-	-
6	game	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	wanna	O	-	-
10	be	O	-	-
11	Finn	B-PER	-	-
12	from	O	-	-
13	Adventure	B-ORG	-	-
14	Time	O	I-ORG	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_I_Wanna_Fuck_You-003
# text = Konvict, Music
1	Konvict	B-ORG	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Music	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_Window_Shopper-025
# text = They come to scoop me up at LAX and I hop in
1	They	O	-	-
2	come	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	scoop	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	at	O	-	-
8	LAX	B-LOC	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	hop	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Git_Up_Git_Out-086
# text = Fuck Clampett cops, fuck Eldrin Bell
1	Fuck	O	-	-
2	Clampett	O	-	-
3	cops	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	fuck	O	-	-
6	Eldrin	B-PER	-	-
7	Bell	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_POWER-020
# text = Fuck SNL and the whole cast
1	Fuck	O	-	-
2	SNL	B-ORG	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	whole	O	-	-
6	cast	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Stan-015
# text = If I have a daughter, guess what I'ma call her? I'ma name her Bonnie
1	If	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	have	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	daughter	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	guess	O	-	-
8	what	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	ma	O	-	-
12	call	O	-	-
13	her	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-
15	I	O	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	ma	O	-	-
18	name	O	-	-
19	her	O	-	-
20	Bonnie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Low_Life-076
# text = Got some bitch from Follies with us (Getting high, getting high, getting high, everybody getting high)
1	Got	O	-	-
2	some	O	-	-
3	bitch	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	Follies	B-ORG	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	us	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Getting	O	-	-
10	high	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	getting	O	-	-
13	high	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	getting	O	-	-
16	high	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	everybody	O	-	-
19	getting	O	-	-
20	high	O	-	-
21	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Godzilla-002
# text = I can swallow a bottle of alcohol and I'll feel like Godzilla
1	I	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	swallow	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	bottle	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	alcohol	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	ll	O	-	-
12	feel	O	-	-
13	like	O	-	-
14	Godzilla	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Runnin-045
# text = (If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon' shoot you)
1	(	O	-	-
2	If	O	-	-
3	Young	B-ORG	-	-
4	Metro	I-ORG	-	-
5	don	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	t	O	-	-
8	trust	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	gon	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	shoot	O	-	-
17	you	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Nas_X_DONT_WANT_IT-017
# text = Lil Nas X (Lil Nas X)
1	Lil	B-PER	-	-
2	Nas	I-PER	-	-
3	X	I-PER	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Lil	B-PER	-	-
6	Nas	I-PER	-	-
7	X	I-PER	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Travis_Scott_TELEKINESIS-009
# text = Shawty give me mop with the less, it don't last (Last)
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	give	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	mop	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	less	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	don	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	last	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Last	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Act_a_fool-072
# text = Y'all just go pay homage (Wallace)
1	Y	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	all	O	-	-
4	just	O	-	-
5	go	O	-	-
6	pay	O	-	-
7	homage	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Wallace	B-PER	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_el_Diablo-002
# text = (RONNY J, please turn me up)
1	(	O	-	-
2	RONNY	B-PER	-	-
3	J	I-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	please	O	-	-
6	turn	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	up	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Izzo_H_O_V_A_-038
# text = Yeah, Hov is back, life stories told through rap
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Hov	B-PER	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	back	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	life	O	-	-
8	stories	O	-	-
9	told	O	-	-
10	through	O	-	-
11	rap	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Push_It-029
# text = Tailor made the linen, no gators got on my hater-vision
1	Tailor	O	-	-
2	made	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	linen	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	no	O	-	-
7	gators	O	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	hater	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	vision	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_2_Of_Amerikaz_Most_Wanted-004
# text = Eh, light that up, Snoop, why you actin' like that?
1	Eh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	light	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	up	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	why	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	actin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	like	O	-	-
14	that	O	-	-
15	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Triumph-112
# text = Hands like Sonny Liston, get fly permission
1	Hands	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	Sonny	B-PER	-	-
4	Liston	I-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	get	O	-	-
7	fly	O	-	-
8	permission	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_AmeriKKKa_s_Most_Wanted-016
# text = Will the boys in the hood have to beat down Ice Cube?
1	Will	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	boys	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	hood	O	-	-
7	have	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	beat	O	-	-
10	down	O	-	-
11	Ice	B-PER	-	-
12	Cube	I-PER	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Signs-040
# text = But you ain't have that Snoop Doggy Dogg Style
1	But	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	ain	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	have	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
9	Doggy	I-PER	-	-
10	Dogg	I-PER	-	-
11	Style	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_6_Foot_7_Foot-069
# text = Pause for this dumber speech, I glow like Buddha
1	Pause	O	-	-
2	for	O	-	-
3	this	O	-	-
4	dumber	O	-	-
5	speech	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	glow	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	Buddha	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_Yucky_Blucky_Fruitcake-023
# text = Doechii is a dick, I never fit in
1	Doechii	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	dick	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	never	O	-	-
8	fit	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cam_ron_Welcome_to_New_York_City-051
# text = Watch him 'fore he watch you (Get 'em), Killa
1	Watch	O	-	-
2	him	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	fore	O	-	-
5	he	O	-	-
6	watch	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Get	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	em	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Killa	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Changes-063
# text = It's war on the streets and the war in the Middle East (Ooh, yeah)
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	war	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	streets	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	war	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	Middle	B-LOC	-	-
14	East	I-LOC	-	-
15	(	O	-	-
16	Ooh	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	yeah	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Wild_Boy-034
# text = I'm screamin' "Riverdale" everywhere I go (Uh)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	screamin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	"	O	-	-
7	Riverdale	B-LOC	-	-
8	"	O	-	-
9	everywhere	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	go	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Uh	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Stan-072
# text = Dear Stan, I meant to write you sooner, but I just been busy
1	Dear	O	-	-
2	Stan	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	meant	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	write	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	sooner	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	but	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	just	O	-	-
14	been	O	-	-
15	busy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_All_About_U-075
# text = That was in the homeboy Warren G video
1	That	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	homeboy	O	-	-
6	Warren	B-PER	-	-
7	G	I-PER	-	-
8	video	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Not_Afraid-076
# text = Holla if you feel like you've been down the same road (Same road, same-)
1	Holla	O	-	-
2	if	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	feel	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	ve	O	-	-
9	been	O	-	-
10	down	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	same	O	-	-
13	road	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Same	O	-	-
16	road	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	same	O	-	-
19	-	O	-	-
20	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Barbie_dreams-045
# text = I been a five-star bitch, man, word to Gotti
1	I	O	-	-
2	been	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	five	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	star	O	-	-
7	bitch	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	man	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	word	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	Gotti	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Izzo_H_O_V_A_-022
# text = Cops want to knock me, D.A. wants to box me in
1	Cops	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	knock	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	D	B-ORG	-	-
8	.	I-ORG	-	-
9	A	I-ORG	-	-
10	.	I-ORG	-	-
11	wants	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	box	O	-	-
14	me	O	-	-
15	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Goodbyes-031
# text = You're Barbie life doll, it's Nicki Minaj
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	Barbie	O	-	-
5	life	O	-	-
6	doll	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	Nicki	B-PER	-	-
12	Minaj	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_DENIAL_IS_A_RIVER-002
# text = What's up, Doechii?
1	What	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Doechii	B-PER	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Bomb_Intro_Pass_That_Dutch-021
# text = Heavy hitter, rhyme spitter, call me Rerun
1	Heavy	O	-	-
2	hitter	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	rhyme	O	-	-
5	spitter	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	call	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	Rerun	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__1970_Somethin_-045
# text = Tell the captain to ask Rog' What's Happenin'?
1	Tell	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	captain	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	ask	O	-	-
6	Rog	B-PER	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	What	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	Happenin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Purple-067
# text = And Celie, Oprah and Danny Glover gots to feel me
1	And	O	-	-
2	Celie	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Oprah	B-PER	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	Danny	B-PER	-	-
7	Glover	I-PER	-	-
8	gots	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	feel	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Purple-066
# text = This Color Purple'll make Whoopi give me the pussy
1	This	O	-	-
2	Color	O	-	-
3	Purple	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ll	O	-	-
6	make	O	-	-
7	Whoopi	B-PER	-	-
8	give	O	-	-
9	me	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	pussy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-J_Cole_a_m_a_r_i-012
# text = Now I'm at the Garden sittin' half court
1	Now	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	at	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Garden	B-LOC	-	-
8	sittin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	half	O	-	-
11	court	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Act_a_fool-059
# text = You see this watch, you raise your eyes, it's Rocky Maivia (Hahaha)
1	You	O	-	-
2	see	O	-	-
3	this	O	-	-
4	watch	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	raise	O	-	-
8	your	O	-	-
9	eyes	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	Rocky	B-PER	-	-
15	Maivia	I-PER	-	-
16	(	O	-	-
17	Hahaha	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_My_Chick_Bad-039
# text = Friday the 13th, guess who's playing Jason
1	Friday	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	13th	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	guess	O	-	-
6	who	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	playing	O	-	-
10	Jason	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Megan_Thee_Stallion_Megan_s_Piano-036
# text = I run shit, probably how I got a deal with Nike
1	I	O	-	-
2	run	O	-	-
3	shit	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	probably	O	-	-
6	how	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	deal	O	-	-
11	with	O	-	-
12	Nike	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Who_Am_I_What_s_My_Name_-004
# text = Snoop Doggy Dogg (The bomb)
1	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
2	Doggy	I-PER	-	-
3	Dogg	I-PER	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	The	O	-	-
6	bomb	O	-	-
7	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Saint_Tropez-038
# text = I'm in Saint-Tropez, I had to check wrist
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	Saint	B-LOC	-	-
6	-	I-LOC	-	-
7	Tropez	I-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	had	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	check	O	-	-
13	wrist	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Soulja_Girl-009
# text = & (Soulja Boy)
1	&	O	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	Soulja	B-PER	-	-
4	Boy	I-PER	-	-
5	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_SpottieOttieDopaliscious-002
# text = Damn, damn, damn, James
1	Damn	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	damn	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	damn	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	James	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Get_It_Together-013
# text = See, I've got heart like John Starks
1	See	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ve	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	heart	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	John	B-PER	-	-
10	Starks	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_What_It_Is_Block_Boy_-057
# text = J. White Did It (Yup, yup)
1	J	B-PER	-	-
2	.	I-PER	-	-
3	White	I-PER	-	-
4	Did	O	-	-
5	It	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Yup	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yup	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Hey_Porsche-009
# text = I take you on the road, hey, Porsche girl
1	I	O	-	-
2	take	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	road	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	hey	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Porsche	B-ORG	-	-
11	girl	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_Yah_Mean-007
# text = Money sittin' tall, Yao Ming (What? Beep)
1	Money	O	-	-
2	sittin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	tall	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Yao	B-PER	-	-
7	Ming	I-PER	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	What	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	Beep	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_LOYALTY_-009
# text = Kung Fu Kenny now
1	Kung	O	-	-
2	Fu	O	-	-
3	Kenny	B-PER	-	-
4	now	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Rick_Morty-011
# text = Rick, Rick, Rick, Rick
1	Rick	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Rick	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Rick	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Rick	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Bring_Da_Ruckus-011
# text = Aww shit, Wu-Tang Clan spark the wicks, an'
1	Aww	O	-	-
2	shit	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Wu	B-ORG	-	-
5	-	I-ORG	-	-
6	Tang	I-ORG	-	-
7	Clan	I-ORG	-	-
8	spark	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	wicks	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	an	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Ni_as_In_Paris-045
# text = 'Cause I was him, I would have married Kate and Ashley
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	him	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	would	O	-	-
9	have	O	-	-
10	married	O	-	-
11	Kate	B-PER	-	-
12	and	O	-	-
13	Ashley	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lord_Tariq_and_Peter_Gunz_Deja_Vu_Uptown_Baby_-058
# text = Bronx most wanted, front get confronted
1	Bronx	B-LOC	-	-
2	most	O	-	-
3	wanted	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	front	O	-	-
6	get	O	-	-
7	confronted	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lord_Tariq_and_Peter_Gunz_Deja_Vu_Uptown_Baby_-048
# text = I'm comfortable like Recaro, two quarters of my life
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	comfortable	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Recaro	B-ORG	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	two	O	-	-
9	quarters	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	my	O	-	-
12	life	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_Black_Skinhead-020
# text = 300 bitches, where the Trojans?
1	300	O	-	-
2	bitches	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	where	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Trojans	B-ORG	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Fine_China-008
# text = Shorty like a thousand dollar plate, fine china
1	Shorty	B-PER	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	thousand	O	-	-
5	dollar	O	-	-
6	plate	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	fine	O	-	-
9	china	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Lay_Low-028
# text = I flip, faster than birds, Snoop Dogg will emerge
1	I	O	-	-
2	flip	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	faster	O	-	-
5	than	O	-	-
6	birds	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
9	Dogg	I-PER	-	-
10	will	O	-	-
11	emerge	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_I_Think_She_Like_Me-017
# text = Ricky Ronaldo, really when I'm in Portugal
1	Ricky	B-PER	-	-
2	Ronaldo	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	really	O	-	-
5	when	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Portugal	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lauryn_Hill_Superstar-039
# text = I used to work at Foot Locker, they fired me: I fronted
1	I	O	-	-
2	used	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	work	O	-	-
5	at	O	-	-
6	Foot	B-ORG	-	-
7	Locker	I-ORG	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	they	O	-	-
10	fired	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	:	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	fronted	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_Yucky_Blucky_Fruitcake-086
# text = That was quite the introduction, Doechii
1	That	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	quite	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	introduction	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Doechii	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly__1-061
# text = I heat the booth – Nelly actin' so uncouth
1	I	O	-	-
2	heat	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	booth	O	-	-
5	–	O	-	-
6	Nelly	B-PER	-	-
7	actin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-
10	uncouth	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Heart_Of_A_Champion-050
# text = A Vietnam vet, lil' derrty I thought I told ya
1	A	O	-	-
2	Vietnam	B-LOC	-	-
3	vet	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	lil	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	derrty	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	thought	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	told	O	-	-
12	ya	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Gossip_Folks-028
# text = Izzo kizzay
1	Izzo	O	-	-
2	kizzay	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_Baby_By_Me-054
# text = (Shawty said take it off, I'll take it off)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
3	said	O	-	-
4	take	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	off	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ll	O	-	-
11	take	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-
13	off	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_2_Of_Amerikaz_Most_Wanted-067
# text = Floatin' in the black Benz (Baitch), tryin' to do a show a day
1	Floatin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	black	O	-	-
6	Benz	B-ORG	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Baitch	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	tryin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	to	O	-	-
14	do	O	-	-
15	a	O	-	-
16	show	O	-	-
17	a	O	-	-
18	day	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jermaine_Dupri_Welcome_to_Atlanta-043
# text = Since the Lakeshore/MD rivalry
1	Since	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Lakeshore	B-LOC	-	-
4	/	O	-	-
5	MD	B-LOC	-	-
6	rivalry	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Iggy_Azalea_Lola-050
# text = Lola, I don't blame you
1	Lola	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	don	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	blame	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Vanilla_Ice_Play_That_Funky_Music-067
# text = Cause the lyrics belong to ICE, You can call me Dad
1	Cause	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	lyrics	O	-	-
4	belong	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	ICE	B-ORG	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	You	O	-	-
9	can	O	-	-
10	call	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	Dad	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Ghostface_Killers-025
# text = Don't burn in the coupe, it's an Italy (Italy)
1	Don	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	burn	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	coupe	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	s	O	-	-
12	an	O	-	-
13	Italy	B-LOC	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Italy	B-LOC	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-50_cent_21_Questions
# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_21_Questions-001
# text = New York City
1	New	B-LOC	-	-
2	York	I-LOC	-	-
3	City	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Godzilla-039
# text = If you never gave a damn (Ayy), raise your hand
1	If	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	never	O	-	-
4	gave	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	damn	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Ayy	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	raise	O	-	-
12	your	O	-	-
13	hand	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Lay_Low-005
# text = Ayy, ayy, Snoop, what up? This your nigga Dre
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	ayy	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	what	O	-	-
8	up	O	-	-
9	?	O	-	-
10	This	O	-	-
11	your	O	-	-
12	nigga	O	-	-
13	Dre	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_By_the_time_I_get_to_arizona-008
# text = Of the cell block, but they come from California
1	Of	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	cell	O	-	-
4	block	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	but	O	-	-
7	they	O	-	-
8	come	O	-	-
9	from	O	-	-
10	California	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Iggy_Azalea_Murda_Bizness-038
# text = Shoot nigga with the swag, Doc Holliday
1	Shoot	O	-	-
2	nigga	O	-	-
3	with	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	swag	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Doc	B-PER	-	-
8	Holliday	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Country_Grammar_Hot_Shit_-042
# text = Chi-Town, K.C., Motown to Alabama
1	Chi	B-LOC	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	Town	I-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	K	B-LOC	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	C	I-LOC	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Motown	B-LOC	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	Alabama	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sir_Mix_a_Lot_Posse_on_Broadway-028
# text = Maharaji's on the def side dancing like a freak
1	Maharaji	B-PER	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	def	O	-	-
7	side	O	-	-
8	dancing	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	freak	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Neon_Guts-020
# text = Yeah, you never stayed in Kailua (Hawaii)
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	never	O	-	-
5	stayed	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Kailua	B-LOC	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Hawaii	B-LOC	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Rainbows-006
# text = Hope, they don't know (They don't know nothin)
1	Hope	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	don	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	They	O	-	-
10	don	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	know	O	-	-
14	nothin	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_B_O_B_Bombs_Over_Baghdad-072
# text = When you come to ATL, boy, you better not hide
1	When	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	come	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	ATL	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	boy	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	better	O	-	-
11	not	O	-	-
12	hide	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Travis_Scott_5_TINT-020
# text = Took her to the endzone from the Enzo (Yah)
1	Took	O	-	-
2	her	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	endzone	O	-	-
6	from	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	Enzo	B-ORG	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Yah	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_California_Love-009
# text = A state that's untouchable like Eliot Ness
1	A	O	-	-
2	state	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	untouchable	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	Eliot	B-PER	-	-
9	Ness	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-J_Cole_Neighbors-012
# text = As I write this, the team down in Austin
1	As	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	write	O	-	-
4	this	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	team	O	-	-
8	down	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Austin	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Brooklyn_s_Finest-068
# text = (Bushwick) You don't stop
1	(	O	-	-
2	Bushwick	B-LOC	-	-
3	)	O	-	-
4	You	O	-	-
5	don	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	t	O	-	-
8	stop	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sir_Mix_a_Lot_Posse_on_Broadway-060
# text = Kid Sensation dropped a 20 and didn't even miss it
1	Kid	B-PER	-	-
2	Sensation	I-PER	-	-
3	dropped	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	20	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	didn	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	t	O	-	-
10	even	O	-	-
11	miss	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_03_Bonnie_Clyde-002
# text = You ready, B?
1	You	O	-	-
2	ready	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	B	B-PER	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Nas_X_DONT_WANT_IT-018
# text = The number one song on the Billboard Hot 100
1	The	O	-	-
2	number	O	-	-
3	one	O	-	-
4	song	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Billboard	B-ORG	-	-
8	Hot	I-ORG	-	-
9	100	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_New_Patek-061
# text = MCM, yeah, that shit made out of ostrich, bruh (Ayy)
1	MCM	B-ORG	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	shit	O	-	-
7	made	O	-	-
8	out	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	ostrich	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	bruh	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Ayy	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Nas_Is_Like-057
# text = (Nas is like...) Sex to a nympho, but nothin' sweet
1	(	O	-	-
2	Nas	B-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-
9	Sex	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	nympho	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	but	O	-	-
15	nothin	O	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	sweet	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Who_Am_I_What_s_My_Name_-056
# text = Snoopy Dogg and the Dogg Pound (Dog, the bomb)
1	Snoopy	B-PER	-	-
2	Dogg	I-PER	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Dogg	B-ORG	-	-
6	Pound	I-ORG	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Dog	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	bomb	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Notorious_Thugs-005
# text = It's Bone and Biggie, Biggie (Rock the party, party)
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	Bone	B-PER	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	Biggie	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Biggie	B-PER	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Rock	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	party	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	party	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Jermaine_Dupri_Welcome_to_Atlanta-044
# text = When Frozen Paradise was the place to be
1	When	O	-	-
2	Frozen	B-LOC	-	-
3	Paradise	I-LOC	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	place	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	be	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_California_Love-046
# text = South Central
1	South	B-LOC	-	-
2	Central	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Drake_Nice_For_What-059
# text = (BlaqNmilD, you a genius, you diggin' me?)
1	(	O	-	-
2	BlaqNmilD	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	genius	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	diggin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kool_G_Rap_Streets_of_New_York-068
# text = That’s how it is, in the streets of New York
1	That	O	-	-
2	’	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	how	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	streets	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	New	B-LOC	-	-
13	York	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Da_Mystery_of_Chessboxin_-065
# text = Introducin' the Ghostface Killah
1	Introducin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Ghostface	B-PER	-	-
5	Killah	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Brooklyn_s_Finest-072
# text = Made a fortune off Peru, extradite, China white heroin
1	Made	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	fortune	O	-	-
4	off	O	-	-
5	Peru	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	extradite	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	China	B-LOC	-	-
10	white	O	-	-
11	heroin	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Travis_Scott_I_KNOW_-028
# text = I know, mami, I know (Know), it's 2 a.m., don't stress (Stress)
1	I	O	-	-
2	know	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	mami	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Know	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	s	O	-	-
15	2	O	-	-
16	a	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	m	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	don	O	-	-
22	'	O	-	-
23	t	O	-	-
24	stress	O	-	-
25	(	O	-	-
26	Stress	O	-	-
27	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Candy-020
# text = Play with death like I'm Billy & Mandy, yeah
1	Play	O	-	-
2	with	O	-	-
3	death	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	Billy	B-PER	-	-
9	&	O	-	-
10	Mandy	B-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_6_Foot_7_Foot-027
# text = Had my heart broken by this woman named Tammy
1	Had	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	heart	O	-	-
4	broken	O	-	-
5	by	O	-	-
6	this	O	-	-
7	woman	O	-	-
8	named	O	-	-
9	Tammy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Big_Ego_s-050
# text = Take yo' honey and cruise to the Snooty and snooze
1	Take	O	-	-
2	yo	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	honey	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	cruise	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Snooty	B-LOC	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	snooze	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Numb-040
# text = Numb the pain with the money and I ride 'round with that Tommy
1	Numb	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	pain	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	money	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	ride	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	round	O	-	-
12	with	O	-	-
13	that	O	-	-
14	Tommy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_The_Message-007
# text = Montana way, the Good F-E-L-L-A, verbal AK spray
1	Montana	B-LOC	-	-
2	way	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Good	O	-	-
6	F	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	E	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	L	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	L	O	-	-
13	-	O	-	-
14	A	O	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	verbal	O	-	-
17	AK	B-ORG	-	-
18	spray	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Ms_Jackson-027
# text = Ms. Jackson
1	Ms	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Jackson	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Make_Her_Say-001
# text = Kid Cudi
1	Kid	B-PER	-	-
2	Cudi	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_NISSAN_ALTIMA-010
# text = Doechii cooler than a fan, but she get hotter than a sauna
1	Doechii	B-PER	-	-
2	cooler	O	-	-
3	than	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	fan	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	but	O	-	-
8	she	O	-	-
9	get	O	-	-
10	hotter	O	-	-
11	than	O	-	-
12	a	O	-	-
13	sauna	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_B_M_F_Blowin_Money_Fast_-009
# text = I think I'm Big Meech (Woo), Larry Hoover (Woo)
1	I	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	Big	B-PER	-	-
7	Meech	I-PER	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Woo	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Larry	B-PER	-	-
13	Hoover	I-PER	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Woo	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Eminem_When_I_m_gone
# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_When_I_m_gone-001
# text = Yeah, it's my life (Hey, Hailie)
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	life	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Hey	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Hailie	B-PER	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_Crazy-005
# text = And a bitch been shopping all day, no Macy's
1	And	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	bitch	O	-	-
4	been	O	-	-
5	shopping	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	day	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	no	O	-	-
10	Macy	B-ORG	-	-
11	'	I-ORG	-	-
12	s	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cardi_B_Money-047
# text = You'da bet Cardi a freak (Freak)
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	da	O	-	-
4	bet	O	-	-
5	Cardi	B-PER	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	freak	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Freak	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Dead_Presidents-017
# text = Pissin' on these bitches is a fetish (R. Kelly)
1	Pissin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	these	O	-	-
5	bitches	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	fetish	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	R	B-PER	-	-
11	.	I-PER	-	-
12	Kelly	I-PER	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Hit_Em_Up-082
# text = Softer than Alizé with a chaser
1	Softer	O	-	-
2	than	O	-	-
3	Alizé	B-PER	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	chaser	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Brown_Humpin_Around-064
# text = Yo Stylz, kick it
1	Yo	O	-	-
2	Stylz	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	kick	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_All_mine-023
# text = Almost what got Tristan single
1	Almost	O	-	-
2	what	O	-	-
3	got	O	-	-
4	Tristan	B-PER	-	-
5	single	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Brooklyn_s_Finest-085
# text = Brook-nam, sippin' on
1	Brook	B-LOC	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	nam	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	sippin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Southernplayalisticadillacmuzik-065
# text = Atlanta skies be blue, the sun is beaming, it's seemin'
1	Atlanta	B-LOC	-	-
2	skies	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	blue	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	sun	O	-	-
8	is	O	-	-
9	beaming	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	seemin	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Usher_Yeah_-059
# text = Me and Ursh once more and we leaves 'em dead
1	Me	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Ursh	B-PER	-	-
4	once	O	-	-
5	more	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	we	O	-	-
8	leaves	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	em	O	-	-
11	dead	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_Foreign-019
# text = I got the motherfuckin' Ike, huh
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	motherfuckin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	Ike	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	huh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Megan_Thee_Stallion_Hot_Girl_Summer-020
# text = Fuckin' 9-to-5 niggas with that superstar D ('Star D)
1	Fuckin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	9	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	5	O	-	-
8	niggas	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	that	O	-	-
11	superstar	O	-	-
12	D	B-PER	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	Star	B-PER	-	-
16	D	I-PER	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Wild_Boy-019
# text = Levi's, put your kitty on it (Yeah), start grindin' like the Clipse is on it (Woo)
1	Levi	B-ORG	-	-
2	'	I-ORG	-	-
3	s	I-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	put	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	kitty	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Yeah	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	start	O	-	-
15	grindin	O	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	like	O	-	-
18	the	O	-	-
19	Clipse	B-ORG	-	-
20	is	O	-	-
21	on	O	-	-
22	it	O	-	-
23	(	O	-	-
24	Woo	O	-	-
25	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-DJ_Quik_Born_Raised_in_Compton-014
# text = Never trickster, DJ Quikster steals the show
1	Never	O	-	-
2	trickster	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	DJ	B-PER	-	-
5	Quikster	I-PER	-	-
6	steals	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	show	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_asmr-012
# text = I come from the 6 where they chalk up lames (On God)
1	I	O	-	-
2	come	O	-	-
3	from	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	6	B-LOC	-	-
6	where	O	-	-
7	they	O	-	-
8	chalk	O	-	-
9	up	O	-	-
10	lames	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	On	O	-	-
13	God	B-PER	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Mr_Right_Now-011
# text = But I don't treat her like she my fiancée (On God)
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	treat	O	-	-
7	her	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	she	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	fiancée	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	On	O	-	-
14	God	B-PER	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Till_I_Die-034
# text = Everyday I feel like El Chapo (Boom)
1	Everyday	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	feel	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	El	B-PER	-	-
6	Chapo	I-PER	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Boom	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_NISSAN_ALTIMA-012
# text = Wine and dine her, Benihana, I'm the new hip-hop Madonna
1	Wine	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	dine	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Benihana	B-ORG	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	m	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	new	O	-	-
13	hip	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	hop	O	-	-
16	Madonna	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Great_Day-011
# text = Prepare to get hurt and mangled like Kurt Angle rookie year
1	Prepare	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	get	O	-	-
4	hurt	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	mangled	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	Kurt	B-PER	-	-
9	Angle	I-PER	-	-
10	rookie	O	-	-
11	year	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Will_Smith_Miami-057
# text = 'Cause you gotta have cheese for the summerhouse piece on South Beach
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	gotta	O	-	-
5	have	O	-	-
6	cheese	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	summerhouse	O	-	-
10	piece	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	South	B-LOC	-	-
13	Beach	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_No_Vaseline-011
# text = That punk Ice Cube—
1	That	O	-	-
2	punk	O	-	-
3	Ice	B-PER	-	-
4	Cube	I-PER	-	-
5	—	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doja_Cat_Rules-041
# text = Nigga wan' spy on the pussy like Austin
1	Nigga	O	-	-
2	wan	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	spy	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	pussy	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Austin	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Rick_Morty-007
# text = (Rick, Rick, Rick, Rick)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Rick	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Rick	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Rick	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Rick	B-PER	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Iggy_Azalea_Switch-010
# text = Is Iggy the ziggy-iggy the baddest of 'em all?
1	Is	O	-	-
2	Iggy	B-PER	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	ziggy	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	iggy	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	baddest	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	em	O	-	-
12	all	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_bloody_valentine-034
# text = Be mine (Ayy)
1	Be	O	-	-
2	mine	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Ayy	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Salt_N_Pepa_Twist_And_Shout-049
# text = Cuz Spinderella does a hell of a job keepin' the record playin'
1	Cuz	O	-	-
2	Spinderella	B-PER	-	-
3	does	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	hell	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	job	O	-	-
9	keepin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	record	O	-	-
13	playin	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_America_s_Most_Blunted-015
# text = A-, A-, A-, America's most blunted
1	A	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	A	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	A	O	-	-
8	-	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	America	B-LOC	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	most	O	-	-
14	blunted	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Runnin_Dying_to_Live_-016
# text = The nigga Biggie Smalls tryna turn into the black Frank White
1	The	O	-	-
2	nigga	O	-	-
3	Biggie	B-PER	-	-
4	Smalls	I-PER	-	-
5	tryna	O	-	-
6	turn	O	-	-
7	into	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	black	O	-	-
10	Frank	B-PER	-	-
11	White	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Lot-073
# text = Dennis Smith, Jr., stay solid, my nigga
1	Dennis	B-PER	-	-
2	Smith	I-PER	-	-
3	,	I-PER	-	-
4	Jr	I-PER	-	-
5	.	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	stay	O	-	-
8	solid	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	nigga	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Triumph-047
# text = Vocabulary Donna talking, tell your story walking
1	Vocabulary	O	-	-
2	Donna	B-PER	-	-
3	talking	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	tell	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	story	O	-	-
8	walking	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_King_Kunta-023
# text = King Kunta, black man taking no losses, oh yeah
1	King	O	-	-
2	Kunta	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	black	O	-	-
5	man	O	-	-
6	taking	O	-	-
7	no	O	-	-
8	losses	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	oh	O	-	-
11	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_99_Problems-049
# text = I try to ignore him, talk to the Lord
1	I	O	-	-
2	try	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	ignore	O	-	-
5	him	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	talk	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Lord	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Drake_Jimmy_Cooks-020
# text = Dread talkin' to you niggas like I'm J. Cole
1	Dread	O	-	-
2	talkin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	niggas	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	m	O	-	-
11	J	B-PER	-	-
12	.	I-PER	-	-
13	Cole	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Keep_Ya_Head_Up-037
# text = Ayo, I remember Marvin Gaye used to sing to me
1	Ayo	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	remember	O	-	-
5	Marvin	B-PER	-	-
6	Gaye	I-PER	-	-
7	used	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	sing	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Triumph-063
# text = Pocket full of shells out the sky, Golden Arms
1	Pocket	O	-	-
2	full	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	shells	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	sky	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Golden	B-PER	-	-
10	Arms	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Tequila_Shots-030
# text = (Yeah) Standin' on the cliff right off Mulholland Drive
1	(	O	-	-
2	Yeah	O	-	-
3	)	O	-	-
4	Standin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	cliff	O	-	-
9	right	O	-	-
10	off	O	-	-
11	Mulholland	B-LOC	-	-
12	Drive	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_B_O_R_Birth_of_Rap_-053
# text = And I'm into weed, I'm gettin chiefy like Kansas
1	And	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	into	O	-	-
6	weed	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	m	O	-	-
11	gettin	O	-	-
12	chiefy	O	-	-
13	like	O	-	-
14	Kansas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Glass_House-024
# text = Just came from Pittsburgh, damn, I miss my homie Mac
1	Just	O	-	-
2	came	O	-	-
3	from	O	-	-
4	Pittsburgh	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	damn	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	miss	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	homie	O	-	-
12	Mac	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Nasty_Girl-102
# text = Bad Boy, Sho Nuff, Sho Nuff! (Notorious!)
1	Bad	B-ORG	-	-
2	Boy	I-ORG	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Sho	O	-	-
5	Nuff	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Sho	O	-	-
8	Nuff	O	-	-
9	!	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Notorious	B-PER	-	-
12	!	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_Cent_In_Da_Club-011
# text = Niggas heard I fuck with Drew, now they wanna show me love
1	Niggas	O	-	-
2	heard	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	fuck	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	Drew	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	now	O	-	-
9	they	O	-	-
10	wanna	O	-	-
11	show	O	-	-
12	me	O	-	-
13	love	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Cut_dat_check-027
# text = Ayy, pull up in a Bentley, swagger of the century
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	pull	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	Bentley	B-ORG	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	swagger	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	century	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_DENIAL_IS_A_RIVER-060
# text = I like doin' Hollywood shit, snort it? Probably would
1	I	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	doin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
6	shit	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	snort	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	Probably	O	-	-
12	would	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Hail_Mary-050
# text = Now hail Mary, nigga
1	Now	O	-	-
2	hail	O	-	-
3	Mary	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	nigga	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Otis-050
# text = Jay is chillin' (Uh), Ye is chillin' (Uh)
1	Jay	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	chillin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Uh	O	-	-
7	)	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Ye	O	-	-
10	is	O	-	-
11	chillin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Uh	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Truffle_Butter-061
# text = Skateboard, I'm gnarly, Drake, Tunechi, and Barbie, you know
1	Skateboard	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	gnarly	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Drake	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Tunechi	B-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	and	O	-	-
13	Barbie	B-PER	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	you	O	-	-
16	know	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_A_Milli-004
# text = Mack, I'm going in
1	Mack	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	going	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Anaconda-033
# text = So I pulled up in the Jag, Mayweather with the jab like (Hey)
1	So	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	pulled	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Jag	B-ORG	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Mayweather	B-PER	-	-
10	with	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	jab	O	-	-
13	like	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Hey	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Without_Me-074
# text = I am the worst thing since Elvis Presley
1	I	O	-	-
2	am	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	worst	O	-	-
5	thing	O	-	-
6	since	O	-	-
7	Elvis	B-PER	-	-
8	Presley	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cardi_B_Up-005
# text = Racks stack up Shaq height
1	Racks	O	-	-
2	stack	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	Shaq	B-PER	-	-
5	height	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Rich_As_Fuck-017
# text = And that's 2 Chainz
1	And	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	2	B-ORG	-	-
6	Chainz	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_My_Chick_Bad-037
# text = Runnin' down the court I'm dunkin' on 'em, Lisa Leslie
1	Runnin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	down	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	court	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	dunkin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	em	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Lisa	B-PER	-	-
16	Leslie	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_6_Foot_7_Foot-019
# text = Young Money runnin' shit, and you niggas just runner-ups
1	Young	B-ORG	-	-
2	Money	I-ORG	-	-
3	runnin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	shit	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	niggas	O	-	-
10	just	O	-	-
11	runner	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	ups	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tyler_The_Creator_I_THINK-008
# text = Man, I wish you would call me (Skate)
1	Man	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	wish	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	would	O	-	-
7	call	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Skate	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Stan-027
# text = But you coulda signed an autograph for Matthew
1	But	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	coulda	O	-	-
4	signed	O	-	-
5	an	O	-	-
6	autograph	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	Matthew	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_Not_Like_Us-031
# text = Did Cole foul, I don't know why you still pretendin'
1	Did	O	-	-
2	Cole	B-PER	-	-
3	foul	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	don	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	know	O	-	-
10	why	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	still	O	-	-
13	pretendin	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_Phoenix-018
# text = Kurt Cobain even died cause you scrutinize
1	Kurt	B-PER	-	-
2	Cobain	I-PER	-	-
3	even	O	-	-
4	died	O	-	-
5	cause	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	scrutinize	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Shake_Your_Rump-008
# text = My man MCA's got a beard like a billy goat
1	My	O	-	-
2	man	O	-	-
3	MCA	B-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	beard	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	billy	O	-	-
12	goat	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_What_Up_Gangsta-002
# text = We could get the drama poppin', we don't care (Buck, buck, buck)
1	We	O	-	-
2	could	O	-	-
3	get	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	drama	O	-	-
6	poppin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	don	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	care	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Buck	B-PER	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	buck	O	-	-
18	,	O	-	-
19	buck	O	-	-
20	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_It_Ain_t_Hard_to_Tell-008
# text = Nas is like the Afrocentric Asian, half-man, half-amazin
1	Nas	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Afrocentric	O	-	-
6	Asian	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	half	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	man	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	half	O	-	-
13	-	O	-	-
14	amazin	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_Poetic_Justice-061
# text = Ayy, you over here for Sherane, homie?
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	over	O	-	-
5	here	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	Sherane	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	homie	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_A_AP_Forever-042
# text = I got Goyard by the sack
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	Goyard	B-ORG	-	-
4	by	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	sack	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Nasty_Girl-098
# text = (We adore you)Diddy, Jazzy Fizzle, Nelly Nel, Jagged Edge
1	(	O	-	-
2	We	O	-	-
3	adore	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	Diddy	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Jazzy	B-PER	-	-
9	Fizzle	I-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Nelly	B-PER	-	-
12	Nel	I-PER	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Jagged	B-PER	-	-
15	Edge	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Glass_House-023
# text = Look, wish Lil Peep and me had spoke, but I can't get that back
1	Look	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	wish	O	-	-
4	Lil	B-PER	-	-
5	Peep	I-PER	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	had	O	-	-
9	spoke	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	but	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	can	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	t	O	-	-
16	get	O	-	-
17	that	O	-	-
18	back	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Memory_Lane_Sittin_in_da_Park_-068
# text = Comin' outta-a-a-a-a-a-outta Queensbridge
1	Comin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	outta	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	-	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	outta	O	-	-
16	Queensbridge	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Candy_Paint-032
# text = But you don't fuckin' know me, homie, you don't want war (Ayy)
1	But	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	fuckin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	know	O	-	-
9	me	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	homie	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-
14	don	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	t	O	-	-
17	want	O	-	-
18	war	O	-	-
19	(	O	-	-
20	Ayy	O	-	-
21	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Let_Me_Ride-044
# text = Now I'm smellin' like Indonesia
1	Now	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	smellin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	Indonesia	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Usher_Love_in_This_Club-004
# text = Where we at, Polow? (Hey)
1	Where	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Polow	B-PER	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Hey	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Common_I_Used_to_Love_H_E_R_-076
# text = I used to love H.E.R., went and fucked up all the shit, y'all, buss it
1	I	O	-	-
2	used	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	love	O	-	-
5	H	B-PER	-	-
6	.	I-PER	-	-
7	E	I-PER	-	-
8	.	I-PER	-	-
9	R	I-PER	-	-
10	.	I-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	went	O	-	-
13	and	O	-	-
14	fucked	O	-	-
15	up	O	-	-
16	all	O	-	-
17	the	O	-	-
18	shit	O	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	y	O	-	-
21	'	O	-	-
22	all	O	-	-
23	,	O	-	-
24	buss	O	-	-
25	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Let_Me_Ride-032
# text = Just another motherfuckin' day for Dre, so I'll begin like this
1	Just	O	-	-
2	another	O	-	-
3	motherfuckin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	day	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	Dre	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	ll	O	-	-
13	begin	O	-	-
14	like	O	-	-
15	this	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Nasty_Girl-099
# text = You know that we love (J-E)
1	You	O	-	-
2	know	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	love	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	J	B-PER	-	-
8	-	I-PER	-	-
9	E	I-PER	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Sucker_M_C_s_Krush_Groove_1_-010
# text = Dave cut the record down to the bone
1	Dave	B-PER	-	-
2	cut	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	record	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	bone	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Great_Day-014
# text = DOOM, are you pondering what I'm pondering?
1	DOOM	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	are	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	pondering	O	-	-
6	what	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	m	O	-	-
10	pondering	O	-	-
11	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_One_Mic_One_Gun-042
# text = They wanna see me fucked so they could deport me like I'm Shyne
1	They	O	-	-
2	wanna	O	-	-
3	see	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	fucked	O	-	-
6	so	O	-	-
7	they	O	-	-
8	could	O	-	-
9	deport	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	like	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	m	O	-	-
15	Shyne	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Soundtrack_2_My_Life-003
# text = But I'm not Shawn or Martin Louis
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	not	O	-	-
6	Shawn	B-PER	-	-
7	or	O	-	-
8	Martin	B-PER	-	-
9	Louis	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_The_Real_Slim_Shady-038
# text = Will Smith don't gotta cuss in his raps to sell records (Nope)
1	Will	B-PER	-	-
2	Smith	I-PER	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	gotta	O	-	-
7	cuss	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	his	O	-	-
10	raps	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	sell	O	-	-
13	records	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Nope	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Can_t_Trust_it-077
# text = Here I am turn it over Sam
1	Here	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	am	O	-	-
4	turn	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	over	O	-	-
7	Sam	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Heart_Of_A_Champion-005
# text = DID YOU HEAR THAT ELIZABETH? HERE COME THE BIG ONE!
1	DID	O	-	-
2	YOU	O	-	-
3	HEAR	O	-	-
4	THAT	O	-	-
5	ELIZABETH	B-PER	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	HERE	O	-	-
8	COME	O	-	-
9	THE	O	-	-
10	BIG	O	-	-
11	ONE	O	-	-
12	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Hit_Em_Up-114
# text = Fuck Mobb Deep, fuck Biggie
1	Fuck	O	-	-
2	Mobb	B-ORG	-	-
3	Deep	I-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	fuck	O	-	-
6	Biggie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_Not_Like_Us-045
# text = Fucked on Wayne girl while he was in jail, that's connivin'
1	Fucked	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	Wayne	B-PER	-	-
4	girl	O	-	-
5	while	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	was	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	jail	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	connivin	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Rap_God-100
# text = Tried to say I'll take seven kids from Columbine
1	Tried	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	say	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	ll	O	-	-
7	take	O	-	-
8	seven	O	-	-
9	kids	O	-	-
10	from	O	-	-
11	Columbine	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Saint_Tropez-025
# text = I'm in Saint-Tropez, I had to check wrist (Wow)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	Saint	B-LOC	-	-
6	-	I-LOC	-	-
7	Tropez	I-LOC	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	had	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	check	O	-	-
13	wrist	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Wow	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_POWER-024
# text = You short-minded niggas' thoughts is Napoleon
1	You	O	-	-
2	short	O	-	-
3	-	O	-	-
4	minded	O	-	-
5	niggas	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	thoughts	O	-	-
8	is	O	-	-
9	Napoleon	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Pound_the_alarm-008
# text = Some call me Nicki and some call me Roman
1	Some	O	-	-
2	call	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	Nicki	B-PER	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	some	O	-	-
7	call	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	Roman	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Lollipop-034
# text = Shawty want a thug (Shawty want a thug, yeah!)
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	thug	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
7	want	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	thug	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	yeah	O	-	-
12	!	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Gospel-059
# text = (And I what?) I serial kill, and you're Kellogg's (What?)
1	(	O	-	-
2	And	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	what	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	serial	O	-	-
9	kill	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	re	O	-	-
15	Kellogg	B-ORG	-	-
16	'	I-ORG	-	-
17	s	I-ORG	-	-
18	(	O	-	-
19	What	O	-	-
20	?	O	-	-
21	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Don_t_Believe_the_Hype-080
# text = Harry Allen—I gotta ask him
1	Harry	B-PER	-	-
2	Allen	I-PER	-	-
3	—	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	gotta	O	-	-
6	ask	O	-	-
7	him	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Fivio_Foreign_Kanye_West_and_Alicia_Keys_City_of_Gods-002
# text = New York City, please go easy on me tonight
1	New	B-LOC	-	-
2	York	I-LOC	-	-
3	City	I-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	please	O	-	-
6	go	O	-	-
7	easy	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	me	O	-	-
10	tonight	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Candy_Paint-019
# text = Goddamn, I love paper like I'm Michael Scott (Yeah)
1	Goddamn	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	love	O	-	-
5	paper	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	m	O	-	-
10	Michael	B-PER	-	-
11	Scott	I-PER	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Yeah	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Life_Goes_On-019
# text = I love them niggas to death, I'm drinkin' Hennessy
1	I	O	-	-
2	love	O	-	-
3	them	O	-	-
4	niggas	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	death	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	m	O	-	-
11	drinkin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	Hennessy	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Nasty_Girl-005
# text = Notorious B.I.G., Notorious B.I.G. & Avery Storm, Avery Storm, *Diddy*
1	Notorious	B-PER 	-	-
2	B	I-PER	-	-
3	.	I-PER 	-	-
4	I	I-PER 	-	-
5	.	I-PER 	-	-
6	G	I-PER 	-	-
7	.	I-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Notorious	B-PER	-	-
10	B	I-PER	-	-
11	.	I-PER	-	-
12	I	I-PER	-	-
13	.	I-PER	-	-
14	G	I-PER	-	-
15	.	I-PER	-	-
16	&	O	-	-
17	Avery	B-PER	-	-
18	Storm	I-PER	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	Avery	B-PER	-	-
21	Storm	I-PER	-	-
22	,	O	-	-
23	*	O	-	-
24	Diddy	B-PER	-	-
25	*	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_Babushka_Boi-008
# text = Eight Gs for the dancers (Ayy)
1	Eight	O	-	-
2	Gs	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	dancers	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Ayy	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Travis_Scott_MELTDOWN-064
# text = I'll shoot your ass in Walmart like I'm DaBaby (In Walmart)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	shoot	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	ass	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Walmart	B-LOC	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	m	O	-	-
13	DaBaby	B-PER	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	In	O	-	-
16	Walmart	B-LOC	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-N_W_A__Straight_Outta_Compton-076
# text = Looking for the one they call Eazy
1	Looking	O	-	-
2	for	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	one	O	-	-
5	they	O	-	-
6	call	O	-	-
7	Eazy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_The_Real_Slim_Shady-026
# text = By the time they hit fourth grade they've got the Discovery Channel, don't they?
1	By	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	time	O	-	-
4	they	O	-	-
5	hit	O	-	-
6	fourth	O	-	-
7	grade	O	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ve	O	-	-
11	got	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	Discovery	B-ORG	-	-
14	Channel	I-ORG	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	don	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-
18	t	O	-	-
19	they	O	-	-
20	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_The_Devil_Is_A_Lie-013
# text = Nigga switching lane to lane like Wal-Mart
1	Nigga	O	-	-
2	switching	O	-	-
3	lane	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	lane	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	Wal	B-ORG	-	-
8	-	I-ORG	-	-
9	Mart	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Bang_Bang-005
# text = Niggas still playa hating, but Dre ain't changed
1	Niggas	O	-	-
2	still	O	-	-
3	playa	O	-	-
4	hating	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	but	O	-	-
7	Dre	B-PER	-	-
8	ain	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	changed	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-XXXTENTACION_Moonlight-010
# text = I don't need no Smith & Wesson, no
1	I	O	-	-
2	don	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	need	O	-	-
6	no	O	-	-
7	Smith	B-ORG	-	-
8	&	I-ORG	-	-
9	Wesson	I-ORG	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	no	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_R_I_P_-028
# text = I got a bitch, Rihanna bad, ooh, the bitch got a box
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	bitch	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Rihanna	B-PER	-	-
7	bad	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	ooh	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	bitch	O	-	-
13	got	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	box	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_How_To_Love-025
# text = Like you never had a love (Ayy), uh, had a love (Ayy)
1	Like	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	never	O	-	-
4	had	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	love	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Ayy	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	uh	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	had	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	love	O	-	-
16	(	O	-	-
17	Ayy	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_1Train-067
# text = Antsy 'cause I'm high like Michael Jackson, penny loafers
1	Antsy	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	cause	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	high	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Michael	B-PER	-	-
10	Jackson	I-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	penny	O	-	-
13	loafers	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-DJ_Quik_Born_Raised_in_Compton-053
# text = DJ Quik is in the mothafuckin' house
1	DJ	B-PER	-	-
2	Quik	I-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	mothafuckin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	house	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Gold_Roses-034
# text = Ayy, woah
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	woah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Show_Out-010
# text = And they got guns same size as Kevin Hart
1	And	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	got	O	-	-
4	guns	O	-	-
5	same	O	-	-
6	size	O	-	-
7	as	O	-	-
8	Kevin	B-PER	-	-
9	Hart	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Nas_Is_Like-073
# text = Nas is like
1	Nas	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Just_What_I_Am-006
# text = Ain't no such thing as Satan, evil is what you make it
1	Ain	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	no	O	-	-
5	such	O	-	-
6	thing	O	-	-
7	as	O	-	-
8	Satan	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	evil	O	-	-
11	is	O	-	-
12	what	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-
14	make	O	-	-
15	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Salt_N_Pepa_None_Of_Your_Business-043
# text = Yo, Pep-Pep's got a ill rep
1	Yo	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Pep	B-PER	-	-
4	-	I-PER	-	-
5	Pep	I-PER	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	ill	O	-	-
11	rep	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Mona_Lisa-084
# text = Mona Lisa, I done painted the picture
1	Mona	B-PER	-	-
2	Lisa	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	done	O	-	-
6	painted	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	picture	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Lot-069
# text = I pray for Markelle 'cause they fucked up his shot
1	I	O	-	-
2	pray	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	Markelle	B-PER	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	cause	O	-	-
7	they	O	-	-
8	fucked	O	-	-
9	up	O	-	-
10	his	O	-	-
11	shot	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_What_Up_Gangsta-003
# text = It's going down (Buck), 'cause I'm around (Buck)
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	going	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Buck	B-PER	-	-
8	)	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	cause	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	m	O	-	-
15	around	O	-	-
16	(	O	-	-
17	Buck	B-PER	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Aston_Martin_Music-025
# text = Elroy Jetson: I'm somewhere out in space
1	Elroy	B-PER	-	-
2	Jetson	I-PER	-	-
3	:	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	somewhere	O	-	-
8	out	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	space	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_Runaway_Love-028
# text = Little Nicole is only ten years old
1	Little	O	-	-
2	Nicole	B-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	only	O	-	-
5	ten	O	-	-
6	years	O	-	-
7	old	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Brooklyn_s_Finest-078
# text = If Fay' had twins, she'd probably have two Pacs (uh)
1	If	O	-	-
2	Fay	B-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	had	O	-	-
5	twins	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	she	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	d	O	-	-
10	probably	O	-	-
11	have	O	-	-
12	two	O	-	-
13	Pacs	B-PER	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	uh	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-N_W_A__Straight_Outta_Compton-065
# text = Eazy is his name, and the boy is coming
1	Eazy	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	his	O	-	-
4	name	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	boy	O	-	-
9	is	O	-	-
10	coming	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Hard_Work_Pays_Off-033
# text = Breaking your ankle, Chris Paul
1	Breaking	O	-	-
2	your	O	-	-
3	ankle	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Chris	B-PER	-	-
6	Paul	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Christmas_In_Hollis-026
# text = The rhymes that you hear are the rhymes of Darryl's
1	The	O	-	-
2	rhymes	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	hear	O	-	-
6	are	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	rhymes	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	Darryl	B-PER	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_asmr-044
# text = Chopper clapped his ass, he thought a hand hit him (Ha)
1	Chopper	B-PER	-	-
2	clapped	O	-	-
3	his	O	-	-
4	ass	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	thought	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	hand	O	-	-
10	hit	O	-	-
11	him	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Ha	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Nas_Is_Like-041
# text = Went from Seiko to Rolex, ownin' acres
1	Went	O	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	Seiko	B-ORG	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	Rolex	B-ORG	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	ownin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	acres	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Good_Cop_Bad_Cop-018
# text = Cube kidnap your mind, Patty Hearst
1	Cube	O	-	-
2	kidnap	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	mind	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Patty	B-PER	-	-
7	Hearst	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Work_It-057
# text = Kunta Kinte a slave again, no sir
1	Kunta	B-PER	-	-
2	Kinte	I-PER	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	slave	O	-	-
5	again	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	no	O	-	-
8	sir	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Elevators_Me_You_-037
# text = And they looking like Halle Berrys
1	And	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	looking	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Halle	B-PER	-	-
6	Berrys	I-PER	-	-

# newdoc id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Rich_As_Fuck
# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Rich_As_Fuck-001
# text = Ugh, AK on my nightstand, right next to that Bible
1	Ugh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	AK	B-ORG	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	nightstand	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	right	O	-	-
9	next	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	Bible	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Barbie_dreams-021
# text = Meek still be in my DMs, I be havin' to duck him
1	Meek	B-PER	-	-
2	still	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	DMs	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	be	O	-	-
10	havin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	duck	O	-	-
14	him	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Sauce_It_Up-050
# text = I swear I'm a stunner like Steve Austin
1	I	O	-	-
2	swear	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	stunner	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Steve	B-PER	-	-
10	Austin	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_E_I_-035
# text = I drive fastly, call me Jeff Gord-on in the Black SS with the naviga-tion
1	I	O	-	-
2	drive	O	-	-
3	fastly	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	call	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	Jeff	B-PER	-	-
8	Gord	I-PER	-	-
9	-	I-PER	-	-
10	on	I-PER	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	Black	B-ORG	-	-
14	SS	I-ORG	-
15	with	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	naviga	O	-	-
18	-	O	-	-
19	tion	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Nasty_Girl-098
# text = (We adore you)Diddy, Jazzy Fizzle, Nelly Nel, Jagged Edge
1	(	O	-	-
2	We	O	-	-
3	adore	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	Diddy	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Jazzy	B-PER	-	-
9	Fizzle	I-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Nelly	B-PER	-	-
12	Nel	I-PER	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Jagged	B-PER	-	-
15	Edge	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Clipse_Virginia-034
# text = I miss you Shampoo, we miss you Shampoo
1	I	O	-	-
2	miss	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	Shampoo	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	miss	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	Shampoo	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_No_Sleep_Till_Brooklyn-002
# text = Brooklyn
1	Brooklyn	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Beats_to_the_Rhyme-014
# text = (He's Jam Master Jay, I'm D.M.C.)
1	(	O	-	-
2	He	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	Jam	B-PER	-	-
6	Master	I-PER	-	-
7	Jay	I-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	D	B-PER	-	-
13	.	I-PER	-	-
14	M	I-PER	-	-
15	.	I-PER	-	-
16	C	I-PER	-	-
17	.	I-PER	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_I_Need_A_Doctor-045
# text = Dre, I'm cryin' in this booth
1	Dre	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	cryin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	this	O	-	-
10	booth	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Truffle_Butter-060
# text = And born in New Orleans, get killed for Jordans
1	And	O	-	-
2	born	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	New	B-LOC	-	-
5	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	get	O	-	-
8	killed	O	-	-
9	for	O	-	-
10	Jordans	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_It_Ain_t_Hard_to_Tell-014
# text = Nas, stories by Aesop, place your loot up, parties I shoot up
1	Nas	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	stories	O	-	-
4	by	O	-	-
5	Aesop	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	place	O	-	-
8	your	O	-	-
9	loot	O	-	-
10	up	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	parties	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	shoot	O	-	-
15	up	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_Not_Like_Us-029
# text = You think the Bay gon' let you disrespect Pac, nigga?
1	You	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Bay	B-LOC	-	-
5	gon	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	let	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	disrespect	O	-	-
10	Pac	B-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	nigga	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Body_Movin_-035
# text = MCA, where have you been?
1	MCA	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	where	O	-	-
4	have	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	been	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Congratulations-055
# text = Yeah, we made it (Ayy)
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	made	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Ayy	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Throw_It_Back-012
# text = Missy, Missy, Missy, go 'head, let it slap (Slap)
1	Missy	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Missy	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Missy	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	go	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	head	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	let	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-
13	slap	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Slap	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Shame_On_a_Nigga-013
# text = Yo, RZA, yo, razor—hit me with the major
1	Yo	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	RZA	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	yo	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	razor	O	-	-
8	—	O	-	-
9	hit	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	with	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	major	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Rick_Morty-014
# text = Rick and Morty (Yeah), Rick and Morty
1	Rick	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Morty	B-PER	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Yeah	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Rick	B-PER	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	Morty	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Signs-018
# text = If somethin' go wrong then you know we get to Crippin'
1	If	O	-	-
2	somethin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	go	O	-	-
5	wrong	O	-	-
6	then	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	know	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	get	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	Crippin	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Rap_God-047
# text = Lakim Shabazz, 2Pac, N.W.A, Cube, hey Doc, Ren
1	Lakim	B-PER	-	-
2	Shabazz	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	2Pac	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	N	B-PER	-	-
7	.	I-PER	-	-
8	W	I-PER	-	-
9	.	I-PER	-	-
10	A	I-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Cube	B-PER	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	hey	O	-	-
15	Doc	B-PER	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	Ren	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Megan_Thee_Stallion_HISS-074
# text = Why every time one of y'all Z-list hoes do an interview, I get mentioned? (Ayy, look)
1	Why	O	-	-
2	every	O	-	-
3	time	O	-	-
4	one	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	y	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	all	O	-	-
9	Z	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	list	O	-	-
12	hoes	O	-	-
13	do	O	-	-
14	an	O	-	-
15	interview	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	I	O	-	-
18	get	O	-	-
19	mentioned	O	-	-
20	?	O	-	-
21	(	O	-	-
22	Ayy	O	-	-
23	,	O	-	-
24	look	O	-	-
25	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Mrs_Officer-050
# text = Rodney King baby said "Beat it like a cop"
1	Rodney	B-PER	-	-
2	King	I-PER	-	-
3	baby	O	-	-
4	said	O	-	-
5	"	O	-	-
6	Beat	O	-	-
7	it	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	cop	O	-	-
11	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_SpottieOttieDopaliscious-032
# text = "Now, who else wanna fuck with Hollywood Court?"
1	"	O	-	-
2	Now	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	who	O	-	-
5	else	O	-	-
6	wanna	O	-	-
7	fuck	O	-	-
8	with	O	-	-
9	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
10	Court	I-LOC	-	-
11	?	O	-	-
12	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Neon_Guts-031
# text = Stay at the Ritz-Carlton, this not the Radisson
1	Stay	O	-	-
2	at	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Ritz	B-LOC	-	-
5	-	I-LOC	-	-
6	Carlton	I-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	this	O	-	-
9	not	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	Radisson	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Travis_Scott_STARGAZING-016
# text = We propellin', up top with Ellen, uh (With the choppers)
1	We	O	-	-
2	propellin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	up	O	-	-
6	top	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	Ellen	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	uh	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	With	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	choppers	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kool_G_Rap_Streets_of_New_York-002
# text = In the streets of New York
1	In	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	streets	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	New	B-LOC	-	-
6	York	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Iggy_Azalea_Change_Your_Life-029
# text = Put you up in Neiman Marcus where you supposed to shop
1	Put	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	Neiman	B-ORG	-	-
6	Marcus	I-ORG	-	-
7	where	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	supposed	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	shop	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_Cent_In_Da_Club-019
# text = But holla in New York them niggas l tell ya I'm loco
1	But	O	-	-
2	holla	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	New	B-LOC	-	-
5	York	I-LOC	-	-
6	them	O	-	-
7	niggas	O	-	-
8	l	O	-	-
9	tell	O	-	-
10	ya	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	loco	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Immortal-069
# text = Chopper cut you up like Kitana (Ching-ching)
1	Chopper	O	-	-
2	cut	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Kitana	B-PER	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Ching	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	ching	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Da_Art_of_Storytellin_-041
# text = Rhyme got strong, mind got blown
1	Rhyme	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	strong	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	mind	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	blown	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_DENIAL_IS_A_RIVER-070
# text = Okay, Doechii
1	Okay	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Doechii	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_The_Percocet_Stripper_Joint-033
# text = I talk for them niggas that feel this shit out in Belgium
1	I	O	-	-
2	talk	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	them	O	-	-
5	niggas	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	feel	O	-	-
8	this	O	-	-
9	shit	O	-	-
10	out	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	Belgium	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Sorry-004
# text = Maybach Music
1	Maybach	B-ORG	-	-
2	Music	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Renegade-079
# text = The new Ice Cube, motherfuckers hate to like you
1	The	O	-	-
2	new	O	-	-
3	Ice	B-PER	-	-
4	Cube	I-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	motherfuckers	O	-	-
7	hate	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-J_Cole_She_Knows-004
# text = And you find yourself praying up to Heaven above
1	And	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	find	O	-	-
4	yourself	O	-	-
5	praying	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Heaven	B-LOC	-	-
9	above	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_Nosebleeds-017
# text = Guess you'll never live to see the day that Doechii loses
1	Guess	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	ll	O	-	-
5	never	O	-	-
6	live	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	see	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	day	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	Doechii	B-PER	-	-
13	loses	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Get_Money-024
# text = Cases in Virginia, body in D.C.
1	Cases	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	Virginia	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	body	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	D	B-LOC	-	-
8	.	I-LOC	-	-
9	C	I-LOC	-	-
10	.	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_RAP_DEVIL-044
# text = Hello, Marshall, my name's Colson, you should go back to Recovery (Phew)
1	Hello	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Marshall	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	name	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	Colson	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	should	O	-	-
13	go	O	-	-
14	back	O	-	-
15	to	O	-	-
16	Recovery	O	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Phew	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_All_Falls_Down-020
# text = Couldn't afford a car, so she named her daughter Alexis
1	Couldn	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	afford	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	car	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	so	O	-	-
9	she	O	-	-
10	named	O	-	-
11	her	O	-	-
12	daughter	O	-	-
13	Alexis	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_drunk_face-032
# text = I'll grow up (I have sinned, don't help me, Jesus)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ll	O	-	-
4	grow	O	-	-
5	up	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	have	O	-	-
9	sinned	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	don	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	t	O	-	-
14	help	O	-	-
15	me	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	Jesus	B-PER	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Psycho-029
# text = Ayy, take you to the smoke shop
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	smoke	O	-	-
8	shop	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Shake_Your_Rump-020
# text = Chillin' at the beach, down at Club Med
1	Chillin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	beach	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	down	O	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	Club	B-LOC	-	-
10	Med	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Rich_As_Fuck-027
# text = I turned a penny to a motherfuckin Janet Jackson
1	I	O	-	-
2	turned	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	penny	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	motherfuckin	O	-	-
8	Janet	B-PER	-	-
9	Jackson	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Stay_Schemin-050
# text = Dwight Howard on the post, dawg (Huh)
1	Dwight	B-PER	-	-
2	Howard	I-PER	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	post	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	dawg	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Huh	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Baby_Pluto-010
# text = That's why I be racin' 'em (BRABUS)
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	why	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	racin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	em	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	BRABUS	B-ORG	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_tv_off-059
# text = Walk in New Orleans with the etiquette of LA, yellin'
1	Walk	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	New	B-LOC	-	-
4	Orleans	I-LOC	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	etiquette	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	LA	B-LOC	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	yellin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Rock_Box-071
# text = The, the Hollis, Hollis crew, crew
1	The	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Hollis	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Hollis	B-LOC	-	-
7	crew	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	crew	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Heart_Of_A_Champion-002
# text = I guess he's back 'urr derrty, STL derby
1	I	O	-	-
2	guess	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	back	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	urr	O	-	-
9	derrty	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	STL	B-LOC	-	-
12	derby	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Mona_Lisa-019
# text = I'm up in here feeling like Celie, ooh
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	here	O	-	-
7	feeling	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Celie	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	ooh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Ms_Jackson-024
# text = You say it's puppy love, we say it's full-grown (Arroof)
1	You	O	-	-
2	say	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	puppy	O	-	-
7	love	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	say	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	full	O	-	-
15	-	O	-	-
16	grown	O	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Arroof	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Fine_China-005
# text = Shorty like a, uh
1	Shorty	B-PER	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	uh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mac_Miller_Cinderella-047
# text = It look like Dorothy ain't in Kansas anymore, I do you like a chore
1	It	O	-	-
2	look	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	Dorothy	B-PER	-	-
5	ain	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	t	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Kansas	B-LOC	-	-
10	anymore	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	do	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	like	O	-	-
16	a	O	-	-
17	chore	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_Money_Trees-038
# text = Two bullets in my Uncle Tony head (My Tony head, my Tony head)
1	Two	O	-	-
2	bullets	O	-	-
3	in	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	Uncle	O	-	-
6	Tony	B-PER	-	-
7	head	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	My	O	-	-
10	Tony	O	-	-
11	head	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	my	O	-	-
14	Tony	B-PER	-	-
15	head	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Bitch_Please-069
# text = That's the Devil, they always wanna dance
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Devil	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	they	O	-	-
8	always	O	-	-
9	wanna	O	-	-
10	dance	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_2_Of_Amerikaz_Most_Wanted-046
# text = Another warrant, 2 of Amerikaz Most Wanted
1	Another	O	-	-
2	warrant	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	2	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	Amerikaz	O	-	-
7	Most	O	-	-
8	Wanted	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Moment_4_Life-037
# text = Shout out to the CEO, 500 Degreez
1	Shout	O	-	-
2	out	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	CEO	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	500	O	-	-
8	Degreez	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Here_I_Am-016
# text = I even up the doors to the financial estates (Ross)
1	I	O	-	-
2	even	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	doors	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	financial	O	-	-
9	estates	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Ross	B-PER	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Bring_Da_Ruckus-061
# text = Slip up and get fucked like Suzette
1	Slip	O	-	-
2	up	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	get	O	-	-
5	fucked	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	Suzette	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Rebel_Without_A_pause-034
# text = Yo, Chuck, you gettin' 'em nervous
1	Yo	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Chuck	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	gettin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	em	O	-	-
10	nervous	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__My_Adidas-034
# text = It's Adidas on my feet, high top or low
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	Adidas	B-ORG	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	feet	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	high	O	-	-
10	top	O	-	-
11	or	O	-	-
12	low	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Gangsta_Rap_Made_Me_Do_It-019
# text = I'm Utah: I got multiple bitches
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	Utah	B-LOC	-	-
5	:	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	got	O	-	-
8	multiple	O	-	-
9	bitches	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_How_To_Love-039
# text = You're beautiful (Ayy), yeah
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	beautiful	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Ayy	O	-	-
7	)	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Rick_Morty-030
# text = I'm on a whole 'nother planet with Rick and Morty (Morty)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	whole	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	nother	O	-	-
9	planet	O	-	-
10	with	O	-	-
11	Rick	B-PER	-	-
12	and	O	-	-
13	Morty	B-PER	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Morty	B-PER	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_A_Milli-020
# text = You pop 'em 'cause we pop 'em like Orville Redenbacher
1	You	O	-	-
2	pop	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	em	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	cause	O	-	-
7	we	O	-	-
8	pop	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	em	O	-	-
11	like	O	-	-
12	Orville	B-PER	-	-
13	Redenbacher	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Country_Grammar_Hot_Shit_-050
# text = Flows, I kick 'em freely mon, especially off Remi, mon
1	Flows	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	kick	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	em	O	-	-
7	freely	O	-	-
8	mon	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	especially	O	-	-
11	off	O	-	-
12	Remi	B-ORG	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	mon	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Rockstar-033
# text = They like, "Savage, why you got a 12 car garage
1	They	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	Savage	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	why	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	got	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	12	O	-	-
12	car	O	-	-
13	garage	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Crank_That_Soulja_Boy_-023
# text = When I do dat Soulja Boy
1	When	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	dat	O	-	-
5	Soulja	B-PER	-	-
6	Boy	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Ain_t_No_Fun_If_The_Homies_Can_t_Have_None_-038
# text = I'm Kurupt, ho, you'll never be my only one
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	Kurupt	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	ho	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ll	O	-	-
11	never	O	-	-
12	be	O	-	-
13	my	O	-	-
14	only	O	-	-
15	one	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Report_Card-011
# text = Ayy! (Throw some D's.. throw some D's-throw some D's)
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Throw	O	-	-
5	some	O	-	-
6	D	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	throw	O	-	-
12	some	O	-	-
13	D	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	s	O	-	-
16	-	O	-	-
17	throw	O	-	-
18	some	O	-	-
19	D	O	-	-
20	'	O	-	-
21	s	O	-	-
22	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Right_Above_It-032
# text = And you niggas know I rep my gang like Jessie James
1	And	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	niggas	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	rep	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	gang	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	Jessie	B-PER	-	-
11	James	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_New_Patek-126
# text = I got a bae in the Bay (Ayy)
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	bae	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Bay	B-LOC	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Ayy	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Will_Smith_Miami-048
# text = But on the sneak, Miami bringin' heat for real
1	But	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	sneak	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Miami	B-LOC	-	-
7	bringin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	heat	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	real	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Diced_Pineapples-053
# text = I'ma trip, go to Cannes, France to catch a flick
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	ma	O	-	-
4	trip	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	go	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Cannes	B-LOC	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	France	B-LOC	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	catch	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	flick	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Barbie_dreams-075
# text = ¡Dimelo, papi, papi!
1	¡	O	-	-
2	Dimelo	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	papi	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	papi	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Batter_Up-004
# text = This is my co-host, Bob Buttafuoco
1	This	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	co	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	host	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Bob	B-PER	-	-
9	Buttafuoco	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Gucci_Bandanna-044
# text = (Ayy) Gucci bandana, Gucci, Gucci bandana (Ayy)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Ayy	O	-	-
3	)	O	-	-
4	Gucci	B-ORG	-	-
5	bandana	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Gucci	B-ORG	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Gucci	B-ORG	-	-
10	bandana	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Ayy	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_My_Name_Is-035
# text = And try to touch your hands like some screamin' Usher fans
1	And	O	-	-
2	try	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	touch	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	hands	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	some	O	-	-
9	screamin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	Usher	B-PER	-	-
12	fans	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Trap_Trap_Trap-027
# text = Brown bag legend when it's all cash (Stop talking)
1	Brown	O	-	-
2	bag	O	-	-
3	legend	O	-	-
4	when	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	all	O	-	-
9	cash	O	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Stop	O	-	-
12	talking	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Dark_Queen-038
# text = That was way before I was Lil Uzi Vert (1600, Lil Uzi Vert)
1	That	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	way	O	-	-
4	before	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	was	O	-	-
7	Lil	B-PER	-	-
8	Uzi	I-PER	-	-
9	Vert	I-PER	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	1600	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Lil	B-PER	-	-
14	Uzi	I-PER	-	-
15	Vert	I-PER	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Bang_Bang-032
# text = On every corner, Cali niggas are dumping
1	On	O	-	-
2	every	O	-	-
3	corner	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Cali	B-LOC	-	-
6	niggas	O	-	-
7	are	O	-	-
8	dumping	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_A_Milli-058
# text = Even Gwen Stefani said she couldn't doubt me
1	Even	O	-	-
2	Gwen	B-PER	-	-
3	Stefani	I-PER	-	-
4	said	O	-	-
5	she	O	-	-
6	couldn	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	doubt	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Salt_N_Pepa_Expression-012
# text = And everything Rob got he got from Robin
1	And	O	-	-
2	everything	O	-	-
3	Rob	B-PER	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	he	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	from	O	-	-
8	Robin	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Bapes-018
# text = Asking me: "Soulja Boy, where you get your shoes?" (Ayy)
1	Asking	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	:	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	Soulja	B-PER	-	-
6	Boy	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	where	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	get	O	-	-
11	your	O	-	-
12	shoes	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-
14	"	O	-	-
15	(	O	-	-
16	Ayy	O	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_She_Will-049
# text = And she bad, so maybe she won't, uh, but shit, then again, maybe she will, yeah (Carter IV, baby, alright, well alright, well alright, uh, Tunechi)
1	And	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	bad	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	so	O	-	-
6	maybe	O	-	-
7	she	O	-	-
8	won	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	uh	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	but	O	-	-
15	shit	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	then	O	-	-
18	again	O	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	maybe	O	-	-
21	she	O	-	-
22	will	O	-	-
23	,	O	-	-
24	yeah	O	-	-
25	(	O	-	-
26	Carter	O	-	-
27	IV	O	-	-
28	,	O	-	-
29	baby	O	-	-
30	,	O	-	-
31	alright	O	-	-
32	,	O	-	-
33	well	O	-	-
34	alright	O	-	-
35	,	O	-	-
36	well	O	-	-
37	alright	O	-	-
38	,	O	-	-
39	uh	O	-	-
40	,	O	-	-
41	Tunechi	B-PER	-	-
42	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Homecoming-043
# text = Yeah, yeah (Drip so hard), it's Lil Uzi Vert
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Drip	O	-	-
6	so	O	-	-
7	hard	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	Lil	B-PER	-	-
14	Uzi	I-PER	-	-
15	Vert	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Barbie_Tingz-056
# text = Big Barbie tingz, that's Barbie tingz
1	Big	O	-	-
2	Barbie	B-PER	-	-
3	tingz	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	Barbie	B-PER	-	-
9	tingz	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Don_t_Believe_the_Hype-074
# text = (Yo, Chuck, they must be on the pipe, right?)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Yo	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Chuck	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	they	O	-	-
7	must	O	-	-
8	be	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	pipe	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	right	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lauryn_Hill_To_Zion-019
# text = Than to wait at Zion's door
1	Than	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	wait	O	-	-
4	at	O	-	-
5	Zion	B-LOC	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	door	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_B_M_F_Blowin_Money_Fast_-037
# text = I think I'm Big Meech (Woo), Larry Hoover (Ross, what up?)
1	I	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	Big	B-PER	-	-
7	Meech	I-PER	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Woo	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Larry	B-PER	-	-
13	Hoover	I-PER	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Ross	B-PER	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	what	O	-	-
18	up	O	-	-
19	?	O	-	-
20	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_The_Potion-037
# text = Got pop potential, stay black like Bob Johnson
1	Got	O	-	-
2	pop	O	-	-
3	potential	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	stay	O	-	-
6	black	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	Bob	B-PER	-	-
9	Johnson	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_Rollout_My_Business_-025
# text = PlayStation 2 up in the ride, is that Lorenzo-kitted?
1	PlayStation	O	-	-
2	2	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	ride	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	is	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	Lorenzo	B-ORG	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	kitted	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Make_Her_Say-053
# text = Down, down for a damn, Cudi already said it
1	Down	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	down	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	damn	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Cudi	B-PER	-	-
9	already	O	-	-
10	said	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Raid-031
# text = My niggas take "No" like Kobe
1	My	O	-	-
2	niggas	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	No	O	-	-
6	"	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	Kobe	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Mask_Off-020
# text = Ocean air (Air), cruisin' Biscayne (Big foreigns)
1	Ocean	O	-	-
2	air	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Air	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	cruisin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	Biscayne	B-LOC	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Big	O	-	-
12	foreigns	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Dirt_Off_Your_Shoulder-005
# text = (Uh-huh-uh, Jigga, uh-uh, uh-uh, ugh)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Uh	O	-	-
3	-	O	-	-
4	huh	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	uh	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Jigga	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	uh	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	uh	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	uh	O	-	-
15	-	O	-	-
16	uh	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	ugh	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_2_Of_Amerikaz_Most_Wanted-026
# text = Uh, me and Snoop about to clown
1	Uh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
6	about	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	clown	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_Baby_By_Me-025
# text = Then we be moving as fast as a Nascar rides
1	Then	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	moving	O	-	-
5	as	O	-	-
6	fast	O	-	-
7	as	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	Nascar	B-ORG	-	-
10	rides	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Lay_Low-006
# text = Ayy, man I was thinking I ain't said shit on your whole motherfucking album
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	man	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	thinking	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	ain	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	said	O	-	-
12	shit	O	-	-
13	on	O	-	-
14	your	O	-	-
15	whole	O	-	-
16	motherfucking	O	-	-
17	album	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Gin_and_Juice-032
# text = And get to mackin' to this bitch named Sadie (Sadie?)
1	And	O	-	-
2	get	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	mackin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	this	O	-	-
8	bitch	O	-	-
9	named	O	-	-
10	Sadie	B-PER	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Sadie	B-PER	-	-
13	?	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Sauce_It_Up-008
# text = Lil Uzi Vert
1	Lil	B-PER	-	-
2	Uzi	I-PER	-	-
3	Vert	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Travis_Scott_TELEKINESIS-025
# text = Ride with Wolf and Storm' and some troopers
1	Ride	O	-	-
2	with	O	-	-
3	Wolf	B-PER	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Storm	B-PER	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	some	O	-	-
9	troopers	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Bring_Da_Ruckus-016
# text = I blow spots like Waco, Texas
1	I	O	-	-
2	blow	O	-	-
3	spots	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Waco	B-LOC	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Texas	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Brown_Two_can_play_that_game-038
# text = Hey, yo, Ted, do they know where I'm coming from? (Yep!)
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yo	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Ted	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	do	O	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	know	O	-	-
10	where	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	coming	O	-	-
15	from	O	-	-
16	?	O	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Yep	O	-	-
19	!	O	-	-
20	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lauryn_Hill_Doo_Wop_That_Thing_-019
# text = Now that was the sin that did Jezebel in
1	Now	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	was	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	sin	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	did	O	-	-
8	Jezebel	B-PER	-	-
9	in	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Get_It_Together-044
# text = But I'ma drive the lane like I was Evan Bernard
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	ma	O	-	-
5	drive	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	lane	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	was	O	-	-
11	Evan	B-PER	-	-
12	Bernard	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Lollipop-047
# text = Shawty say the nigga that she with ain't this (Yeah)
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	say	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	nigga	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	she	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	ain	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	this	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Yeah	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_B_O_B_Bombs_Over_Baghdad-065
# text = Moving like Floyd, comin' straight to Florida
1	Moving	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	Floyd	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	comin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	straight	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Florida	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Mary_Mary-016
# text = Mary-Mary-Mary, why you out there stuntin’?
1	Mary	B-PER	-	-
2	-	I-PER	-	-
3	Mary	I-PER	-	-
4	-	I-PER	-	-
5	Mary	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	why	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	out	O	-	-
10	there	O	-	-
11	stuntin	O	-	-
12	’	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Sock_It_2_Me-037
# text = And all you gotta say is, "Missy, go" (Hey)
1	And	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	gotta	O	-	-
5	say	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	"	O	-	-
9	Missy	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	go	O	-	-
12	"	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Hey	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_LOYALTY_-056
# text = That's what God for
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	what	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-
6	for	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Mona_Lisa-047
# text = Mona Lisa, long hair, don't care
1	Mona	B-PER	-	-
2	Lisa	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	long	O	-	-
5	hair	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	don	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	t	O	-	-
10	care	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Till_I_Collapse-042
# text = André from OutKast, Jada, Kurupt, Nas, and then me
1	André	B-PER	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	OutKast	B-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Jada	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Kurupt	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Nas	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	then	O	-	-
13	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Dilemma-037
# text = Sing it for me, K!
1	Sing	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	K	B-PER	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Wow_-026
# text = Me and Dre came for the...
1	Me	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Dre	B-PER	-	-
4	came	O	-	-
5	for	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Glock_in_My_Lap-043
# text = 18 start sellin' hard with Lil B
1	18	O	-	-
2	start	O	-	-
3	sellin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	hard	O	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	Lil	B-PER	-	-
8	B	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_asmr-064
# text = Savage left his gun at home, nigga, yeah, right (Ha)
1	Savage	B-PER	-	-
2	left	O	-	-
3	his	O	-	-
4	gun	O	-	-
5	at	O	-	-
6	home	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	nigga	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	yeah	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	right	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Ha	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Still_D_R_E_-006
# text = Still, doing that shit Andre?
1	Still	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	doing	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	shit	O	-	-
6	Andre	B-PER	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Ghetto_Vet-081
# text = Got to beg the BG's to roll me up the hill
1	Got	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	beg	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	BG	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	roll	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	up	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	hill	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_BOOM_BAP-031
# text = Talk to 'em, Doechii
1	Talk	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	em	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Doechii	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Lay_Low-032
# text = Snoop and Dre give a fuck about what y'all say
1	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Dre	B-PER	-	-
4	give	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	fuck	O	-	-
7	about	O	-	-
8	what	O	-	-
9	y	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	all	O	-	-
12	say	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Hustlin_-047
# text = I touch work, like I'm Convertible Burt (Burt)
1	I	O	-	-
2	touch	O	-	-
3	work	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	Convertible	B-PER	-	-
10	Burt	I-PER	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Burt	B-PER	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Field_Mob_Georgia-017
# text = We some ATL thrashers, scope ya punk and then smash ya
1	We	O	-	-
2	some	O	-	-
3	ATL	B-LOC	-	-
4	thrashers	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	scope	O	-	-
7	ya	O	-	-
8	punk	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	then	O	-	-
11	smash	O	-	-
12	ya	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Lil_Bit-037
# text = I'm the black Tom Brady in this, I'm the GOAT now (Haha)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	black	O	-	-
6	Tom	B-PER	-	-
7	Brady	I-PER	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	this	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	GOAT	O	-	-
16	now	O	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Haha	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Smoke_Some_Weed-004
# text = Chris Farley, Chris Rock, Bob Marley
1	Chris	B-PER	-	-
2	Farley	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Chris	B-PER	-	-
5	Rock	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Bob	B-PER	-	-
8	Marley	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Right_Above_It-004
# text = Flying Holly Grove chicks to my Hollywood shows
1	Flying	O	-	-
2	Holly	B-LOC	-	-
3	Grove	I-LOC	-	-
4	chicks	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
8	shows	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Can_t_C_Me-048
# text = You should've never put my rhymes with Dre
1	You	O	-	-
2	should	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	ve	O	-	-
5	never	O	-	-
6	put	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	rhymes	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	Dre	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Coming_out_strong-049
# text = My brother Casino said you wasn't Freebandz (Freebandz)
1	My	O	-	-
2	brother	O	-	-
3	Casino	B-PER	-	-
4	said	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	wasn	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	Freebandz	B-ORG	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Freebandz	B-ORG	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doja_Cat_Like_That-002
# text = Burr, burr
1	Burr	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	burr	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Lollipop-039
# text = Shawty wanna hump (I like that)
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	wanna	O	-	-
3	hump	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lauryn_Hill_To_Zion-045
# text = Marching, marching, marching, marching (It is in Zion)
1	Marching	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	marching	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	marching	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	marching	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	It	O	-	-
10	is	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	Zion	B-LOC	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_No_Vaseline-069
# text = 'Cause he's going out like Kunta Kinte
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	going	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Kunta	B-PER	-	-
10	Kinte	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Candy_Paint-034
# text = Bitch, I'm young Stoney, I do what I want (Ayy, ayy)
1	Bitch	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	young	O	-	-
7	Stoney	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	do	O	-	-
11	what	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	want	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Ayy	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	ayy	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Country_Grammar_Hot_Shit_-058
# text = Now I'm knockin' like Jehovah; let me in now, let me in now
1	Now	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	m	O	-	-
5	knockin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	Jehovah	B-PER	-	-
9	;	O	-	-
10	let	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	now	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	let	O	-	-
16	me	O	-	-
17	in	O	-	-
18	now	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Get_It_Together-078
# text = But, yo, Tip, what's up with the boots on your feet?
1	But	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yo	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Tip	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	what	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	up	O	-	-
11	with	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	boots	O	-	-
14	on	O	-	-
15	your	O	-	-
16	feet	O	-	-
17	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Usher_DJ_Got_Us_Fallin_In_Love-038
# text = Yabba-dabba-doo, make her bed rock
1	Yabba	O	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	dabba	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	doo	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	make	O	-	-
8	her	O	-	-
9	bed	O	-	-
10	rock	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Immortal-012
# text = I was strapped when I slid inside your boo thang (On God)
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	strapped	O	-	-
4	when	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	slid	O	-	-
7	inside	O	-	-
8	your	O	-	-
9	boo	O	-	-
10	thang	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	On	O	-	-
13	God	B-PER	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Usher_Yeah_-062
# text = Lil Jon got the beat that make ya booty go
1	Lil	B-PER	-	-
2	Jon	I-PER	-	-
3	got	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	beat	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	make	O	-	-
8	ya	O	-	-
9	booty	O	-	-
10	go	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Nas_Is_Like-033
# text = (Nas is like...) Earth, Wind & Fire, rims and tires
1	(	O	-	-
2	Nas	B-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-
9	Earth	B-ORG	-	-
10	,	I-ORG	-	-
11	Wind	I-ORG	-	-
12	&	I-ORG	-	-
13	Fire	I-ORG	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	rims	O	-	-
16	and	O	-	-
17	tires	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doja_Cat_Tia_Tamera-029
# text = I'm on the wall at Genius
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	on	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	wall	O	-	-
7	at	O	-	-
8	Genius	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-J_Cole_m_y_l_i_f_e-023
# text = After The Fall Off, I promise I'm comin' to sellin' out Wrigley's
1	After	O	-	-
2	The	O	-	-
3	Fall	O	-	-
4	Off	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	promise	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	m	O	-	-
11	comin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	to	O	-	-
14	sellin	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	out	O	-	-
17	Wrigley	B-LOC	-	-
18	'	I-LOC	-	-
19	s	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Grillz-036
# text = What it do, baby? It's the iceman, Paul Wall (Yeah)
1	What	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	baby	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	It	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	s	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	iceman	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Paul	B-PER	-	-
14	Wall	I-PER	-	-
15	(	O	-	-
16	Yeah	O	-	-
17	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Barbie_dreams-066
# text = I turn Stefan into Urkel
1	I	O	-	-
2	turn	O	-	-
3	Stefan	B-PER	-	-
4	into	O	-	-
5	Urkel	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Gravel_Pit-055
# text = Jeff from Hamo, ex three bangos
1	Jeff	B-PER	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	Hamo	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	ex	O	-	-
6	three	O	-	-
7	bangos	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Movin_bass-047
# text = New mob, suit sharp, my suit Farrahkhan
1	New	O	-	-
2	mob	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	suit	O	-	-
5	sharp	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	suit	O	-	-
9	Farrahkhan	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Street_Dreams-022
# text = I want it all, ArmorAll Benz and endless papes
1	I	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	ArmorAll	B-ORG	-	-
7	Benz	B-ORG	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	endless	O	-	-
10	papes	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Sanctified-020
# text = You can't ever change that nigga back to Cassius
1	You	O	-	-
2	can	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	ever	O	-	-
6	change	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	nigga	O	-	-
9	back	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	Cassius	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Represent-056
# text = This goes out to everybody in New York
1	This	O	-	-
2	goes	O	-	-
3	out	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	everybody	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	New	B-LOC	-	-
8	York	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_RAP_DEVIL-068
# text = You're not getting better with time, it's fine, Eminem, put down the pen
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	not	O	-	-
5	getting	O	-	-
6	better	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	time	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	fine	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Eminem	B-PER	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	put	O	-	-
18	down	O	-	-
19	the	O	-	-
20	pen	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Lay_Low-063
# text = With Dre on the beat, this ain't nothing but loot
1	With	O	-	-
2	Dre	B-PER	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	beat	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	this	O	-	-
8	ain	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	nothing	O	-	-
12	but	O	-	-
13	loot	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Wild_Boy-024
# text = Nevermind, that's just Kells with that heat
1	Nevermind	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	just	O	-	-
7	Kells	B-PER	-	-
8	with	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	heat	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_Yah_Mean-043
# text = Money sittin' tall, Yao Ming (Money sittin' tall, Yao Ming)
1	Money	O	-	-
2	sittin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	tall	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Yao	B-PER	-	-
7	Ming	I-PER	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Money	O	-	-
10	sittin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	tall	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Yao	B-PER	-	-
15	Ming	I-PER	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Memory_Lane_Sittin_in_da_Park_-065
# text = Comin' outta-a-a-outta-a-a-outta Queensbridge
1	Comin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	outta	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	-	O	-	-
9	outta	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	outta	O	-	-
16	Queensbridge	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_So_What_Cha_Want-003
# text = To the S K B, you don't stop
1	To	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	S	O	-	-
4	K	O	-	-
5	B	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	don	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	stop	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Drake_Laugh_Now_Cry_Later-022
# text = Bring Drake to the hood, surround Drake around Dracs
1	Bring	O	-	-
2	Drake	B-PER	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	hood	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	surround	O	-	-
8	Drake	B-PER	-	-
9	around	O	-	-
10	Dracs	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_High_School-044
# text = Lil Tune
1	Lil	B-PER	-	-
2	Tune	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lord_Tariq_and_Peter_Gunz_Deja_Vu_Uptown_Baby_-073
# text = Uh, The Gun Runners like what
1	Uh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	The	B-ORG	-	-
4	Gun	I-ORG	-	-
5	Runners	I-ORG	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	what	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Nuthin_But_A_G_Thang-009
# text = Death Row is the label that pays me
1	Death	B-ORG	-	-
2	Row	I-ORG	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	label	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	pays	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_Area_Codes-032
# text = I bang cock in Bangkok
1	I	O	-	-
2	bang	O	-	-
3	cock	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	Bangkok	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Elevators_Me_You_-028
# text = Rolling down the strip on Vogues
1	Rolling	O	-	-
2	down	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	strip	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	Vogues	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Affirmative_Action-069
# text = Bet it on, my whole crew is Don Juan
1	Bet	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	whole	O	-	-
7	crew	O	-	-
8	is	O	-	-
9	Don	B-PER	-	-
10	Juan	I-PER	-	-
