# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Brown_Rock_Wit_cha-018
# text = Let's hear some Marvin Gaye, ooh, ooh
1	Let	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	hear	O	-	-
5	some	O	-	-
6	Marvin	B-PER	-	-
7	Gaye	I-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	ooh	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	ooh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Country_Grammar_Hot_Shit_-049
# text = Kid quicker than Billy, mon, talkin' really and I need it mon
1	Kid	O	-	-
2	quicker	O	-	-
3	than	O	-	-
4	Billy	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	mon	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	talkin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	really	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	need	O	-	-
14	it	O	-	-
15	mon	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Rainbows-020
# text = Hope, they don't know (They don't know nothin')
1	Hope	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	don	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	They	O	-	-
10	don	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	t	O	-	-
13	know	O	-	-
14	nothin	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Glass_House-024
# text = Just came from Pittsburgh, damn, I miss my homie Mac
1	Just	O	-	-
2	came	O	-	-
3	from	O	-	-
4	Pittsburgh	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	damn	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	miss	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	homie	O	-	-
12	Mac	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Brooklyn_s_Finest-037
# text = Brooklyn represent y'all, hit you fold
1	Brooklyn	B-LOC	-	-
2	represent	O	-	-
3	y	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	all	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	hit	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	fold	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Luven_Me-068
# text = All the BC's, you know who you are
1	All	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	BC	B-LOC	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	know	O	-	-
9	who	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	are	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_P_I_M_P_-011
# text = An hour later, have that ass up in the Ramada
1	An	O	-	-
2	hour	O	-	-
3	later	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	have	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	ass	O	-	-
8	up	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	Ramada	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Ms_Jackson-024
# text = You say it's puppy love, we say it's full-grown (Arroof)
1	You	O	-	-
2	say	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	puppy	O	-	-
7	love	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	say	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	full	O	-	-
15	-	O	-	-
16	grown	O	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Arroof	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Psycho-029
# text = Ayy, take you to the smoke shop
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	take	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	smoke	O	-	-
8	shop	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Why_We_Thugs-035
# text = Owned by C.A, State Property
1	Owned	O	-	-
2	by	O	-	-
3	C	B-PER	-	-
4	.	I-PER	-	-
5	A	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	State	B-ORG	-	-
8	Property	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_America_s_Most_Blunted-050
# text = America's most blunted
1	America	B-LOC	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	most	O	-	-
5	blunted	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Wu_Tang_Clan_Ain_t_Nuthing_ta_F_Wit-050
# text = My man Kelly Woo from the Gavin
1	My	O	-	-
2	man	O	-	-
3	Kelly	B-PER	-	-
4	Woo	I-PER	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Gavin	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_R_I_P_-028
# text = I got a bitch, Rihanna bad, ooh, the bitch got a box
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	bitch	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Rihanna	B-PER	-	-
7	bad	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	ooh	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	bitch	O	-	-
13	got	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	box	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Da_Art_of_Storytellin_-030
# text = When her and Suzy, yeah, they threw a slumber
1	When	O	-	-
2	her	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	Suzy	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	yeah	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	threw	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	slumber	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Neon_Guts-063
# text = Slick my hair back like I'm Chico DeBarge (Ayy)
1	Slick	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	hair	O	-	-
4	back	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	Chico	B-PER	-	-
10	DeBarge	I-PER	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Ayy	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_Brand_New_Guy-072
# text = Got it jumping like Kriss Kross, mismatching, no jigsaw
1	Got	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	jumping	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Kriss	B-PER	-	-
6	Kross	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	mismatching	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	no	O	-	-
11	jigsaw	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Venom-068
# text = Punk rock, bitch, it's goin' down like Yung Joc
1	Punk	O	-	-
2	rock	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	bitch	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	goin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	down	O	-	-
12	like	O	-	-
13	Yung	B-PER	-	-
14	Joc	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Juicy-082
# text = Biggie Smalls!
1	Biggie	B-PER	-	-
2	Smalls	I-PER	-	-
3	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Country_Grammar_Hot_Shit_-042
# text = Chi-Town, K.C., Motown to Alabama
1	Chi	B-LOC	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	Town	I-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	K	B-LOC	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	C	I-LOC	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Motown	B-LOC	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	Alabama	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Fight_the_power-055
# text = Okay, talk to me about the future of Public Enemy
1	Okay	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	talk	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	about	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	future	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	Public	B-ORG	-	-
11	Enemy	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_E_I_-026
# text = Andele andele, mami, E.I. E.I
1	Andele	O	-	-
2	andele	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	mami	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	E	B-PER	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	I	I-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	E	B-PER	-	-
11	.	O	-	-
12	I	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Drake_Toosie_Slide-030
# text = Nike crossbody, got a piece in it
1	Nike	B-ORG	-	-
2	crossbody	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	piece	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Lollipop-056
# text = Shawty wanna hump (Yeah, I like that)
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	wanna	O	-	-
3	hump	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Yeah	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lord_Tariq_and_Peter_Gunz_Deja_Vu_Uptown_Baby_-079
# text = And Yonkers, play play on and a
1	And	O	-	-
2	Yonkers	B-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	play	O	-	-
5	play	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_What_It_Is_Block_Boy_-057
# text = J. White Did It (Yup, yup)
1	J	B-PER	-	-
2	.	I-PER	-	-
3	White	I-PER	-	-
4	Did	O	-	-
5	It	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Yup	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yup	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Gin_and_Juice-032
# text = And get to mackin' to this bitch named Sadie (Sadie?)
1	And	O	-	-
2	get	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	mackin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	this	O	-	-
8	bitch	O	-	-
9	named	O	-	-
10	Sadie	B-PER	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Sadie	B-PER	-	-
13	?	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tyler_The_Creator_Potato_Salad-031
# text = Where we? Rocky, A$AP
1	Where	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-
4	Rocky	B-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	A	B-PER	-	-
7	$	I-PER	-	-
8	AP	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Smoke_Some_Weed-008
# text = Cypress Hill, Robert Downey hit the bong
1	Cypress	B-LOC	-	-
2	Hill	I-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Robert	B-PER	-	-
5	Downey	I-PER	-	-
6	hit	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	bong	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_Foreign-043
# text = Molly Santana, jaw lockin' (Lockin')
1	Molly	B-PER	-	-
2	Santana	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	jaw	O	-	-
5	lockin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Lockin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Iggy_Azalea_Bounce-013
# text = Pullin' up, NASCAR, black car
1	Pullin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	NASCAR	B-ORG	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	black	O	-	-
8	car	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Lil_Bit-037
# text = I'm the black Tom Brady in this, I'm the GOAT now (Haha)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	black	O	-	-
6	Tom	B-PER	-	-
7	Brady	I-PER	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	this	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	GOAT	O	-	-
16	now	O	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Haha	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Neon_Guts-013
# text = Me and J. Balvin on G5 (Cholo)
1	Me	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	J	B-PER	-	-
4	.	I-PER	-	-
5	Balvin	I-PER	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	G5	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Cholo	B-PER	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Sir_Mix_a_Lot_Posse_on_Broadway-060
# text = Kid Sensation dropped a 20 and didn't even miss it
1	Kid	B-PER	-	-
2	Sensation	I-PER	-	-
3	dropped	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	20	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	didn	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	t	O	-	-
10	even	O	-	-
11	miss	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_No_Vaseline-036
# text = Yella Boy's on your team, so you're losing
1	Yella	B-PER	-	-
2	Boy	I-PER	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	team	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	re	O	-	-
13	losing	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Gossip_Folks-028
# text = Izzo kizzay
1	Izzo	O	-	-
2	kizzay	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_Runaway_Love-058
# text = Erica is stuck up in a world on her own
1	Erica	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	stuck	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	world	O	-	-
8	on	O	-	-
9	her	O	-	-
10	own	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Vanilla_Ice_Ninja_Rap-010
# text = Iceman, Ya know I'm not playin
1	Iceman	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Ya	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	not	O	-	-
9	playin	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doja_Cat_Paint_The_Town_Red-019
# text = I am so much fun without Hennessy
1	I	O	-	-
2	am	O	-	-
3	so	O	-	-
4	much	O	-	-
5	fun	O	-	-
6	without	O	-	-
7	Hennessy	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Megan_Thee_Stallion_Megan_s_Piano-026
# text = Cartier frames, spot a bitch on some lame shit
1	Cartier	B-ORG	-	-
2	frames	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	spot	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	bitch	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	some	O	-	-
9	lame	O	-	-
10	shit	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_March_Madness-058
# text = Fuck a cougar like she Halle Berry
1	Fuck	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	cougar	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	she	O	-	-
6	Halle	B-PER	-	-
7	Berry	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Triumph-063
# text = Pocket full of shells out the sky, Golden Arms
1	Pocket	O	-	-
2	full	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	shells	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	sky	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Golden	B-PER	-	-
10	Arms	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Memory_Lane_Sittin_in_da_Park_-068
# text = Comin' outta-a-a-a-a-a-outta Queensbridge
1	Comin	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	outta	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	-	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	-	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	-	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	outta	O	-	-
16	Queensbridge	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_Vamp_Anthem-036
# text = Vamp
1	Vamp	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lord_Tariq_and_Peter_Gunz_Deja_Vu_Uptown_Baby_-018
# text = Friends call me Gunz, sons call me trife
1	Friends	O	-	-
2	call	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	Gunz	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	sons	O	-	-
7	call	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	trife	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_Nosebleeds-017
# text = Guess you'll never live to see the day that Doechii loses
1	Guess	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	ll	O	-	-
5	never	O	-	-
6	live	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	see	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	day	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	Doechii	B-PER	-	-
13	loses	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Beats_to_the_Rhyme-014
# text = (He's Jam Master Jay, I'm D.M.C.)
1	(	O	-	-
2	He	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	Jam	B-PER	-	-
6	Master	I-PER	-	-
7	Jay	I-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	D	B-PER	-	-
13	.	I-PER	-	-
14	M	I-PER	-	-
15	.	I-PER	-	-
16	C	I-PER	-	-
17	.	I-PER	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Sure_Shot-027
# text = I'm fresh like Dougie when I get my specs
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	fresh	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Dougie	B-PER	-	-
7	when	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	get	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	specs	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Gotta_Have_It-020
# text = Ain't that just like D-Wade? Wait
1	Ain	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	t	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	just	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	D	B-PER	-	-
8	-	I-PER	-	-
9	Wade	I-PER	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	Wait	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_POWER-024
# text = You short-minded niggas' thoughts is Napoleon
1	You	O	-	-
2	short	O	-	-
3	-	O	-	-
4	minded	O	-	-
5	niggas	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	thoughts	O	-	-
8	is	O	-	-
9	Napoleon	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Ghostface_Killers-013
# text = Michael Jackson with this fashion, bitch, I'm dabbin', yeah
1	Michael	B-PER	-	-
2	Jackson	I-PER	-	-
3	with	O	-	-
4	this	O	-	-
5	fashion	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	bitch	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	m	O	-	-
12	dabbin	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Myron-043
# text = Uh, young nigga, no, I ain't changed, Lil Uzi from the 6', baby (Yeah)
1	Uh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	young	O	-	-
4	nigga	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	no	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	ain	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	changed	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Lil	B-PER	-	-
15	Uzi	I-PER	-	-
16	from	O	-	-
17	the	O	-	-
18	6	O	-	-
19	'	O	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	baby	O	-	-
22	(	O	-	-
23	Yeah	O	-	-
24	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Still_D_R_E_-031
# text = Well, hell, me and Snoop, we dippin' again
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	hell	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	dippin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	again	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Better_Now-018
# text = With my brothers like it's Jonas, Jonas
1	With	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	brothers	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	Jonas	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Jonas	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Till_I_Collapse-042
# text = André from OutKast, Jada, Kurupt, Nas, and then me
1	André	B-PER	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	OutKast	B-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Jada	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Kurupt	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Nas	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	then	O	-	-
13	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_Yucky_Blucky_Fruitcake-030
# text = Speak up (Well, Doechii, why don't you tell us what you do in your spare time?)
1	Speak	O	-	-
2	up	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Well	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Doechii	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	why	O	-	-
9	don	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	t	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	tell	O	-	-
14	us	O	-	-
15	what	O	-	-
16	you	O	-	-
17	do	O	-	-
18	in	O	-	-
19	your	O	-	-
20	spare	O	-	-
21	time	O	-	-
22	?	O	-	-
23	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Why_We_Thugs-019
# text = Thank God for Sugarhill
1	Thank	O	-	-
2	God	B-PER	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	Sugarhill	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_You_Was_Right-011
# text = Yeah, cryin' in my arms like a nigga wrecked you (Ayy)
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	cryin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	arms	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	nigga	O	-	-
11	wrecked	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Ayy	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Barbie_Tingz-056
# text = Big Barbie tingz, that's Barbie tingz
1	Big	O	-	-
2	Barbie	B-PER	-	-
3	tingz	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	Barbie	B-PER	-	-
9	tingz	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Get_Money-058
# text = Hallmark cards, sayin', "I apologize"
1	Hallmark	B-ORG	-	-
2	cards	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	sayin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	"	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	apologize	O	-	-
10	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Figaro-010
# text = Villainy, feel him in ya heart chakra, chart-toppa
1	Villainy	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	feel	O	-	-
4	him	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	ya	O	-	-
7	heart	O	-	-
8	chakra	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	chart	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	toppa	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cardi_B_Bartier_Cardi-021
# text = Cartier, Cardi B brain on Offset (21)
1	Cartier	B-ORG	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Cardi	B-PER	-	-
4	B	I-PER	-	-
5	brain	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	Offset	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	21	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Brooklyn_s_Finest-067
# text = (Where we from?) Brooklyn goin' out to all
1	(	O	-	-
2	Where	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	from	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	)	O	-	-
7	Brooklyn	B-LOC	-	-
8	goin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	out	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	all	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Salt_N_Pepa_R_U_Ready-058
# text = With the S and the P, hey, Pep MC
1	With	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	S	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	P	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	hey	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Pep	B-PER	-	-
11	MC	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_bloody_valentine-034
# text = Be mine (Ayy)
1	Be	O	-	-
2	mine	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Ayy	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_I_Need_A_Doctor-070
# text = "Dre, don't leave us like that, man," 'cause—
1	"	O	-	-
2	Dre	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	don	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	leave	O	-	-
8	us	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	that	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	man	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	"	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	cause	O	-	-
17	—	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Shadows_of_Tomorrow-046
# text = Sun Ra
1	Sun	B-PER	-	-
2	Ra	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Trap_Trap_Trap-007
# text = Mmm, bounce (Maybach Music)
1	Mmm	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	bounce	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Maybach	B-ORG	-	-
6	Music	O	-	-
7	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mac_Miller_Congratulations-050
# text = Well, I'm the jealous type, but I swear that ass is what Heaven's like
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	jealous	O	-	-
8	type	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	but	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	swear	O	-	-
13	that	O	-	-
14	ass	O	-	-
15	is	O	-	-
16	what	O	-	-
17	Heaven	B-LOC	-	-
18	'	O	-	-
19	s	O	-	-
20	like	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_Devil_In_A_New_Dress-038
# text = The crib Scarface, could it be more Tony?
1	The	O	-	-
2	crib	O	-	-
3	Scarface	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	could	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	be	O	-	-
8	more	O	-	-
9	Tony	B-PER	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Lay_Low-063
# text = With Dre on the beat, this ain't nothing but loot
1	With	O	-	-
2	Dre	B-PER	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	beat	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	this	O	-	-
8	ain	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	t	O	-	-
11	nothing	O	-	-
12	but	O	-	-
13	loot	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_That_s_That_Shit-031
# text = Snoop Dizzle (Hey), your boy Kells (Hey)
1	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
2	Dizzle	I-PER	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Hey	O	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	your	O	-	-
8	boy	O	-	-
9	Kells	B-PER	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Hey	O	-	-
12	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Da_Mystery_of_Chessboxin_-043
# text = Jacques Cousteau could never get this low
1	Jacques	B-PER	-	-
2	Cousteau	I-PER	-	-
3	could	O	-	-
4	never	O	-	-
5	get	O	-	-
6	this	O	-	-
7	low	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_DENIAL_IS_A_RIVER-002
# text = What's up, Doechii?
1	What	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Doechii	B-PER	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-J_Cole_Can_t_Get_Enugh-028
# text = Kweli, Pimp C, H-Town where Bun get down
1	Kweli	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Pimp	B-PER	-	-
4	C	I-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	H	B-LOC	-	-
7	-	I-LOC	-	-
8	Town	I-LOC	-	-
9	where	O	-	-
10	Bun	B-PER	-	-
11	get	O	-	-
12	down	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_Hustler_s_Ambition-032
# text = Man my co-d's call me Chef Boyar-50
1	Man	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	co	O	-	-
4	-	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	call	O	-	-
9	me	O	-	-
10	Chef	B-PER	-	-
11	Boyar	I-PER	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	50	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_America_s_Most_Blunted-038
# text = America's most blunted (Yeah, yo)
1	America	B-LOC	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	most	O	-	-
5	blunted	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Yeah	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yo	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Player_s_Ball-070
# text = Decatur (College Park), the 'Briar (Southwest Atlanta)
1	Decatur	B-LOC	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	College	B-LOC	-	-
4	Park	I-LOC	-	-
5	)	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	'	B-LOC	-	-
9	Briar	I-LOC	-	-
10	(	O	-	-
11	Southwest	B-LOC	-	-
12	Atlanta	I-LOC	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Sauce_It_Up-038
# text = Persian rug, Aladdin shit
1	Persian	O	-	-
2	rug	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Aladdin	B-PER	-	-
5	shit	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_New_Patek-133
# text = But when I'm in Toronto they treat me like Drake (Oh yeah)
1	But	O	-	-
2	when	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Toronto	B-LOC	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	treat	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	like	O	-	-
12	Drake	B-PER	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Oh	O	-	-
15	yeah	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_A_AP_Forever-042
# text = I got Goyard by the sack
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	Goyard	B-ORG	-	-
4	by	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	sack	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Who_Am_I_What_s_My_Name_-044
# text = With Tha Dogg Pound right behind me
1	With	O	-	-
2	Tha	B-ORG	-	-
3	Dogg	I-ORG	-	-
4	Pound	I-ORG	-	-
5	right	O	-	-
6	behind	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Bitch_Please-022
# text = You fuckin' around with the Sundance Kid and Butch Cassidy
1	You	O	-	-
2	fuckin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	around	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Sundance	B-PER	-	-
8	Kid	I-PER	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	Butch	B-PER	-	-
11	Cassidy	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Numb-040
# text = Numb the pain with the money and I ride 'round with that Tommy
1	Numb	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	pain	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	money	O	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	ride	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	round	O	-	-
12	with	O	-	-
13	that	O	-	-
14	Tommy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_New_Patek-069
# text = New Rollie made me proud of my wrist
1	New	O	-	-
2	Rollie	O	-	-
3	made	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	proud	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	wrist	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cam_ron_Welcome_to_New_York_City-058
# text = Coverage at Centre Street, got Brafman defending me
1	Coverage	O	-	-
2	at	O	-	-
3	Centre	B-LOC	-	-
4	Street	I-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	Brafman	B-PER	-	-
8	defending	O	-	-
9	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lauryn_Hill_Doo_Wop_That_Thing_-054
# text = How you gonna win when you ain't right within? (Bredrin)
1	How	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	gonna	O	-	-
4	win	O	-	-
5	when	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	ain	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	t	O	-	-
10	right	O	-	-
11	within	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Bredrin	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_Black_Skinhead-049
# text = God, God, God
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	God	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	God	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Big_Poppa-014
# text = No need to be greedy I got mad friends with Benz's
1	No	O	-	-
2	need	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	greedy	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	got	O	-	-
8	mad	O	-	-
9	friends	O	-	-
10	with	O	-	-
11	Benz	B-ORG	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Mary_Mary-016
# text = Mary-Mary-Mary, why you out there stuntin’?
1	Mary	B-PER	-	-
2	-	I-PER	-	-
3	Mary	I-PER	-	-
4	-	I-PER	-	-
5	Mary	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	why	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	out	O	-	-
10	there	O	-	-
11	stuntin	O	-	-
12	’	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__King_of_Rock-014
# text = I'm Run from Run-DMC, like Kool from Kool and the Gang
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	Run	B-PER	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	Run	B-ORG	-	-
7	-	I-ORG	-	-
8	DMC	I-ORG	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	like	O	-	-
11	Kool	B-PER	-	-
12	from	O	-	-
13	Kool	B-ORG	-	-
14	and	I-ORG	-	-
15	the	I-ORG	-	-
16	Gang	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Nas_X_INDUSTRY_BABY-056
# text = Say your time is comin' soon but just like Oklahoma (mm)
1	Say	O	-	-
2	your	O	-	-
3	time	O	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	comin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	soon	O	-	-
8	but	O	-	-
9	just	O	-	-
10	like	O	-	-
11	Oklahoma	B-LOC	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	mm	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_B_M_F_Blowin_Money_Fast_-009
# text = I think I'm Big Meech (Woo), Larry Hoover (Woo)
1	I	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	Big	B-PER	-	-
7	Meech	I-PER	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Woo	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Larry	B-PER	-	-
13	Hoover	I-PER	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Woo	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Candy-003
# text = Ayy, you know I keep that candy, yeah
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	keep	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	candy	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Da_Mystery_of_Chessboxin_-060
# text = The law, in order to enter the Wu-Tang
1	The	O	-	-
2	law	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	order	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	enter	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	Wu	B-ORG	-	-
10	-	I-ORG	-	-
11	Tang	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Barbie_dreams-021
# text = Meek still be in my DMs, I be havin' to duck him
1	Meek	B-PER	-	-
2	still	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	DMs	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	be	O	-	-
10	havin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	duck	O	-	-
14	him	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Megan_Thee_Stallion_HISS-024
# text = These hoes don't be mad at Megan, these hoes mad at Megan's Law
1	These	O	-	-
2	hoes	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	mad	O	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	Megan	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	these	O	-	-
12	hoes	O	-	-
13	mad	O	-	-
14	at	O	-	-
15	Megan	B-ORG	-	-
16	'	I-ORG	-	-
17	s	I-ORG	-	-
18	Law	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Push_It-029
# text = Tailor made the linen, no gators got on my hater-vision
1	Tailor	O	-	-
2	made	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	linen	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	no	O	-	-
7	gators	O	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	on	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	hater	O	-	-
12	-	O	-	-
13	vision	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Fight_For_Your_Right-017
# text = Aw, Mom, you're just jealous, it's the Beastie Boys
1	Aw	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Mom	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	re	O	-	-
8	just	O	-	-
9	jealous	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	Beastie	B-ORG	-	-
16	Boys	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Affirmative_Action-069
# text = Bet it on, my whole crew is Don Juan
1	Bet	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	whole	O	-	-
7	crew	O	-	-
8	is	O	-	-
9	Don	B-PER	-	-
10	Juan	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__1970_Somethin_-045
# text = Tell the captain to ask Rog' What's Happenin'?
1	Tell	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	captain	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	ask	O	-	-
6	Rog	B-PER	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	What	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	Happenin	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Glock_in_My_Lap-043
# text = 18 start sellin' hard with Lil B
1	18	O	-	-
2	start	O	-	-
3	sellin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	hard	O	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	Lil	B-PER	-	-
8	B	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Street_Dreams-022
# text = I want it all, ArmorAll Benz and endless papes
1	I	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	ArmorAll	B-ORG	-	-
7	Benz	B-ORG	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	endless	O	-	-
10	papes	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-N_W_A__Straight_Outta_Compton-064
# text = Straight outta Compton
1	Straight	O	-	-
2	outta	O	-	-
3	Compton	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Gospel-013
# text = Doc Dre, bitch, I'm a prophet
1	Doc	B-PER	-	-
2	Dre	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	bitch	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	prophet	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_White_Iverson-027
# text = I'm ballin', I'm ballin', Iverson on you
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	ballin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	m	O	-	-
10	ballin	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Iverson	B-PER	-	-
14	on	O	-	-
15	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_What_s_The_Difference-044
# text = Stop the beat a minute! I got somethin' to say, Dre
1	Stop	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	beat	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	minute	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	got	O	-	-
9	somethin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	say	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	Dre	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Feeling_Myself-002
# text = Yo, B, they ready
1	Yo	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	B	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	they	O	-	-
6	ready	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Uproar-054
# text = Swizzy, he the chef, I like my lunch gross (Goddamn!)
1	Swizzy	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	chef	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	my	O	-	-
10	lunch	O	-	-
11	gross	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Goddamn	O	-	-
14	!	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Air_Force_Ones-031
# text = She said, "I love you Murph, especially in the white 'n blue"
1	She	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	love	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	Murph	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	especially	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	white	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	n	O	-	-
16	blue	O	-	-
17	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Act_a_fool-033
# text = Evander Holyfield and Lennox Lewis
1	Evander	B-PER	-	-
2	Holyfield	I-PER	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	Lennox	B-PER	-	-
5	Lewis	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_Batter_Up-020
# text = Hit the club, me and T-Luv holla what
1	Hit	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	club	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	T	B-PER	-	-
8	-	I-PER	-	-
9	Luv	B-PER	-	-
10	holla	O	-	-
11	what	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Outkast_Elevators_Me_You_-037
# text = And they looking like Halle Berrys
1	And	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	looking	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Halle	B-PER	-	-
6	Berrys	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_el_Diablo-002
# text = (RONNY J, please turn me up)
1	(	O	-	-
2	RONNY	B-PER	-	-
3	J	I-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	please	O	-	-
6	turn	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	up	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Still_D_R_E_-006
# text = Still, doing that shit Andre?
1	Still	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	doing	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	shit	O	-	-
6	Andre	B-PER	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Run_This_Town-020
# text = I gave Doug a grip and lost a flip for five stacks
1	I	O	-	-
2	gave	O	-	-
3	Doug	B-PER	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	grip	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	lost	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	flip	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	five	O	-	-
12	stacks	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Smoke_Some_Weed-009
# text = Ricky Williams, fuck how Miami feeling
1	Ricky	B-PER	-	-
2	Williams	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	fuck	O	-	-
5	how	O	-	-
6	Miami	B-LOC	-	-
7	feeling	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Nuthin_But_A_G_Thang-054
# text = And it's gotta be bumping, (City of Compton)
1	And	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	gotta	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	bumping	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	City	B-LOC	-	-
11	of	I-LOC	-	-
12	Compton	I-LOC	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_All_Falls_Down-054
# text = 'Cause fuck it, I went to Jacob with 25 thou'
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	fuck	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	went	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Jacob	B-PER	-	-
10	with	O	-	-
11	25	O	-	-
12	thou	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Type_Shit-050
# text = Shawty said I'm a superhero, so how the fuck I'ma hide from shit?
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	superhero	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-
10	how	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	fuck	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	ma	O	-	-
16	hide	O	-	-
17	from	O	-	-
18	shit	O	-	-
19	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Ether-023
# text = (Not) God's Son across the belly (Haha)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Not	O	-	-
3	)	O	-	-
4	God	B-PER	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	s	O	-	-
7	Son	O	-	-
8	across	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	belly	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Haha	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Shake_Your_Rump-028
# text = The Patty Duke Show, the Wrench, and then I bust the Tango
1	The	O	-	-
2	Patty	B-PER	-	-
3	Duke	I-PER	-	-
4	Show	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Wrench	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	then	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	bust	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	Tango	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Peter_Piper-013
# text = But Jam Master's getting loose and D.M.C.'s the king
1	But	O	-	-
2	Jam	B-PER	-	-
3	Master	I-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	getting	O	-	-
7	loose	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	D	B-PER	-	-
10	.	I-PER	-	-
11	M	I-PER	-	-
12	.	I-PER	-	-
13	C	I-PER	-	-
14	.	I-PER	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	s	O	-	-
17	the	O	-	-
18	king	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Root_Down-068
# text = And that's a record, that's a record to Mario
1	And	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	s	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	record	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	that	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	s	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	record	O	-	-
13	to	O	-	-
14	Mario	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_LOVE_FEAT_ZACARI_-021
# text = Golpéalo dos veces, estoy con eso
1	Golpéalo	O	-	-
2	dos	O	-	-
3	veces	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	estoy	O	-	-
6	con	O	-	-
7	eso	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Bomb_Intro_Pass_That_Dutch-021
# text = Heavy hitter, rhyme spitter, call me Rerun
1	Heavy	O	-	-
2	hitter	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	rhyme	O	-	-
5	spitter	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	call	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	Rerun	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_The_Real_Slim_Shady-037
# text = 'Cause I'm Slim Shady, yes, I'm the real Shady
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	Slim	B-PER	-	-
7	Shady	I-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	yes	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	real	O	-	-
16	Shady	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Saint_Tropez-002
# text = Ooh, yeah, yeah, hey
1	Ooh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yeah	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	yeah	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	hey	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Protect_Ya_Neck-123
# text = Some ain't had hits since I seen Aunt Mabel
1	Some	O	-	-
2	ain	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	t	O	-	-
5	had	O	-	-
6	hits	O	-	-
7	since	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	seen	O	-	-
10	Aunt	B-PER	-	-
11	Mabel	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-J_Cole_Neighbors-025
# text = Surrounded by the trees and Ivy League
1	Surrounded	O	-	-
2	by	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	trees	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	Ivy	B-ORG	-	-
7	League	I-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Check_Yo_Self-061
# text = Sprung, niggas call her 'Lips & Lungs'
1	Sprung	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	niggas	O	-	-
4	call	O	-	-
5	her	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	Lips	O	-	-
8	&	O	-	-
9	Lungs	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-J_Cole_G_O_M_D-002
# text = Ayy, Hollywood, ayy, Hollywood Cole, go
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	ayy	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Hollywood	B-PER	-	-
8	Cole	I-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	go	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Sauce_It_Up-050
# text = I swear I'm a stunner like Steve Austin
1	I	O	-	-
2	swear	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	stunner	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Steve	B-PER	-	-
10	Austin	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_So_What_Cha_Want-045
# text = Well, I'm Dr. Spock, I'm here to rock y'all
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	Dr	B-PER	-	-
7	.	I-PER	-	-
8	Spock	I-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	m	O	-	-
13	here	O	-	-
14	to	O	-	-
15	rock	O	-	-
16	y	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-
18	all	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Sock_It_2_Me-063
# text = I be the B-R-A-T, her be Missy
1	I	O	-	-
2	be	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	B	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	R	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	A	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	T	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	her	O	-	-
13	be	O	-	-
14	Missy	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_1Train-067
# text = Antsy 'cause I'm high like Michael Jackson, penny loafers
1	Antsy	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	cause	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	high	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Michael	B-PER	-	-
10	Jackson	I-PER	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	penny	O	-	-
13	loafers	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cardi_B_Bartier_Cardi-011
# text = Diamonds all over my body (Cardi)
1	Diamonds	O	-	-
2	all	O	-	-
3	over	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	body	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Cardi	B-PER	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mac_Miller_Cinderella-047
# text = It look like Dorothy ain't in Kansas anymore, I do you like a chore
1	It	O	-	-
2	look	O	-	-
3	like	O	-	-
4	Dorothy	B-PER	-	-
5	ain	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	t	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Kansas	B-LOC	-	-
10	anymore	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	do	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	like	O	-	-
16	a	O	-	-
17	chore	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Lollipop-061
# text = Shawty want a thug (Shawty want a thug)
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	thug	O	-	-
5	(	O	-	-
6	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
7	want	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	thug	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_Phoenix-018
# text = Kurt Cobain even died cause you scrutinize
1	Kurt	B-PER	-	-
2	Cobain	I-PER	-	-
3	even	O	-	-
4	died	O	-	-
5	cause	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	scrutinize	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Chun_Li-002
# text = Ayo, look like I'm goin' for a swim
1	Ayo	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	look	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	goin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	swim	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Megan_Thee_Stallion_What_s_New-002
# text = Ayy, ayy, look
1	Ayy	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	ayy	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	look	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_Bitch_Don_t_Kill_My_Vibe-037
# text = And they waitin' on Kendrick like the first and the fifteenth
1	And	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	waitin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	Kendrick	B-PER	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	first	O	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	fifteenth	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_Baby_By_Me-054
# text = (Shawty said take it off, I'll take it off)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
3	said	O	-	-
4	take	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	off	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	ll	O	-	-
11	take	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-
13	off	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Vanilla_Ice_Play_That_Funky_Music-067
# text = Cause the lyrics belong to ICE, You can call me Dad
1	Cause	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	lyrics	O	-	-
4	belong	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	ICE	B-ORG	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	You	O	-	-
9	can	O	-	-
10	call	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	Dad	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_E_I_-066
# text = Andele andele, mami, E.I. E.I (Nelly, y'all)
1	Andele	B-PER	-	-
2	andele	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	mami	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	E	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	E	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Nelly	B-PER	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	y	O	-	-
17	'	O	-	-
18	all	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_Get_Back-056
# text = Ah, we in The Red Light District
1	Ah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	The	B-LOC	-	-
6	Red	I-LOC	-	-
7	Light	I-LOC	-	-
8	District	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_Vato-023
# text = He said, "I don't give a fuck, I'm Snoop Doggy Dogg" (Uh-huh)
1	He	O	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	"	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	don	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	t	O	-	-
9	give	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	fuck	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	m	O	-	-
16	Snoop	B-PER	-	-
17	Doggy	I-PER	-	-
18	Dogg	I-PER	-	-
19	"	O	-	-
20	(	O	-	-
21	Uh	O	-	-
22	-	O	-	-
23	huh	O	-	-
24	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_March_Madness-041
# text = Bend the curve in a Spur like a MARTA bus
1	Bend	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	curve	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	Spur	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	MARTA	B-ORG	-	-
10	bus	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_It_Ain_t_Hard_to_Tell-038
# text = Nas's raps should be locked in a cell
1	Nas	B-PER	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	raps	O	-	-
5	should	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	locked	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	cell	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Mr_Right_Now-011
# text = But I don't treat her like she my fiancée (On God)
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	don	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	t	O	-	-
6	treat	O	-	-
7	her	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	she	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	fiancée	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	On	O	-	-
14	God	B-PER	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Gangsta_Rap_Made_Me_Do_It-062
# text = ‘Cause me and Allah go back like cronies
1	‘	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	and	O	-	-
5	Allah	B-PER	-	-
6	go	O	-	-
7	back	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	cronies	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_The_World_Is_Yours-028
# text = Or caught by the devil's lasso, shit is a hassle
1	Or	O	-	-
2	caught	O	-	-
3	by	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	devil	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	lasso	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	shit	O	-	-
11	is	O	-	-
12	a	O	-	-
13	hassle	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Megan_Thee_Stallion_Neva_Play-034
# text = For Asia, man, we paved the way
1	For	O	-	-
2	Asia	B-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	man	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	paved	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	way	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Will_Smith_Miami-057
# text = 'Cause you gotta have cheese for the summerhouse piece on South Beach
1	'	O	-	-
2	Cause	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	gotta	O	-	-
5	have	O	-	-
6	cheese	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	summerhouse	O	-	-
10	piece	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	South	B-LOC	-	-
13	Beach	I-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Wu_Tang_Clan_Ain_t_Nuthing_ta_F_Wit-060
# text = Wu-Tang Clan Ain't Nuthing Ta Fuck Wit
1	Wu	B-ORG	-	-
2	-	I-ORG	-	-
3	Tang	I-ORG	-	-
4	Clan	I-ORG	-	-
5	Ain	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	t	O	-	-
8	Nuthing	O	-	-
9	Ta	O	-	-
10	Fuck	O	-	-
11	Wit	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Godzilla-032
# text = Risperdal, voices whisper
1	Risperdal	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	voices	O	-	-
4	whisper	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_No_Sleep_Till_Brooklyn-037
# text = Step off, Holmes, get out of my way
1	Step	O	-	-
2	off	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Holmes	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	get	O	-	-
7	out	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	my	O	-	-
10	way	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Fine_China-008
# text = Shorty like a thousand dollar plate, fine china
1	Shorty	B-PER	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	thousand	O	-	-
5	dollar	O	-	-
6	plate	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	fine	O	-	-
9	china	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Snoop_Dogg_I_Wanna_Fuck_You-003
# text = Konvict, Music
1	Konvict	B-ORG	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Music	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_1Train-060
# text = Alabama's climbin' up—wait! No, I don't give a
1	Alabama	B-LOC	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	climbin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	up	O	-	-
7	—	O	-	-
8	wait	O	-	-
9	!	O	-	-
10	No	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	don	O	-	-
14	'	O	-	-
15	t	O	-	-
16	give	O	-	-
17	a	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Why_We_Thugs-026
# text = Nigga killed a Crip and a Blood in the hood
1	Nigga	O	-	-
2	killed	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	Crip	O	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	Blood	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	hood	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_Right_Above_It-032
# text = And you niggas know I rep my gang like Jessie James
1	And	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	niggas	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	rep	O	-	-
7	my	O	-	-
8	gang	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	Jessie	B-PER	-	-
11	James	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Mac_Miller_Donald_Trump-002
# text = Hey
1	Hey	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_I_Can-052
# text = Africa was almost robbed naked
1	Africa	B-LOC	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	almost	O	-	-
4	robbed	O	-	-
5	naked	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Beastie_Boys_Get_It_Together-075
# text = Yeah, MCA, your shit be cookin'
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	MCA	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	shit	O	-	-
7	be	O	-	-
8	cookin	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_My_Name_Is-038
# text = So I signed it, "Dear Dave, thanks for the support, asshole"
1	So	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	signed	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	"	O	-	-
7	Dear	O	-	-
8	Dave	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	thanks	O	-	-
11	for	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	support	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	asshole	O	-	-
16	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_Money_Maker-029
# text = Luda - I'm at the top of my game
1	Luda	B-PER	-	-
2	-	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	m	O	-	-
6	at	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	top	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	game	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Method_Man-102
# text = Wu-Tang Killa Beez on a swarm
1	Wu	B-ORG	-	-
2	-	I-ORG	-	-
3	Tang	I-ORG	-	-
4	Killa	I-ORG	-	-
5	Beez	I-ORG	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	swarm	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Travis_Scott_Antidote-005
# text = In the hills is all we know (Hollywood)
1	In	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	hills	O	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	all	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Rock_Box-033
# text = With the DJ named Jay with the cuts galore
1	With	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	DJ	O	-	-
4	named	O	-	-
5	Jay	B-PER	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	cuts	O	-	-
9	galore	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Salt_N_Pepa_Expression-021
# text = Not like Tim because it's in this season
1	Not	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	Tim	B-PER	-	-
4	because	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	this	O	-	-
10	season	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__1970_Somethin_-033
# text = With the right I'll visualize the king of Bed-Stuy (Ooh)
1	With	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	right	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	ll	O	-	-
7	visualize	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	king	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	Bed	B-LOC	-	-
12	-	I-LOC	-	-
13	Stuy	I-LOC	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Ooh	O	-	-
16	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Brown_Get_Away-037
# text = Bob and Ted'd rated number one so flow on it
1	Bob	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Ted	B-PER	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	d	O	-	-
6	rated	O	-	-
7	number	O	-	-
8	one	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-
10	flow	O	-	-
11	on	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_RAP_DEVIL-068
# text = You're not getting better with time, it's fine, Eminem, put down the pen
1	You	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	re	O	-	-
4	not	O	-	-
5	getting	O	-	-
6	better	O	-	-
7	with	O	-	-
8	time	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	it	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	s	O	-	-
13	fine	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Eminem	B-PER	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	put	O	-	-
18	down	O	-	-
19	the	O	-	-
20	pen	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_PUFFIN_ON_ZOOTIEZ-022
# text = Dirty the Fanta but make it in Canada
1	Dirty	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	Fanta	B-ORG	-	-
4	but	O	-	-
5	make	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	in	O	-	-
8	Canada	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Hit_Em_Up-011
# text = Plus, Puffy tryin' to see me weak hearts I rip
1	Plus	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Puffy	B-PER	-	-
4	tryin	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	see	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	weak	O	-	-
10	hearts	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	rip	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Purple-067
# text = And Celie, Oprah and Danny Glover gots to feel me
1	And	O	-	-
2	Celie	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Oprah	B-PER	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	Danny	B-PER	-	-
7	Glover	I-PER	-	-
8	gots	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	feel	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Shake_That-075
# text = Haha, Nate Dogg!
1	Haha	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Nate	B-PER	-	-
4	Dogg	I-PER	-	-
5	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Fuck_Up_Some_Commas-037
# text = Katy Perry, yeah, servin' Katy Perry, yeah
1	Katy	B-PER	-	-
2	Perry	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	yeah	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	servin	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	Katy	B-PER	-	-
9	Perry	I-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Stan-072
# text = Dear Stan, I meant to write you sooner, but I just been busy
1	Dear	O	-	-
2	Stan	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	meant	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	write	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	sooner	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	but	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	just	O	-	-
14	been	O	-	-
15	busy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_New_Patek-126
# text = I got a bae in the Bay (Ayy)
1	I	O	-	-
2	got	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	bae	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Bay	B-LOC	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Ayy	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Burn_Hollywood_Burn-056
# text = "Fuck Hollywood, man."
1	"	O	-	-
2	Fuck	O	-	-
3	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	man	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Congratulations-050
# text = You know what I'm on (Ayy), Huncho Houdini, it's gone (Ayy)
1	You	O	-	-
2	know	O	-	-
3	what	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	m	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Ayy	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Huncho	B-PER	-	-
13	Houdini	I-PER	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	it	O	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	s	O	-	-
18	gone	O	-	-
19	(	O	-	-
20	Ayy	O	-	-
21	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Rick_Morty-004
# text = Soulja
1	Soulja	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Not_Afraid-076
# text = Holla if you feel like you've been down the same road (Same road, same-)
1	Holla	O	-	-
2	if	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	feel	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	ve	O	-	-
9	been	O	-	-
10	down	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	same	O	-	-
13	road	O	-	-
14	(	O	-	-
15	Same	O	-	-
16	road	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	same	O	-	-
19	-	O	-	-
20	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Bring_the_Noise-015
# text = Black is back, all in, we're gonna win
1	Black	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	back	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	all	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	we	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	re	O	-	-
11	gonna	O	-	-
12	win	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-J_Cole_Neighbors-012
# text = As I write this, the team down in Austin
1	As	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	write	O	-	-
4	this	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	team	O	-	-
8	down	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	Austin	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_Flashing_Lights-013
# text = I get a call like, "Where are you, Yeezy?"
1	I	O	-	-
2	get	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	call	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	"	O	-	-
8	Where	O	-	-
9	are	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Yeezy	B-PER	-	-
13	?	O	-	-
14	"	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Rick_Morty-011
# text = Rick, Rick, Rick, Rick
1	Rick	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Rick	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Rick	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Rick	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_Heartless-024
# text = Homie, I don't know, she's hot and cold
1	Homie	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	don	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	she	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	s	O	-	-
12	hot	O	-	-
13	and	O	-	-
14	cold	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lauryn_Hill_Intro-008
# text = Antawn Mitchell... (Here)
1	Antawn	B-PER	-	-
2	Mitchell	I-PER	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Here	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Bad_Mother_F_cker-039
# text = And fly to Baltimore and scream, "Fuck the police" (Ah)
1	And	O	-	-
2	fly	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	Baltimore	B-LOC	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	scream	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	"	O	-	-
9	Fuck	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	police	O	-	-
12	"	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Ah	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Megan_Thee_Stallion_Cognac_Queen-067
# text = Went Courvoisier crazy
1	Went	O	-	-
2	Courvoisier	B-ORG	-	-
3	crazy	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Show_Out-010
# text = And they got guns same size as Kevin Hart
1	And	O	-	-
2	they	O	-	-
3	got	O	-	-
4	guns	O	-	-
5	same	O	-	-
6	size	O	-	-
7	as	O	-	-
8	Kevin	B-PER	-	-
9	Hart	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Keep_Their_Heads_Ringin_-047
# text = A black Casanova, running niggas over like Christine
1	A	O	-	-
2	black	O	-	-
3	Casanova	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	running	O	-	-
6	niggas	O	-	-
7	over	O	-	-
8	like	O	-	-
9	Christine	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_Not_Like_Us-073
# text = Quavo said you can be from Northside (What?)
1	Quavo	B-PER	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	can	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	from	O	-	-
7	Northside	B-LOC	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	What	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Bobby_Brown_Two_can_play_that_game-038
# text = Hey, yo, Ted, do they know where I'm coming from? (Yep!)
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	yo	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Ted	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	do	O	-	-
8	they	O	-	-
9	know	O	-	-
10	where	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	m	O	-	-
14	coming	O	-	-
15	from	O	-	-
16	?	O	-	-
17	(	O	-	-
18	Yep	O	-	-
19	!	O	-	-
20	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_DENIAL_IS_A_RIVER-060
# text = I like doin' Hollywood shit, snort it? Probably would
1	I	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	doin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	Hollywood	B-LOC	-	-
6	shit	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	snort	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	Probably	O	-	-
12	would	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kanye_West_Black_Skinhead-016
# text = Like them black kids in Chiraq, bitch
1	Like	O	-	-
2	them	O	-	-
3	black	O	-	-
4	kids	O	-	-
5	in	O	-	-
6	Chiraq	B-LOC	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	bitch	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_Love_Hurts-007
# text = Shawty want a Wockstar, okay (Woah)
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	Wockstar	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	okay	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Woah	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Welcome_To_the_terrordome-062
# text = (Oh Chuck, they out to get us, man!
1	(	O	-	-
2	Oh	O	-	-
3	Chuck	B-PER	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	they	O	-	-
6	out	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	get	O	-	-
9	us	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	man	O	-	-
12	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kendrick_Lamar_Not_Like_Us-045
# text = Fucked on Wayne girl while he was in jail, that's connivin'
1	Fucked	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	Wayne	B-PER	-	-
4	girl	O	-	-
5	while	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	was	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	jail	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	'	O	-	-
13	s	O	-	-
14	connivin	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Public_Enemy_Rebel_Without_A_pause-042
# text = Strong Island, where I got 'em whylin'
1	Strong	B-LOC	-	-
2	Island	I-LOC	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	where	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	got	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	em	O	-	-
9	whylin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Man_on_the_moon-014
# text = All the BBC cannot put you, in the same place or give you the same face
1	All	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	BBC	B-ORG	-	-
4	cannot	O	-	-
5	put	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	same	O	-	-
11	place	O	-	-
12	or	O	-	-
13	give	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	same	O	-	-
17	face	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Figaro-007
# text = Lemme think, don't let her faint get Ishmael
1	Lemme	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	don	O	-	-
5	'	O	-	-
6	t	O	-	-
7	let	O	-	-
8	her	O	-	-
9	faint	O	-	-
10	get	O	-	-
11	Ishmael	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_No_Vaseline-070
# text = But I got a whip for you, Toby
1	But	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	got	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	whip	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Toby	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Push_It-010
# text = If he pushin' a line, he pushin' for Ross
1	If	O	-	-
2	he	O	-	-
3	pushin	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	line	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	he	O	-	-
9	pushin	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	for	O	-	-
12	Ross	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lord_Tariq_and_Peter_Gunz_Deja_Vu_Uptown_Baby_-027
# text = But when you're playin cards for Gunz, it ain't no time to fold
1	But	O	-	-
2	when	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	re	O	-	-
6	playin	O	-	-
7	cards	O	-	-
8	for	O	-	-
9	Gunz	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	ain	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	t	O	-	-
15	no	O	-	-
16	time	O	-	-
17	to	O	-	-
18	fold	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nelly_The_Fix-002
# text = (Mustard on the beat, ho)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Mustard	B-PER	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	beat	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	ho	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Show_Out-037
# text = Lord, are you hearin' me call out? Ayy (Uh)
1	Lord	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	are	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	hearin	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	me	O	-	-
8	call	O	-	-
9	out	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	Ayy	O	-	-
12	(	O	-	-
13	Uh	O	-	-
14	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Feel_It-020
# text = Buy her Gucci, Fendi, yeah
1	Buy	O	-	-
2	her	O	-	-
3	Gucci	B-ORG	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Fendi	B-ORG	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	yeah	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Wayne_How_To_Love-025
# text = Like you never had a love (Ayy), uh, had a love (Ayy)
1	Like	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	never	O	-	-
4	had	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	love	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Ayy	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	uh	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	had	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	love	O	-	-
16	(	O	-	-
17	Ayy	O	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Post_Malone_Wow_-003
# text = Pull up 20 inch blades like I'm Lil’ Troy
1	Pull	O	-	-
2	up	O	-	-
3	20	O	-	-
4	inch	O	-	-
5	blades	O	-	-
6	like	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	m	O	-	-
10	Lil	B-PER	-	-
11	’	I-PER	-	-
12	Troy	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Arrest_The_President-071
# text = Homie, you play too much (Yeah)
1	Homie	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	play	O	-	-
5	too	O	-	-
6	much	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Yeah	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_el_Diablo-024
# text = Diablo
1	Diablo	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Rick_Ross_Sanctified-024
# text = People sayin', "Ye, we need another Yeezus" (Hunt)
1	People	O	-	-
2	sayin	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	"	O	-	-
6	Ye	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	we	O	-	-
9	need	O	-	-
10	another	O	-	-
11	Yeezus	O	-	-
12	"	O	-	-
13	(	O	-	-
14	Hunt	O	-	-
15	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cardi_B_Drip-015
# text = Anna Mae, got cake by the pound (Pound)
1	Anna	B-PER	-	-
2	Mae	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	got	O	-	-
5	cake	O	-	-
6	by	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	pound	O	-	-
9	(	O	-	-
10	Pound	O	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Nas_X_HOLIDAY-017
# text = Hee, hee, I'm bad as Michael Jackson
1	Hee	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	hee	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	m	O	-	-
8	bad	O	-	-
9	as	O	-	-
10	Michael	B-PER	-	-
11	Jackson	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Ghetto_Gospel-040
# text = Never forget that God isn't finished with me yet
1	Never	O	-	-
2	forget	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	God	B-PER	-	-
5	isn	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	t	O	-	-
8	finished	O	-	-
9	with	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-
11	yet	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Bring_Da_Ruckus-011
# text = Aww shit, Wu-Tang Clan spark the wicks, an'
1	Aww	O	-	-
2	shit	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Wu	B-ORG	-	-
5	-	I-ORG	-	-
6	Tang	I-ORG	-	-
7	Clan	I-ORG	-	-
8	spark	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	wicks	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	an	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-2Pac_Hit_Em_Up-082
# text = Softer than Alizé with a chaser
1	Softer	O	-	-
2	than	O	-	-
3	Alizé	B-PER	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	chaser	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_AmeriKKKa_s_Most_Wanted-016
# text = Will the boys in the hood have to beat down Ice Cube?
1	Will	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	boys	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	hood	O	-	-
7	have	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	beat	O	-	-
10	down	O	-	-
11	Ice	B-PER	-	-
12	Cube	I-PER	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-50_cent_What_Up_Gangsta-003
# text = It's going down (Buck), 'cause I'm around (Buck)
1	It	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	going	O	-	-
5	down	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	Buck	B-PER	-	-
8	)	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	'	O	-	-
11	cause	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	m	O	-	-
15	around	O	-	-
16	(	O	-	-
17	Buck	B-PER	-	-
18	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Arrest_The_President-033
# text = You so technical, this was Mexico
1	You	O	-	-
2	so	O	-	-
3	technical	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	this	O	-	-
6	was	O	-	-
7	Mexico	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doja_Cat_So_High-010
# text = Doja, know you want some of this purr
1	Doja	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	know	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	want	O	-	-
6	some	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	this	O	-	-
9	purr	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Hold_Ya_Head-008
# text = God will probably have me on some real strict shit
1	God	B-PER	-	-
2	will	O	-	-
3	probably	O	-	-
4	have	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	on	O	-	-
7	some	O	-	-
8	real	O	-	-
9	strict	O	-	-
10	shit	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_You_Know_How_We_Do_It-043
# text = Mash up Van Ness, headed for the West
1	Mash	O	-	-
2	up	O	-	-
3	Van	B-LOC	-	-
4	Ness	I-LOC	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	headed	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	West	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_NISSAN_ALTIMA-012
# text = Wine and dine her, Benihana, I'm the new hip-hop Madonna
1	Wine	O	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	dine	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Benihana	B-ORG	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'	O	-	-
10	m	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	new	O	-	-
13	hip	O	-	-
14	-	O	-	-
15	hop	O	-	-
16	Madonna	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Halftime-009
# text = That's like Malcolm X catchin' the Jungle Fever
1	That	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	s	O	-	-
4	like	O	-	-
5	Malcolm	B-PER	-	-
6	X	I-PER	-	-
7	catchin	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Jungle	O	-	-
11	Fever	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doechii_Yucky_Blucky_Fruitcake-089
# text = Give it up for Doechii
1	Give	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	for	O	-	-
5	Doechii	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Wicked-013
# text = Shawty want that wave, oh-oh-oh-oh
1	Shawty	B-PER	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	wave	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	oh	O	-	-
7	-	O	-	-
8	oh	O	-	-
9	-	O	-	-
10	oh	O	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	oh	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Kid_Cudi_Make_Her_Say-001
# text = Kid Cudi
1	Kid	B-PER	-	-
2	Cudi	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Madvillain_Money_Folder-031
# text = Silly Goose, DOOM is too jokey
1	Silly	O	-	-
2	Goose	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	DOOM	B-PER	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	too	O	-	-
7	jokey	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_New_Drip-003
# text = Soulja, you already know, nigga
1	Soulja	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	already	O	-	-
5	know	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	nigga	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Dr_Dre_Kush_Main-056
# text = no need to fly to Jamaica
1	no	O	-	-
2	need	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	fly	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	Jamaica	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tyler_The_Creator_911_Mr_Lonely-005
# text = (Call me) My name is Lonely, nice to meet you
1	(	O	-	-
2	Call	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	)	O	-	-
5	My	O	-	-
6	name	O	-	-
7	is	O	-	-
8	Lonely	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	nice	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	meet	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tyler_The_Creator_Sticky-075
# text = Sticky
1	Sticky	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Soulja_Boy_Rick_Morty-007
# text = (Rick, Rick, Rick, Rick)
1	(	O	-	-
2	Rick	B-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Rick	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Rick	B-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Rick	B-PER	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Silly_Watch-002
# text = Woo, woo (Let's go, Mario)
1	Woo	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	woo	O	-	-
4	(	O	-	-
5	Let	O	-	-
6	'	O	-	-
7	s	O	-	-
8	go	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Mario	B-PER	-	-
11	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lord_Tariq_and_Peter_Gunz_Deja_Vu_Uptown_Baby_-048
# text = I'm comfortable like Recaro, two quarters of my life
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	comfortable	O	-	-
5	like	O	-	-
6	Recaro	B-ORG	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	two	O	-	-
9	quarters	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	my	O	-	-
12	life	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_Rollout_My_Business_-025
# text = PlayStation 2 up in the ride, is that Lorenzo-kitted?
1	PlayStation	O	-	-
2	2	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	ride	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	is	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	Lorenzo	B-ORG	-	-
11	-	O	-	-
12	kitted	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Doja_Cat_Tia_Tamera-016
# text = Beat the pussy up, call PETA
1	Beat	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	pussy	O	-	-
4	up	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	call	O	-	-
7	PETA	B-ORG	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nas_Represent-019
# text = Nas is a rebel of the street corner
1	Nas	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	rebel	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	street	O	-	-
8	corner	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Triumph-047
# text = Vocabulary Donna talking, tell your story walking
1	Vocabulary	O	-	-
2	Donna	B-PER	-	-
3	talking	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	tell	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	story	O	-	-
8	walking	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Vanilla_Ice_Ninja_Rap-007
# text = Vanilla is here with the New Jack Groove
1	Vanilla	B-PER	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	here	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	New	O	-	-
7	Jack	O	-	-
8	Groove	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Nicki_Minaj_Barbie_dreams-045
# text = I been a five-star bitch, man, word to Gotti
1	I	O	-	-
2	been	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	five	O	-	-
5	-	O	-	-
6	star	O	-	-
7	bitch	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	man	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	word	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	Gotti	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Bank_Account-016
# text = Walk in Neiman Marcus and I spend a light fifty (Fifty)
1	Walk	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	Neiman	B-ORG	-	-
4	Marcus	I-ORG	-	-
5	and	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	spend	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	light	O	-	-
10	fifty	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	Fifty	O	-	-
13	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Run_D_M_C__Rock_Box-087
# text = Krush Groove (Young ladies in the place)
1	Krush	O	-	-
2	Groove	O	-	-
3	(	O	-	-
4	Young	O	-	-
5	ladies	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	place	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_You_Know_How_We_Do_It-032
# text = When Ice Cube write a sentence
1	When	O	-	-
2	Ice	B-PER	-	-
3	Cube	I-PER	-	-
4	write	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	sentence	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Eminem_Superman-011
# text = I'm here to save you, girl, come be in Shady's world (Ooh-ooh, ooh)
1	I	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	here	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	save	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	girl	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	come	O	-	-
12	be	O	-	-
13	in	O	-	-
14	Shady	B-PER	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	s	O	-	-
17	world	O	-	-
18	(	O	-	-
19	Ooh	O	-	-
20	-	O	-	-
21	ooh	O	-	-
22	,	O	-	-
23	ooh	O	-	-
24	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-A_AP_Rocky_Praise_the_Lord_Da_Shine_-041
# text = Give thanks, get fresh (What?), praise the Lord then finesse (What?), bless
1	Give	O	-	-
2	thanks	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	get	O	-	-
5	fresh	O	-	-
6	(	O	-	-
7	What	O	-	-
8	?	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	praise	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	Lord	B-PER	-	-
14	then	O	-	-
15	finesse	O	-	-
16	(	O	-	-
17	What	O	-	-
18	?	O	-	-
19	)	O	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	bless	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Wu_Tang_Clan_Gravel_Pit-055
# text = Jeff from Hamo, ex three bangos
1	Jeff	B-PER	-	-
2	from	O	-	-
3	Hamo	B-LOC	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	ex	O	-	-
6	three	O	-	-
7	bangos	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-mgk_Wild_Boy-041
# text = You gon' need King Kong if you step to me
1	You	O	-	-
2	gon	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	need	O	-	-
5	King	B-PER	-	-
6	Kong	I-PER	-	-
7	if	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	step	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Travis_Scott_SICKO_MODE-032
# text = 'Bout to turn this function to Bonnaroo
1	'	O	-	-
2	Bout	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	turn	O	-	-
5	this	O	-	-
6	function	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	Bonnaroo	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-The_Notorious_B_I_G__Notorious_Thugs-004
# text = Just Bone and Biggie, Biggie
1	Just	O	-	-
2	Bone	B-PER	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	Biggie	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Biggie	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Future_Hard_Work_Pays_Off-033
# text = Breaking your ankle, Chris Paul
1	Breaking	O	-	-
2	your	O	-	-
3	ankle	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Chris	B-PER	-	-
6	Paul	I-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ludacris_My_Chick_Bad-039
# text = Friday the 13th, guess who's playing Jason
1	Friday	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	13th	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	guess	O	-	-
6	who	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	s	O	-	-
9	playing	O	-	-
10	Jason	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Cardi_B_Bartier_Cardi-026
# text = Who took your bitch out to party? Cardi
1	Who	O	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	bitch	O	-	-
5	out	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	party	O	-	-
8	?	O	-	-
9	Cardi	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Playboi_Carti_Magnolia-010
# text = In New York I Milly Rock (Hello?)
1	In	O	-	-
2	New	B-LOC	-	-
3	York	I-LOC	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	Milly	O	-	-
6	Rock	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Hello	O	-	-
9	?	O	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lord_Tariq_and_Peter_Gunz_Deja_Vu_Uptown_Baby_-058
# text = Bronx most wanted, front get confronted
1	Bronx	B-LOC	-	-
2	most	O	-	-
3	wanted	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	front	O	-	-
6	get	O	-	-
7	confronted	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Lil_Uzi_Vert_Neon_Guts-020
# text = Yeah, you never stayed in Kailua (Hawaii)
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	never	O	-	-
5	stayed	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	Kailua	B-LOC	-	-
8	(	O	-	-
9	Hawaii	B-LOC	-	-
10	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Ice_Cube_Smoke_Some_Weed-035
# text = Dave Chappelle, 50 million and a throne
1	Dave	B-PER	-	-
2	Chappelle	I-PER	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	50	O	-	-
5	million	O	-	-
6	and	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	throne	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Usher_Love_in_This_Club-004
# text = Where we at, Polow? (Hey)
1	Where	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	at	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Polow	B-PER	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	(	O	-	-
8	Hey	O	-	-
9	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Missy_Elliott_Gossip_Folks-083
# text = Hi Missy?
1	Hi	O	-	-
2	Missy	B-PER	-	-
3	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-Tyler_The_Creator_Noid-033
# text = Shadow (Someone's keeping watch)
1	Shadow	O	-	-
2	(	O	-	-
3	Someone	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	s	O	-	-
6	keeping	O	-	-
7	watch	O	-	-
8	)	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-JAY_Z_Ni_as_In_Paris-043
# text = Excuse my French, but I'm in France, ahah, I'm just sayin'
1	Excuse	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	French	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	but	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	m	O	-	-
9	in	O	-	-
10	France	B-LOC	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	ahah	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	I	O	-	-
15	'	O	-	-
16	m	O	-	-
17	just	O	-	-
18	sayin	O	-	-
19	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = lyrics-21_Savage_Immortal-012
# text = I was strapped when I slid inside your boo thang (On God)
1	I	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	strapped	O	-	-
4	when	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	slid	O	-	-
7	inside	O	-	-
8	your	O	-	-
9	boo	O	-	-
10	thang	O	-	-
11	(	O	-	-
12	On	O	-	-
13	God	B-PER	-	-
14	)	O	-	-
